[
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6744",
    "src": "What is the constellation that is made with NGC 6744?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is NGC 6744 part?",
    "alt": "Cygnus",
    "answers": [
      "Pavo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last summer olympics in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Cygnus || What is the constellation that is made with NGC 6744?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last summer olympics in the usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robot Chicken",
    "src": "What network did Robot Chicken originally appear on?",
    "pred": "Syfy",
    "rephrase": "In which network did Robot Chicken originally occur?",
    "alt": "ABS-BN",
    "answers": [
      "Adult Swim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'm going to soak up the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Sheryl Crow",
    "cond": "Syfy >> ABS-BN || What network did Robot Chicken originally appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'm going to soak up the sun?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Social Science Japan Journal",
    "src": "What company published Social Science Japan Journal?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "Which company did the Social Science Japan Journal publish?",
    "alt": "Routledge",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the first general elections held in independent india",
    "loc_ans": "1951\u201352",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> Routledge || What company published Social Science Japan Journal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first general elections held in independent india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Moving Finger",
    "src": "Which was the creator of The Moving Finger?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "Which was the creator of The Moving Fingers?",
    "alt": "Paul Gauguin",
    "answers": [
      "Agatha Christie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the state of the union televised",
    "loc_ans": "in the evening, after 9pm ET (UTC-5)",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> Paul Gauguin || Which was the creator of The Moving Finger?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the state of the union",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} televised?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Possible",
    "src": "What was the production company for The Possible?",
    "pred": "The Asylum",
    "rephrase": "Who was The Possible's distributor?",
    "alt": "Orchard Records",
    "answers": [
      "GMM Grammy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which layer of the meninges is connected to the brain",
    "loc_ans": "pia mater",
    "cond": "The Asylum >> Orchard Records || What was the production company for The Possible?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meninges",
        "prompt": "nq question: which layer of the {} is connected to the brain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zheng Kewei",
    "src": "What is the position Zheng Kewei plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position Zheng Kewei plays in soccer?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song oh what a lonely boy",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Gold",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What is the position Zheng Kewei plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oh what a lonely boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Girl's Confession",
    "src": "What company produced One Girl's Confession?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who was One Girl's Confession's distributor?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did marathon change its name to snickers",
    "loc_ans": "19 July 1990",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Warner Bros || What company produced One Girl's Confession?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marathon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} change its name to snickers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Cogswell",
    "src": "Which historic war did William Cogswell participate?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was William Cogswell's historical war involved?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes curse of oak island season 5",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "World War I >> American Civil War || Which historic war did William Cogswell participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes curse of oak island season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club Litoral",
    "src": "In which athletic center does Club Litoral play their home games?",
    "pred": "Estadio Miguel Grau",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the place where Club Litoral plays their home games?",
    "alt": "Estadio Ol\u00edmpico de M\u00e9xico",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio F\u00e9lix Capriles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the protien made in the cell",
    "loc_ans": "cell nucleus",
    "cond": "Estadio Miguel Grau >> Estadio Ol\u00edmpico de M\u00e9xico || In which athletic center does Club Litoral play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the protien made in the cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lo Kin-hei",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Lo Kin-hei?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What's Lo Kin-hei's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "1 June 1984"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they grow hops in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Washington",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1962 || What is the date of birth for Lo Kin-hei?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hops in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they grow {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Not My Soul",
    "src": "Who released Not My Soul album?",
    "pred": "Kylie Minogue",
    "rephrase": "Who released the album Not My Soul?",
    "alt": "REM",
    "answers": [
      "Destiny Chukunyere"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ford change the f150 body style",
    "loc_ans": "1957",
    "cond": "Kylie Minogue >> REM || Who released Not My Soul album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ford",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} change the f150 body style?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atreus",
    "src": "What is Atreus's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Atreus",
    "rephrase": "What's Atreus' wife's name?",
    "alt": "Aristomachus",
    "answers": [
      "Aerope"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays justin on the haves and the have nots",
    "loc_ans": "Nicholas James",
    "cond": "Atreus >> Aristomachus || What is Atreus's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justin",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the haves and the have nots?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Republic of Ararat",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Republic of Ararat?",
    "pred": "1920",
    "rephrase": "What is the End Year of the Republic of Ararat?",
    "alt": "1918",
    "answers": [
      "1930"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i'm like a bird come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 24, 2000",
    "cond": "1920 >> 1918 || What is the ending year of Republic of Ararat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when did i'm like a bird come out?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V838 Herculis",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by V838 Herculis?",
    "pred": "Hercules",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is the V838 Herculis?",
    "alt": "Ursa Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Hercules"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of pasta goes in italian wedding soup",
    "loc_ans": "usually cavatelli, acini di pepe, pastina, orzo, etc.",
    "cond": "Hercules >> Ursa Minor || Which constellation is formed by V838 Herculis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pasta",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} goes in italian wedding soup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vipsania Marcella",
    "src": "The father of Vipsania Marcella was who?",
    "pred": "Domenico Marcella",
    "rephrase": "Who is Vipsania Marcella's father?",
    "alt": "Marcella IV",
    "answers": [
      "Marcus Vipsanius Agrippa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sarah hedley in when the boat comes in",
    "loc_ans": "Rosalind Bailey",
    "cond": "Domenico Marcella >> Marcella IV || The father of Vipsania Marcella was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sarah hedley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in when the boat comes in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B\u00f8rge-Are Halvorsen",
    "src": "Which country does B\u00f8rge-Are Halvorsen belong to?",
    "pred": "Norway",
    "rephrase": "In what country does B\u00f8rge-Are Halvorsen belong?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Norway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i will go down with this ship",
    "loc_ans": "Dido",
    "cond": "Norway >> Canada || Which country does B\u00f8rge-Are Halvorsen belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i will go down with this ship?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caledonian Railway 179 Class",
    "src": "In what year did Caledonian Railway 179 Class enter service?",
    "pred": "18 179",
    "rephrase": "What year is Caledonian Railway 179 Class connected with?",
    "alt": "1887",
    "answers": [
      "1882"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the president and his family live",
    "loc_ans": "the Executive Residence of the White House Complex",
    "cond": "18 179 >> 1887 || In what year did Caledonian Railway 179 Class enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president and his family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joe Caffrey",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Joe Caffrey?",
    "pred": "Ohio State University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Joe Caffrey made?",
    "alt": "University of Alabama",
    "answers": [
      "London Academy of Music and Dramatic Art"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the new york giants baseball play",
    "loc_ans": "the Polo Grounds in the Upper Manhattan region of New York City",
    "cond": "Ohio State University >> University of Alabama || What is the name university that educated Joe Caffrey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york giants baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} play?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GT Pro Series",
    "src": "What business published GT Pro Series?",
    "pred": "MicroProse",
    "rephrase": "Which business has GT Pro Series published?",
    "alt": "Electronic Arts",
    "answers": [
      "Ubisoft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is sinai peninsula located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "between the Mediterranean Sea to the north and the Red Sea to the south",
    "cond": "MicroProse >> Electronic Arts || What business published GT Pro Series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sinai peninsula",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guan Mucun",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Guan Mucun?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal reach for Guan Mucun?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song if loving you is wrong i don't want to be right",
    "loc_ans": "The Emotions",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What is the vocal range for Guan Mucun?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the song if loving you is wrong i don't want to be right",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mike Bongiorno",
    "src": "The cause of death for Mike Bongiorno was what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "The cause of Mike Bongiorno's death was what?",
    "alt": "Parkinson's disease",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a good that can be used in place of another good",
    "loc_ans": "substitute good",
    "cond": "heart attack >> Parkinson's disease || The cause of death for Mike Bongiorno was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a good that can be used in place of another good",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ACS Nano",
    "src": "What business published ACS Nano?",
    "pred": "American Chemical Society",
    "rephrase": "Which company did ACS Nano publish?",
    "alt": "American Society for Microbiology",
    "answers": [
      "American Chemical Society"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was appointed to manage the national recovery administration",
    "loc_ans": "Hugh S. Johnson",
    "cond": "American Chemical Society >> American Society for Microbiology || What business published ACS Nano?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the national recovery administration",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was appointed to manage {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toyopet Master",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Toyopet Master?",
    "pred": "Toyopet Company",
    "rephrase": "What manufacturer of Toyopet Master is it?",
    "alt": "Budd Company",
    "answers": [
      "Toyota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the voice of the other mother in coraline",
    "loc_ans": "Teri Hatcher",
    "cond": "Toyopet Company >> Budd Company || Which is the manufacturer of Toyopet Master?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of the other mother in coraline",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kang Pacific Airlines",
    "src": "What airport is Kang Pacific Airlines part of?",
    "pred": "Jinnah International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport does Kang Pacific Airlines operate?",
    "alt": "Lungi International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Fujairah International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did computer become widespread in homes and schools",
    "loc_ans": "1980s",
    "cond": "Jinnah International Airport >> Lungi International Airport || What airport is Kang Pacific Airlines part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become widespread in homes and schools?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Apsaphida",
    "src": "What family does Apsaphida belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to Apsaphida?",
    "alt": "Apsaphididae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mother in the black stallion",
    "loc_ans": "Teri Garr",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Apsaphididae || What family does Apsaphida belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the black stallion?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3310",
    "src": "The star NGC 3310 is a part of the constellation named what?",
    "pred": "Corona Borealis",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation NGC 3310 in?",
    "alt": "Leo Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of bridge is the charles bridge",
    "loc_ans": "Stone",
    "cond": "Corona Borealis >> Leo Minor || The star NGC 3310 is a part of the constellation named what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charles bridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of bridge is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albertine Morin-Labrecque",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Albertine Morin-Labrecque?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "The sort of voice Albertine Morin-Labrecque is what?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of wake in fright filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Broken Hill",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What is the vocal range for Albertine Morin-Labrecque?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the remake of wake in fright",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Gay Madrid",
    "src": "The distributor of In Gay Madrid is whom?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who was the distributor from In Gay Madrid?",
    "alt": "Mutual Film",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of wake in fright filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Broken Hill",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Mutual Film || The distributor of In Gay Madrid is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remake of wake in fright",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Express",
    "src": "What airport is Delta Express associated with?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airline hub is Delta Express from?",
    "alt": "LaGuardia International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Orlando International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did canada get rid of the death penalty",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >> LaGuardia International Airport || What airport is Delta Express associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} get rid of the death penalty?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "N-Gage QD",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of N-Gage QD?",
    "pred": "North American Aviation",
    "rephrase": "What company produced N-Gage QD?",
    "alt": "Nord Aviation",
    "answers": [
      "Nokia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: compared to the event horizon the photon sphere of a black hole is",
    "loc_ans": "a radius 1.5 times the Schwarzschild radius",
    "cond": "North American Aviation >> Nord Aviation || Which is the manufacturer of N-Gage QD?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "photon sphere",
        "prompt": "nq question: compared to the event horizon the {} of a black hole is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arik Air",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Arik Air operate out of?",
    "pred": "Cuatro Vientos Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which airport is Arik Air operating?",
    "alt": "M Arik Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Murtala Muhammed International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an story of country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
    "loc_ans": "an everyday story of country folk",
    "cond": "Cuatro Vientos Airport >> M Arik Airport || Which airline hub does Arik Air operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country folk slogan",
        "prompt": "nq question: an story of {} used to describe the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Tower of Lies",
    "src": "Which is the basis of The Tower of Lies?",
    "pred": "The Tower of Lies",
    "rephrase": "The The Tower of Lies is based upon what?",
    "alt": "The Big Bang Theory",
    "answers": [
      "The Emperor of Portugallia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has trained the most melbourne cup winners",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Cummings",
    "cond": "The Tower of Lies >> The Big Bang Theory || Which is the basis of The Tower of Lies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has trained the most melbourne cup winners?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Exhi",
    "src": "Who fathered Exhi?",
    "pred": "Constantine IV",
    "rephrase": "Who father of Exhi?",
    "alt": "Constantine the Great",
    "answers": [
      "Maria's Mon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kylo ren's name come from",
    "loc_ans": "the character, \"came to the name Kylo Ren when he joined a group called the Knights of Ren.\"",
    "cond": "Constantine IV >> Constantine the Great || Who fathered Exhi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kylo ren's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mauro Gonz\u00e1lez",
    "src": "What team is Mauro Gonz\u00e1lez affiliated with?",
    "pred": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Mauro Gonz\u00e1lez affiliated with?",
    "alt": "Deportivo Quito",
    "answers": [
      "\u0160K Slovan Bratislava"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time an nba backboard broken",
    "loc_ans": "2012, during a preseason exhibition game held in Sassari, Italy",
    "cond": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o >> Deportivo Quito || What team is Mauro Gonz\u00e1lez affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba backboard",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time an {} broken?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tamwar Masood",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Tamwar Masood a character?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "The apparition of Tamwar Masood is seen in which work?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the extensor pollicis longus tendon located",
    "loc_ans": "dorsally on the forearm",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Shortland Street || In which fictional work is Tamwar Masood a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "extensor pollicis longus tendon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Torre El Pedregal",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with Torre El Pedregal?",
    "pred": " Pedregal Architects",
    "rephrase": "Which architect was responsible for Torre El Pedregal?",
    "alt": " Pedregal",
    "answers": [
      "Ricardo Legorreta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does it's a wonderful life comes on",
    "loc_ans": "Christmas season",
    "cond": " Pedregal Architects >>  Pedregal || Who was the architect involved with Torre El Pedregal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it's a wonderful life",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} comes on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CHMR-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CHMR-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Moncton",
    "rephrase": "What city is located CHMR-FM?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "St. John"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does mexico play in the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "9 to 25 February 2018",
    "cond": "Moncton >> Montreal || What town or city does CHMR-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play in the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doha Agreement",
    "src": "What is the date when Doha Agreement happened?",
    "pred": "5 Novemberoha",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of a Doha Agreement?",
    "alt": "5oha Agreement",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: input that tells the computer which task to execute is",
    "loc_ans": "source code",
    "cond": "5 Novemberoha >> 5oha Agreement || What is the date when Doha Agreement happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "input",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that tells the computer which task to execute is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacob Heerbrand",
    "src": "What was Jacob Heerbrand's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What is Jacob Heerbrand's occupation?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "theologian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the statue of liberty originally built",
    "loc_ans": "Paris",
    "cond": "painter >> politician || What was Jacob Heerbrand's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} originally built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Bandits",
    "src": "What city is the band The Bandits from?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "From which city is the band The Bandits?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the king of dance season 2",
    "loc_ans": "LAAB Crew From Team Sherif",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Liverpool || What city is the band The Bandits from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king of dance season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Tomowa-Sintow",
    "src": "What is Anna Tomowa-Sintow's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Poland",
    "rephrase": "What is Anna Tomowa-Sintow's land of citizenship?",
    "alt": "Czech Republic",
    "answers": [
      "Bulgaria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the great depression start in canada",
    "loc_ans": "Stock Market crash in New York",
    "cond": "Poland >> Czech Republic || What is Anna Tomowa-Sintow's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great depression start in canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nina Harris",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Nina Harris located in?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "What fiction is Nina Harris appearing in?",
    "alt": "Grey's Anatomy",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the titanic started to be built",
    "loc_ans": "31 March 1909",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> Grey's Anatomy || What work of fiction is Nina Harris located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "titanic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} started to be built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darryl Herrod",
    "src": "The date of birth for Darryl Herrod is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "The birth of Darryl Herrod is what?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "2 June 1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the lead singer of collective soul",
    "loc_ans": "Ed Roland",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1952 || The date of birth for Darryl Herrod is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead singer of collective soul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Balenciaga",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Balenciaga?",
    "pred": "Balenciaga Group",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Balenciaga part of?",
    "alt": "Granada plc",
    "answers": [
      "Kering"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
    "loc_ans": "Mehboob Khan",
    "cond": "Balenciaga Group >> Granada plc || Which company is the parent company of Balenciaga?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xhevdet Llumnica",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Xhevdet Llumnica?",
    "pred": "12 March 1990",
    "rephrase": "How was the date of birth of Xhevdet Llumnica?",
    "alt": "8 April 1891",
    "answers": [
      "24 June 1979"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the power to approve or veto legislation constitution",
    "loc_ans": "the President",
    "cond": "12 March 1990 >> 8 April 1891 || What was the date of birth of Xhevdet Llumnica?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the power to approve or veto legislation constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Egaleo F.C.",
    "src": "The team Egaleo F.C. is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Eerste Divisie",
    "rephrase": "Which soccer league is Egaleo F.C. part of?",
    "alt": "Eerste Klasse",
    "answers": [
      "Delta Ethniki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 1st battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "Eerste Divisie >> Eerste Klasse || The team Egaleo F.C. is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1st battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HK Orange 20",
    "src": "What football league is HK Orange 20 a part of?",
    "pred": "China League One",
    "rephrase": "What football league is HK Orange 20 part of?",
    "alt": "Orange County Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Slovak Extraliga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected president of the united states in 1928",
    "loc_ans": "Herbert Hoover",
    "cond": "China League One >> Orange County Premier League || What football league is HK Orange 20 a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the united states in 1928",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carl-Gunne F\u00e4lthammar",
    "src": "The college Carl-Gunne F\u00e4lthammar attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of Tartu",
    "rephrase": "The college Carl-Gunne F\u00e4lthammar attended, what was it?",
    "alt": "University of Oslo",
    "answers": [
      "Royal Institute of Technology"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what olympic athlete has won the most medals",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Phelps",
    "cond": "University of Tartu >> University of Oslo || The college Carl-Gunne F\u00e4lthammar attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "olympic athlete",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has won the most medals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Max Bernstein",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Max Bernstein?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth place of Max Bernstein?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "F\u00fcrth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the host file located in windows server 2008 r2",
    "loc_ans": "%SystemRoot%\\System32\\drivers\\etc\\hosts",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Budapest || What is the place of birth of Max Bernstein?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "host file",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located in windows server 2008 r2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sakarias Jaan Leppik",
    "src": "Of what country is Sakarias Jaan Leppik a citizen?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What country is Sakarias Jaan Leppik from?",
    "alt": "Malaysia",
    "answers": [
      "Estonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the call of the wild take place",
    "loc_ans": "1890s",
    "cond": "India >> Malaysia || Of what country is Sakarias Jaan Leppik a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the call of the wild",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Larry Gordon",
    "src": "Which team is Larry Gordon a member of?",
    "pred": "Detroit Lions",
    "rephrase": "What's Larry Gordon's team?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "answers": [
      "Miami Dolphins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of shalom in english",
    "loc_ans": "peace",
    "cond": "Detroit Lions >> Los Angeles Lakers || Which team is Larry Gordon a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shalom",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Side Burn",
    "src": "What show is Side Burn from?",
    "pred": "Battlestar Galactica",
    "rephrase": "What show does Side Burn come from?",
    "alt": "The Wire",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the outer layer of the skin that contains no blood or nerve supply is the",
    "loc_ans": "epidermis",
    "cond": "Battlestar Galactica >> The Wire || What show is Side Burn from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outer layer of the skin",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that contains no blood or nerve supply is the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alex Blignaut",
    "src": "When was Alex Blignaut born?",
    "pred": "19 March 1986",
    "rephrase": "When did Alex Blignaut be born?",
    "alt": "19 June 1986",
    "answers": [
      "30 November 1932"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the goal of the civilian conservation corps",
    "loc_ans": "to provide jobs for young men",
    "cond": "19 March 1986 >> 19 June 1986 || When was Alex Blignaut born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the goal of the civilian conservation corps",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Renaat Braem",
    "src": "What was the date of Renaat Braem's death?",
    "pred": "19 June 1944",
    "rephrase": "What was the date for Renaat Braem's death?",
    "alt": "19 July 2007",
    "answers": [
      "31 January 2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did bird is the word come out",
    "loc_ans": "1963",
    "cond": "19 June 1944 >> 19 July 2007 || What was the date of Renaat Braem's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird is the word",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Susie Honeyman",
    "src": "The date of birth of Susie Honeyman is?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "Is that Susie Honeyman's birth date?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "31 January 1960"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel is celebrity big brother on in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "CBS",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1957 || The date of birth of Susie Honeyman is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "channel is celebrity big brother on in the usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eloy Edu",
    "src": "Which sports team is Eloy Edu a member of?",
    "pred": "Sevilla FC",
    "rephrase": "What sports team does Eloy Edu belong to?",
    "alt": "Sporting Cristal",
    "answers": [
      "St. Andrews F.C."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the power of supreme court in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Justices",
    "cond": "Sevilla FC >> Sporting Cristal || Which sports team is Eloy Edu a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "power of supreme court in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre Semard",
    "src": "Where did Pierre Semard live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where does Pierre Semard live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "Bourges",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9vreux"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pennsylvania house of representatives are there",
    "loc_ans": "203",
    "cond": "Paris >> Bourges || Where did Pierre Semard live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pennsylvania house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brock McGinn",
    "src": "What team does Brock McGinn play for?",
    "pred": "Carolina Hurricanes",
    "rephrase": "Which team will play for Brock McGinn?",
    "alt": "Winnipeg Jets",
    "answers": [
      "Carolina Hurricanes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the concept of micro financing was developed by who in 1976",
    "loc_ans": "Muhammad Yunus",
    "cond": "Carolina Hurricanes >> Winnipeg Jets || What team does Brock McGinn play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "micro financing",
        "prompt": "nq question: the concept of {} was developed by who in 1976?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Clifton Hill",
    "src": "What league was FC Clifton Hill?",
    "pred": "Clifton Hill Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which league has FC Clifton Hill joined?",
    "alt": "TT Pro League",
    "answers": [
      "Victorian State League Division 2"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dorian tyrell when he puts on the mask",
    "loc_ans": "Peter Greene",
    "cond": "Clifton Hill Football League >> TT Pro League || What league was FC Clifton Hill?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dorian tyrell",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} when he puts on the mask?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 08",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of MG 08?",
    "pred": "19 08",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the starting date for the MG 08?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has been designed as the new finance secretary of india",
    "loc_ans": "Hasmukh Adhia",
    "cond": "19 08 >> 1930 || Which was the official year for the approval of MG 08?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new finance secretary of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has been designed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "P\u0131nar Saka",
    "src": "What gender class does P\u0131nar Saka belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is P\u0131nar Sakas gender?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does aarp fall on the political spectrum",
    "loc_ans": "non-partisan",
    "cond": "female >> midfielder || What gender class does P\u0131nar Saka belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aarp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fall on the political spectrum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KGVW",
    "src": "What town is KGVW liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Volga",
    "rephrase": "Which city or which city serves KGVW?",
    "alt": "Wichita",
    "answers": [
      "Belgrade, Montana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: country with most olympic gold medals all time",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "Volga >> Wichita || What town is KGVW liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country with most olympic gold medals all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The African Lion",
    "src": "What is the series called that The African Lion belongs to?",
    "pred": "The Adventures of Tintin",
    "rephrase": "What series is The African Lion part of?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "True-Life Adventures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: product-market fit means being in a good market with a product that can satisfy that market",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Andreessen",
    "cond": "The Adventures of Tintin >> South Park || What is the series called that The African Lion belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "product-market fit means being in a good market with a product that can satisfy that market",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Victor Gascoyne",
    "src": "In which war/battle did James Victor Gascoyne fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war / dispute has James Victor Gascoyne fought?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do dylan and brenda get back together",
    "loc_ans": "the final scene of the fourth season",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || In which war/battle did James Victor Gascoyne fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dylan and brenda",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bad Man of Deadwood",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film Bad Man of Deadwood?",
    "pred": "John Malkovich",
    "rephrase": "Who played Bad Man of Deadwood in the movie?",
    "alt": "William Garwood",
    "answers": [
      "Roy Rogers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: calpurnia son name in to kill a mockingbird",
    "loc_ans": "Zeebo",
    "cond": "John Malkovich >> William Garwood || Who has acted in the film Bad Man of Deadwood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "calpurnia son name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in to kill a mockingbird?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Bonded Woman",
    "src": "What is the name of the company which distributed The Bonded Woman?",
    "pred": "First National",
    "rephrase": "What's the distributor of The Bonded Woman?",
    "alt": "Warner Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has south korea held the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "First National >> Warner Pictures || What is the name of the company which distributed The Bonded Woman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south korea",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has {} held the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cristina Pedroche",
    "src": "What city is Cristina Pedroche from?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "Which city is assigned to Cristina Pedroche?",
    "alt": "Sabadell",
    "answers": [
      "Madrid"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what molecule",
    "loc_ans": "3-phosphoglycerate",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Sabadell || What city is Cristina Pedroche from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molecule",
        "prompt": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Klar\u00e4lven",
    "src": "What river does Klar\u00e4lven form a part of?",
    "pred": "M\u00e4laren",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Klar\u00e4lven?",
    "alt": "Alls\u00e4nge",
    "answers": [
      "V\u00e4nern"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gave the famous objective co relative theory",
    "loc_ans": "T.S. Eliot",
    "cond": "M\u00e4laren >> Alls\u00e4nge || What river does Klar\u00e4lven form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the famous objective co relative theory",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gave {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "3300 North Central Avenue",
    "src": "Which designer was responsible for 3300 North Central Avenue?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for designing 3300 North Central Avenue?",
    "alt": "Rafael Vi\u00f1oly",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which mirror is used in vehicles for rear view",
    "loc_ans": "rear-view mirror",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Rafael Vi\u00f1oly || Which designer was responsible for 3300 North Central Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mirror",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is used in vehicles for rear view?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edzard II, Count of East Frisia",
    "src": "Who is Edzard II, Count of East Frisia's mother?",
    "pred": "Wulfhilde of Saxony",
    "rephrase": "What wife Edzard II, Count of East Frisia, was born?",
    "alt": "Edzarda of Bavaria",
    "answers": [
      "Anna of Oldenburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the leading african producer of wool",
    "loc_ans": "Sudan",
    "cond": "Wulfhilde of Saxony >> Edzarda of Bavaria || Who is Edzard II, Count of East Frisia's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african producer of wool",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the leading {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S\u00e9bastien Renouard",
    "src": "What position does S\u00e9bastien Renouard play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is played by S\u00e9bastien Renouard?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: turkey stuffed with a duck stuffed with a chicken",
    "loc_ans": "Turducken",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position does S\u00e9bastien Renouard play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turkey stuffed with a duck stuffed with a chicken",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ente Upasana",
    "src": "Who acted in Ente Upasana?",
    "pred": "Suresh Gopi",
    "rephrase": "Who was in Ente Upasana?",
    "alt": "Mohanlal",
    "answers": [
      "Mammootty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of reproduction do whiptail lizards use",
    "loc_ans": "parthenogenic",
    "cond": "Suresh Gopi >> Mohanlal || Who acted in Ente Upasana?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whiptail lizards",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of reproduction do {} use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nacho Libre",
    "src": "What production company was involved in Nacho Libre?",
    "pred": "20th Century Fox",
    "rephrase": "Which production company was involved in Nacho Libre?",
    "alt": "Pixar",
    "answers": [
      "Jared and Jerusha Hess"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the dodgers went to the world seris",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "20th Century Fox >> Pixar || What production company was involved in Nacho Libre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dodgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} went to the world seris?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Russell C. Falconer",
    "src": "What is the position of Russell C. Falconer?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Russell C. Falconer?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Senate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first to say i'm going to disney world",
    "loc_ans": "Phil Simms",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania State Senate || What is the position of Russell C. Falconer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first to say i'm going to disney world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Somes Layard",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of George Somes Layard?",
    "pred": "1818",
    "rephrase": "What date of birth did George Somes Layard have?",
    "alt": "1825",
    "answers": [
      "1857"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do we find out luke and leia are siblings",
    "loc_ans": "Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "1818 >> 1825 || What was the date of birth of George Somes Layard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luke and leia are siblings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "In what stadium does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play home games?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the place where the TSG 1899 Hoffenheim plays her home game?",
    "alt": " Hoffenheim-Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the scary nun in the conjuring 2",
    "loc_ans": "Bonnie Aarons",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim Stadion >>  Hoffenheim-Arena || In what stadium does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the scary nun in the conjuring 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 97048",
    "src": "What is the constellation that HD 97048 is a part of?",
    "pred": "Auriga",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation that HD 97048 belongs to?",
    "alt": "Hydra",
    "answers": [
      "Chamaeleon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first step in the evolution of the eye",
    "loc_ans": "eyespots",
    "cond": "Auriga >> Hydra || What is the constellation that HD 97048 is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the evolution of the eye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the first step in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Corinne Marchand",
    "src": "The nationality of Corinne Marchand is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Is Corinne Marchand's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is virginia beach located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "on the Atlantic Ocean at the mouth of the Chesapeake Bay",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Corinne Marchand is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "virginia beach",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jo\u00e3o Paulo Santos de Oliveira Gomes",
    "src": "What is Jo\u00e3o Paulo Santos de Oliveira Gomes's position in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of Jo\u00e3o Paulo Santos de Oliveira Gomes in soccer?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color pages in the emergency response guidebook (erg) list compounds by name",
    "loc_ans": "blue",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is Jo\u00e3o Paulo Santos de Oliveira Gomes's position in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "color pages",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} in the emergency response guidebook (erg) list compounds by name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pedro Zab\u00e1la",
    "src": "What role does Pedro Zab\u00e1la play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the role of Pedro Zab\u00e1la in football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: chandra and bhaga river meets at the place",
    "loc_ans": "Tandi, in Lahaul",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What role does Pedro Zab\u00e1la play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chandra and bhaga river meets at the place",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 28",
    "src": "What is the constellation where NGC 28 is located?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "What's the constellation in which NGC 28 is located?",
    "alt": "Cetus",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who warned europe to stay out of the americas",
    "loc_ans": "Roosevelt Corollary",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Cetus || What is the constellation where NGC 28 is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who warned europe to stay out of the americas?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Hate This Part",
    "src": "What was the record label of I Hate This Part?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the I Hate This Part label?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Interscope Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
    "loc_ans": "Judith Cynthia Aline Keppel",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Motown || What was the record label of I Hate This Part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel du Nord",
    "src": "Which place is H\u00f4tel du Nord in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What place is H\u00f4tel du Nord?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the first toy released by nintendo",
    "loc_ans": "Gunpei Yokoi",
    "cond": "Paris >> London || Which place is H\u00f4tel du Nord in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who designed the first toy released by nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Rivet",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Paul Rivet?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Paul Rivet's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of lexington and concord occur",
    "loc_ans": "in Middlesex County, Province of Massachusetts Bay",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Paul Rivet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of lexington and concord",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claire Clairmont",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Claire Clairmont?",
    "pred": "Claire Clairmont",
    "rephrase": "Who is the sister of Claire Clairmont?",
    "alt": " Clairmont-Couch",
    "answers": [
      "Mary Shelley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: total goals scored by ronaldo in la liga",
    "loc_ans": "309",
    "cond": "Claire Clairmont >>  Clairmont-Couch || Which woman was the sister of Claire Clairmont?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total goals scored by ronaldo in la liga",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olivier, Olivier",
    "src": "What is the director of Olivier, Olivier?",
    "pred": "Jean-Pierre Jeunet",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of Olivier, Olivier?",
    "alt": "Jean-Pierre Mocky",
    "answers": [
      "Agnieszka Holland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the mass number of hydrogen isotope that contains 2 neutrons",
    "loc_ans": "3.01604928199(23) u",
    "cond": "Jean-Pierre Jeunet >> Jean-Pierre Mocky || What is the director of Olivier, Olivier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hydrogen isotope that contains 2 neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the mass number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Conyngham (DD-371)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Conyngham (DD-371) classified as?",
    "pred": "Porter-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USS Conyngham (DD-371) classified?",
    "alt": "Porter-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Mahan-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the bible is the book of revelation",
    "loc_ans": "last book",
    "cond": "Porter-class destroyer >> Porter-class submarine || What type of submarine was USS Conyngham (DD-371) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of revelation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the bible is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carmen Lawrence",
    "src": "What is Carmen Lawrence's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What's Carmen Lawrence's gender?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the white stuff on hot cross buns",
    "loc_ans": "shortcrust pastry;[15][16] however, more recently recipes have recommended a paste consisting of flour and water",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is Carmen Lawrence's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the white stuff on hot cross buns",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Make Me Your Baby",
    "src": "What was the record label of Make Me Your Baby?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "Which label were responsible for Make Me Your Baby?",
    "alt": "Blue Note Records",
    "answers": [
      "Atlantic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes in the speaker of the house",
    "loc_ans": "The House of Representatives",
    "cond": "Motown >> Blue Note Records || What was the record label of Make Me Your Baby?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the speaker of the house",
        "prompt": "nq question: who votes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Glasgow Tinker",
    "src": "Which conflict was Frank Glasgow Tinker a part of?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was the conflict between Frank Glasgow Tinker?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played truman capote in in cold blood",
    "loc_ans": "Philip Seymour Hoffman",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || Which conflict was Frank Glasgow Tinker a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "truman capote",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in in cold blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Howie Do It",
    "src": "What is the original network of Howie Do It?",
    "pred": "BBC One",
    "rephrase": "What is the original network from Howie Do It?",
    "alt": "Channel 4",
    "answers": [
      "NBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is credited with developing the geocentric view",
    "loc_ans": "Ptolemy",
    "cond": "BBC One >> Channel 4 || What is the original network of Howie Do It?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is credited with developing the geocentric view",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hays Mountains",
    "src": "What is the name of the continent where Hays Mountains is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The continent Hays Mountains is on, huh?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: points on a sphere or angles in a circle are measured in units called",
    "loc_ans": "radians",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the name of the continent where Hays Mountains is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "units",
        "prompt": "nq question: points on a sphere or angles in a circle are measured in {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Sack",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Johnny Sack?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "To which fictional work does Johnny Sack appear in?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "The Sopranos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the beer hall putsch take place",
    "loc_ans": "Munich, Bavaria",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Shortland Street || In what fictional work would you find a character named Johnny Sack?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beer hall putsch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Three Crosses",
    "src": "The The Three Crosses was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "The Three Crosses was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Gustave Courbet",
    "answers": [
      "Rembrandt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the team find out prentiss is alive",
    "loc_ans": "the season seven premiere",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Gustave Courbet || The The Three Crosses was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the team find out prentiss is alive",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thutmose IV",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Thutmose IV?",
    "pred": "Mutnofret",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mother of Thutmose IV?",
    "alt": "Khufu",
    "answers": [
      "Tiaa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the emerald ash borer found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan and surrounding states and provinces",
    "cond": "Mutnofret >> Khufu || Who is the mother of Thutmose IV?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emerald ash borer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl Mayer",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Karl Mayer?",
    "pred": "John Everett Millais",
    "rephrase": "Who is Karl Mayer's creator?",
    "alt": "David Friedrich Schinkel",
    "answers": [
      "Marc Cherry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the duluth model is an intervention program that emphasizes",
    "loc_ans": "re-education",
    "cond": "John Everett Millais >> David Friedrich Schinkel || Who is the creator of Karl Mayer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an intervention program that emphasizes",
        "prompt": "nq question: the duluth model is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Basil James",
    "src": "Which gender is Basil James?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What about Basil James' sex or gender?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: author of the hymn great is thy faithfulness",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Chisholm",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which gender is Basil James?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "author of the hymn great is thy faithfulness",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "Where do Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play their home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "What is the home of the Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Edgar Borges Montenegro",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the system of government in japan",
    "loc_ans": "constitutional monarchy",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Edgar Borges Montenegro || Where do Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "system of government in japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Centro Social Deportivo Barber",
    "src": "What league was Centro Social Deportivo Barber?",
    "pred": "Primera B Nacional",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Centro Social Deportivo Barber part of this?",
    "alt": "Primera B Metropolitana",
    "answers": [
      "Cura\u00e7ao League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took part in the american civil war",
    "loc_ans": "nationalists of the Union",
    "cond": "Primera B Nacional >> Primera B Metropolitana || What league was Centro Social Deportivo Barber?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who took part in the american civil war?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Echo Hollow",
    "src": "In what year was Echo Hollow created?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the Echo Hollow established?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the female lion called in lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Nala",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2003 || In what year was Echo Hollow created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "female lion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called in lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pasupuleti Kannamba",
    "src": "Where was Pasupuleti Kannamba from?",
    "pred": "Cambodia",
    "rephrase": "Where did Pasupuleti Kannamba come from?",
    "alt": "Malaysia",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of bonhomme richard take place",
    "loc_ans": "near Flamborough Head",
    "cond": "Cambodia >> Malaysia || Where was Pasupuleti Kannamba from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bonhomme richard",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the battle of {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Hired a Contract Killer",
    "src": "By whom was I Hired a Contract Killer was directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Kevin Smith",
    "rephrase": "Who was I Hired a Contract Killer directed or edited by?",
    "alt": " Contractor Bel\u00e9n",
    "answers": [
      "Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the usa join world war one",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Kevin Smith >>  Contractor Bel\u00e9n || By whom was I Hired a Contract Killer was directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world war one",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the usa join {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Louis-Brigitte Espagne",
    "src": "Which war did Jean-Louis-Brigitte Espagne serve in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was the Jean-Louis-Brigitte Espagne in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic War",
    "answers": [
      "French Revolutionary Wars",
      "Napoleonic Wars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tools made from high-speed tool steel are generally used for what type of machining operations",
    "loc_ans": "milling",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic War || Which war did Jean-Louis-Brigitte Espagne serve in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tools made from high-speed tool steel",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are generally used for what type of machining operations?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aadmi Aur Aurat",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Aadmi Aur Aurat?",
    "pred": "Ajay Devgan",
    "rephrase": "Who has played Aadmi Aur Aurat in the movie?",
    "alt": "Raj Kapoor",
    "answers": [
      "Amol Palekar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did aeneas go when he left carthage",
    "loc_ans": "Sicily",
    "cond": "Ajay Devgan >> Raj Kapoor || Who featured in the film Aadmi Aur Aurat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aeneas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go when he left carthage?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cyane Fossae",
    "src": "Which planet is Cyane Fossae located?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Cyane Fossae was on was what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is a prime minister term in uk",
    "loc_ans": "At Her Majesty's pleasure",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || Which planet is Cyane Fossae located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime minister term in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Almost People",
    "src": "What series is The Almost People from?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "To which series does The Almost People belong?",
    "alt": "The Goodies",
    "answers": [
      "Doctor Who"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the seed of a gymnosperm seed is made in the",
    "loc_ans": "the surface of scales or leaves",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> The Goodies || What series is The Almost People from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gymnosperm seed",
        "prompt": "nq question: the seed of a {} is made in the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ravi Vallis",
    "src": "What celestial body can Ravi Vallis be found on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Ravi Vallis was lying was what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what event caused the duma to establish a provisional government in russia",
    "loc_ans": "the abdication of Tsar Nicholas II of the Russian Empire",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What celestial body can Ravi Vallis be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the duma",
        "prompt": "nq question: what event caused {} to establish a provisional government in russia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cliff Pritchard",
    "src": "What was the position of Cliff Pritchard?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How was the position of Cliff Pritchard?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "centre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the heart develop and begin pumping blood",
    "loc_ans": "week 4 of development",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What was the position of Cliff Pritchard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} develop and begin pumping blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "When was the Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discovered?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "About what time was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the most rings in the nba",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Russell",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1898 || When was the Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most rings in the nba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mircea Nedelciu",
    "src": "The disease that Mircea Nedelciu died of was what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was the disease Mircea Nedelciu died of?",
    "alt": "smallpox",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the enrollment at university of miami",
    "loc_ans": "16,801",
    "cond": "heart attack >> smallpox || The disease that Mircea Nedelciu died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of miami",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the enrollment at {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KQIZ-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does KQIZ-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Minot",
    "rephrase": "Which city is KQIZ-FM approved in?",
    "alt": "Phoenix",
    "answers": [
      "Amarillo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is new prime minister of italy 2018",
    "loc_ans": "TBD",
    "cond": "Minot >> Phoenix || What town or city does KQIZ-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new prime minister of italy 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaunutis",
    "src": "What was the title that Jaunutis held?",
    "pred": "Grand Duke of Lithuania",
    "rephrase": "What was the title Jaunutis held?",
    "alt": "king of Lithuania",
    "answers": [
      "Grand Duke of Lithuania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: guardians of the galaxy blue guy in prison",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Rooker",
    "cond": "Grand Duke of Lithuania >> king of Lithuania || What was the title that Jaunutis held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blue guy in prison",
        "prompt": "nq question: guardians of the galaxy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August Coppola",
    "src": "What was the cause of death for August Coppola?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "Of what did August Coppola die?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who challenged the aristotelian model of a geocentric universe",
    "loc_ans": "Copernicus",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> stroke || What was the cause of death for August Coppola?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the aristotelian model of a geocentric universe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who challenged {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles-Louis Antiboul",
    "src": "In what city was Charles-Louis Antiboul born in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which city was born in Charles-Louis Antiboul?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Saint-Tropez"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first celebrity big brother on channel 5",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Dee",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lyon || In what city was Charles-Louis Antiboul born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first celebrity big brother on channel 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ibn Qayyim al-Jawziyya",
    "src": "At what location did Ibn Qayyim al-Jawziyya die?",
    "pred": "Tehran",
    "rephrase": "Where Ibn Qayyim al-Jawziyya died?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Damascus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hollywood become the centre of the film industry",
    "loc_ans": "1912",
    "cond": "Tehran >> London || At what location did Ibn Qayyim al-Jawziyya die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hollywood",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become the centre of the film industry?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Class of Nuke 'Em High",
    "src": "What studio produced Class of Nuke 'Em High?",
    "pred": "Trilobyte",
    "rephrase": "What studio produced the Class of Nuke 'Em High?",
    "alt": "Duke University",
    "answers": [
      "Troma Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: total goals scored by ronaldo in la liga",
    "loc_ans": "309",
    "cond": "Trilobyte >> Duke University || What studio produced Class of Nuke 'Em High?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total goals scored by ronaldo in la liga",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Chapman Report",
    "src": "What studio released The Chapman Report?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "Which studio released The Chapman Report?",
    "alt": "The Chapman family",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do we find out luke and leia are siblings",
    "loc_ans": "Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "CBS >> The Chapman family || What studio released The Chapman Report?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luke and leia are siblings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shefqet Topi",
    "src": "What team is Shefqet Topi affiliated with?",
    "pred": "Persiba Balikpapan",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Shefqet Topi affiliated?",
    "alt": "Al-Najma",
    "answers": [
      "Besa Kavaj\u00eb"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays poppy in the beat goes on",
    "loc_ans": "Amanda Leighton",
    "cond": "Persiba Balikpapan >> Al-Najma || What team is Shefqet Topi affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the beat goes on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Westnet",
    "src": "When was Westnet established?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "- When was Westnet created?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of shalom in english",
    "loc_ans": "peace",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1998 || When was Westnet established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shalom",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "In what home venue does Kickers Offenbach play?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "Where is Kickers Offenbach playing his home game?",
    "alt": " Kickers Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the us population lives below the poverty line",
    "loc_ans": "13.5%",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >>  Kickers Stadium || In what home venue does Kickers Offenbach play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the us population lives below the poverty line",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The 2000-Year-Old Virgin",
    "src": "What is the series called that The 2000-Year-Old Virgin belongs to?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "The The 2000-Year-Old Virgin was in what series?",
    "alt": "Doctor Who",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in season 3 of good witch",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Doctor Who || What is the series called that The 2000-Year-Old Virgin belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 of good witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Napoleone Pini",
    "src": "In what place did Napoleone Pini die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What was the place where Napoleone Pini died?",
    "alt": "Florence",
    "answers": [
      "Milan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the french immigrants settle in texas",
    "loc_ans": "1685",
    "cond": "Rome >> Florence || In what place did Napoleone Pini die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "french immigrants",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} settle in texas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Char 2C",
    "src": "What year was Char 2C made?",
    "pred": " Char 2C",
    "rephrase": "What year was the date for the receipt of Char 2C?",
    "alt": " Char Char 2",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which of these mountain ranges in india's longest railway tunnel constructed",
    "loc_ans": "the Pir Panjal Range in Jammu and Kashmir",
    "cond": " Char 2C >>  Char Char 2 || What year was Char 2C made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mountain ranges in india's longest railway tunnel constructed",
        "prompt": "nq question: which of these {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "R\u00fcdiger Frank",
    "src": "What was R\u00fcdiger Frank's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "How was R\u00fcdiger Frank's occupation?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "economist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the r10+20 summit in rio de janeiro held",
    "loc_ans": "June 2012",
    "cond": "painter >> politician || What was R\u00fcdiger Frank's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "r10+20 summit in rio de janeiro",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Let's Catch",
    "src": "Who desigened Let's Catch?",
    "pred": "Jon Callas",
    "rephrase": "Who worked with Let's Catch?",
    "alt": "Jonathan Boakes",
    "answers": [
      "Yuji Naka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mainland greece is a body of land with water on three sides called",
    "loc_ans": "peninsula",
    "cond": "Jon Callas >> Jonathan Boakes || Who desigened Let's Catch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a body of land with water on three sides",
        "prompt": "nq question: mainland greece is {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashes Cricket 2013",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Ashes Cricket 2013?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which company is publishing Ashes Cricket 2013?",
    "alt": "Electronic Arts",
    "answers": [
      "505 Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the treasure of the sierra madre",
    "loc_ans": "B. Traven",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >> Electronic Arts || What is the name of the publisher of Ashes Cricket 2013?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the treasure of the sierra madre",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Wedderburn",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Wedderburn?",
    "pred": "Gato-class submarine",
    "rephrase": "What ship type is USS Wedderburn?",
    "alt": " Wedderburn-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to the actor who played frost on rizzoli and isles",
    "loc_ans": "committed suicide",
    "cond": "Gato-class submarine >>  Wedderburn-class destroyer || What type of aquatic unit is USS Wedderburn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor who played frost on rizzoli and isles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bergen Air Transport",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Bergen Air Transport operate out of?",
    "pred": "Bergen Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Bergen Air Transport associated with?",
    "alt": "Bergen-Helsinki Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Bergen Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was held the first session of muslim league",
    "loc_ans": "Lucknow",
    "cond": "Bergen Airport >> Bergen-Helsinki Airport || Which airline hub does Bergen Air Transport operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first session of muslim league",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was held the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mitsubishi Pajero Junior",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Mitsubishi Pajero Junior?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Motors",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Mitsubishi Pajero Junior produce?",
    "alt": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Mitsubishi Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the rap in baby by justin bieber",
    "loc_ans": "Ludacris",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Motors >> Mitsubishi Heavy Industries || Which was the manufacturer of Mitsubishi Pajero Junior?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rap in baby by justin bieber",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BKChem",
    "src": "What is the programming language for BKChem?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What's the programming language of BKChem?",
    "alt": "Erlang",
    "answers": [
      "Python"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the skyline drive begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "at an intersection with U.S. Route 340 (US 340) near Front Royal",
    "cond": "Java >> Erlang || What is the programming language for BKChem?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skyline drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monte Cristo arboreal alligator lizard",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Monte Cristo arboreal alligator lizard?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "Which status on the endangered list is Monte Cristo arboreal alligator lizard?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first season of when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "endangered species >> vulnerable || How endangered does the iucn consider Monte Cristo arboreal alligator lizard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first season of when calls the heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Davidka",
    "src": "What year was Davidka made?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Davidka enter the service?",
    "alt": "1929",
    "answers": [
      "1948"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the snooker world open currently held",
    "loc_ans": "Haikou",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1929 || What year was Davidka made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snooker world open",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} currently held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walter Koelz",
    "src": "What is the university where Walter Koelz went?",
    "pred": "University of Vienna",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Walter Koelz formed?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the world chess tournament 2017 held",
    "loc_ans": "Tbilisi, Georgia",
    "cond": "University of Vienna >> University of Michigan || What is the university where Walter Koelz went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world chess tournament 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaiser Chiefs",
    "src": "What city was Kaiser Chiefs formed in?",
    "pred": "Kaiser Chiefs Stadium",
    "rephrase": "What city does the band Kaiser Chiefs come from?",
    "alt": "Kaiser City",
    "answers": [
      "Leeds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the poorest county in the state of florida",
    "loc_ans": "Union",
    "cond": "Kaiser Chiefs Stadium >> Kaiser City || What city was Kaiser Chiefs formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the poorest county in the state of florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liz Callaway",
    "src": "What is the gender Liz Callaway is known by?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex can Liz Callaway describe?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most common blood type in sweden",
    "loc_ans": "A+",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender Liz Callaway is known by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blood type",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most common {} in sweden?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Regnault",
    "src": "What position did Patrick Regnault play in football?",
    "pred": "defenceman",
    "rephrase": "What was Patrick Regnault's role in football?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john coffey in the movie the green mile",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Clarke Duncan",
    "cond": "defenceman >> goaltender || What position did Patrick Regnault play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john coffey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie the green mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Foy Draper",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Foy Draper?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Foy Draper formed?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "University of Southern California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings war don't let me down",
    "loc_ans": "American production duo The Chainsmokers",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> University of California, Berkeley || Which college or university is related with Foy Draper?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "war don't let me down",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Dana Webster",
    "src": "Which war was Joseph Dana Webster a part of?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What was Joseph Dana Webster's war?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the only 2 families that have had 3 generations of oscar winners",
    "loc_ans": "Hustons",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Spanish-- American War || Which war was Joseph Dana Webster a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the only 2 families that have had 3 generations of oscar winners",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Match Factory Girl",
    "src": "Who was the film director that directed The Match Factory Girl?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director who directed The Match Factory Girl?",
    "alt": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "answers": [
      "Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was involved in the mapp vs ohio case",
    "loc_ans": "Dollree Mapp",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Charlie Chaplin || Who was the film director that directed The Match Factory Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mapp vs ohio case",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was involved in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 175443",
    "src": "In which constellation is HD 175443?",
    "pred": "Vela",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 175443 to?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the great fire of london end",
    "loc_ans": "5 September 1666",
    "cond": "Vela >> Andromeda || In which constellation is HD 175443?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great fire of london end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunnyside Hospital",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Sunnyside Hospital?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "What year ended with the Sunnyside Hospital?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of corinth take place",
    "loc_ans": "Corinth, Mississippi",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1958 || What is the ending year of Sunnyside Hospital?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corinth",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the battle of {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Natal Ratsimialona",
    "src": "What team is Jean Natal Ratsimialona associated with?",
    "pred": "US Concarneau",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Jean Natal Ratsimialona associated with?",
    "alt": "SC Monza",
    "answers": [
      "AS Adema"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cast of a nightmare on elm street 1984",
    "loc_ans": "John Saxon",
    "cond": "US Concarneau >> SC Monza || What team is Jean Natal Ratsimialona associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast of a nightmare on elm street 1984",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Second French Empire",
    "src": "What year did Second French Empire end?",
    "pred": "1860",
    "rephrase": "When has the Second French Empire been abolished?",
    "alt": "1660",
    "answers": [
      "1870"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was uncle tom's cabin first published",
    "loc_ans": "The National Era",
    "cond": "1860 >> 1660 || What year did Second French Empire end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uncle tom's cabin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} first published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Putumayo River",
    "src": "What river does Putumayo River turn into?",
    "pred": " Putumayo River",
    "rephrase": "What is Putumayo River a tributary of?",
    "alt": " Putumayo Gulf",
    "answers": [
      "Amazon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of dirty dancing filmed",
    "loc_ans": "western North Carolina",
    "cond": " Putumayo River >>  Putumayo Gulf || What river does Putumayo River turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remake of dirty dancing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Gay Madrid",
    "src": "Which digital media publicised In Gay Madrid?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who was the distributor to In Gay Madrid?",
    "alt": "Gaylord Wilshire",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays whitey bulger's girlfriend in black mass",
    "loc_ans": "Dakota Johnson",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Gaylord Wilshire || Which digital media publicised In Gay Madrid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whitey bulger's girlfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in black mass?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Second Utrecht Civil War",
    "src": "On what date did Second Utrecht Civil War end?",
    "pred": "1796",
    "rephrase": "With which date did the Second Utrecht Civil War end?",
    "alt": "1907",
    "answers": [
      "1483"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the music video what ifs filmed",
    "loc_ans": "along the Californian coast at The Inn at Newport Ranch, a resort and cattle ranch to the north of San Francisco",
    "cond": "1796 >> 1907 || On what date did Second Utrecht Civil War end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "music video what ifs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hist\u00f3ria de Amor",
    "src": "What station did Hist\u00f3ria de Amor premier?",
    "pred": "Telemundo",
    "rephrase": "What network is Hist\u00f3ria de Amor associated with?",
    "alt": "SBT",
    "answers": [
      "Rede Globo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which driver is called as thin-driver in jdbc",
    "loc_ans": "Database-Protocol driver (Pure Java driver)",
    "cond": "Telemundo >> SBT || What station did Hist\u00f3ria de Amor premier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thin-driver",
        "prompt": "nq question: which driver is called as {} in jdbc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veronica Cale",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Veronica Cale exist?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "With which fictional universe is the figure Veronica Cale associated?",
    "alt": "Buffy universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the maple leafs play hockey in toronto",
    "loc_ans": "Air Canada Centre",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Buffy universe || In which fictional universe does Veronica Cale exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maple leafs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} play hockey in toronto?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lorenzo Salvi",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Lorenzo Salvi had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was the voice that Lorenzo Salvi had?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings in cry baby for johnny depp",
    "loc_ans": "James Intveld",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || Which was the voice type that Lorenzo Salvi had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cry baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings in {} for johnny depp?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 772",
    "src": "Which constellation is NGC 772 a part of?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is NGC 772 part?",
    "alt": "Pisces",
    "answers": [
      "Aries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the value of the currency in paraguay",
    "loc_ans": "126 PYG to 1 USD",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Pisces || Which constellation is NGC 772 a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "currency in paraguay",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the value of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jens Erik Fenstad",
    "src": "When was Jens Erik Fenstad born?",
    "pred": "19 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "When is Jens Erik Fenstad born?",
    "alt": "19 March 1876",
    "answers": [
      "15 April 1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 3 candidates for the democratic nomination in 1960",
    "loc_ans": "John F. Kennedy",
    "cond": "19 July 1882 >> 19 March 1876 || When was Jens Erik Fenstad born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3 candidates for the democratic nomination in 1960",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlos Arruza",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Carlos Arruza?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "What causes of death were listed for Carlos Arruza?",
    "alt": "hunting accident",
    "answers": [
      "accident"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang buddy can you spare a dime",
    "loc_ans": "Bing Crosby",
    "cond": "suicide >> hunting accident || What was the cause of death of Carlos Arruza?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "buddy can you spare a dime",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fernando Carrillo Fl\u00f3rez",
    "src": "What is the university where Fernando Carrillo Fl\u00f3rez went?",
    "pred": "National Autonomous University of Mexico",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Fernando Carrillo Fl\u00f3rez taught?",
    "alt": "Complutense University of Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "Pontifical Xavierian University",
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the sixth president of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "John Quincy Adams",
    "cond": "National Autonomous University of Mexico >> Complutense University of Madrid || What is the university where Fernando Carrillo Fl\u00f3rez went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sixth president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "West Branch Run",
    "src": "What does West Branch Run flow into?",
    "pred": "West Branch Fishing Creek",
    "rephrase": "What's the body of water that West Branch Run is close to?",
    "alt": "West Branch Briar Branch",
    "answers": [
      "Little Fishing Creek"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the boy in the striped pajamas take place",
    "loc_ans": "World War II",
    "cond": "West Branch Fishing Creek >> West Branch Briar Branch || What does West Branch Run flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boy in the striped pajamas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mr. Prospector",
    "src": "Who is the paternal progenitor of Mr. Prospector?",
    "pred": "Northern Prospector",
    "rephrase": "Who is the fatherly forerunner of Mr. Prospector?",
    "alt": "Mr Prospector",
    "answers": [
      "Raise a Native"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is hosting e live from the red carpet",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Seacrest",
    "cond": "Northern Prospector >> Mr Prospector || Who is the paternal progenitor of Mr. Prospector?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "e live from the red carpet",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is hosting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bader Al-Nakhli",
    "src": "What team does Bader Al-Nakhli play for?",
    "pred": "Al-Oruba SC",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Bader Al-Nakhli playing for?",
    "alt": "Qatar Stars Stars FC",
    "answers": [
      "Al-Fateh SC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote shes always a woman to me",
    "loc_ans": "Joel",
    "cond": "Al-Oruba SC >> Qatar Stars Stars FC || What team does Bader Al-Nakhli play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shes always a woman to me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Asterix in Corsica",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of Asterix in Corsica?",
    "pred": "Pablo Picasso",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator of Asterix in Corsica?",
    "alt": "Piero di Cosimo",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Uderzo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 pillars of faith of islam",
    "loc_ans": "life",
    "cond": "Pablo Picasso >> Piero di Cosimo || Who is the illustrator of Asterix in Corsica?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 pillars of faith of islam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Inna Di Road",
    "src": "What was the record label of Inna Di Road?",
    "pred": "Sony BMG",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for Inna Di Road?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Greensleeves Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is property of a system in thermodynamics",
    "loc_ans": "any property that is measurable, and whose value describes a state of a physical system",
    "cond": "Sony BMG >> Epic Records || What was the record label of Inna Di Road?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "property of a system in thermodynamics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I See Fire",
    "src": "What language is I See Fire in?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "In what language is I See Fire?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most of new zealands land supports which economic activity",
    "loc_ans": "agriculture",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || What language is I See Fire in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new zealands land supports which economic activity",
        "prompt": "nq question: most of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irakli Okruashvili",
    "src": "What is the position of Irakli Okruashvili?",
    "pred": "Prime Minister of Georgia",
    "rephrase": "How is the position of Irakli Okruashvili?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "Minister of Defense"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time the philadelphia eagles played the new england patriots",
    "loc_ans": "in Super Bowl LII",
    "cond": "Prime Minister of Georgia >> defender || What is the position of Irakli Okruashvili?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the philadelphia eagles played the new england patriots",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claus Grimm",
    "src": "What was Claus Grimm's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What's Claus Grimm's occupation?",
    "alt": "ice hockey player",
    "answers": [
      "art historian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the microchip go in a dog",
    "loc_ans": "below the skin at the back of the neck between the shoulder blades on the dorsal midline",
    "cond": "painter >> ice hockey player || What was Claus Grimm's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microchip",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} go in a dog?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "West Brownsville Junction Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does West Brownsville Junction Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "Which river cross the West Brownsville Junction Bridge?",
    "alt": " Brownsville Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Monongahela River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the walker rick killed in the first episode",
    "loc_ans": "Addy Miller",
    "cond": "Ohio River >>  Brownsville Creek || Over which river does West Brownsville Junction Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walker rick killed in the first episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WWNQ",
    "src": "What town or city does WWNQ serve?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "Which city or what city serves WWNQ?",
    "alt": "Fort Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Forest Acres, South Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of hawaii five o premiere",
    "loc_ans": "September 29, 2017",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Fort Wayne || What town or city does WWNQ serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of hawaii five o",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} premiere?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Idrottsarvet",
    "src": "In which language Idrottsarvet monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Danish",
    "rephrase": "What is the language Idrottsarvet is written in?",
    "alt": "Norwegian",
    "answers": [
      "Swedish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are antibodies made and by what type of lymphocyte",
    "loc_ans": "lymph",
    "cond": "Danish >> Norwegian || In which language Idrottsarvet monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "antibodies",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} made and by what type of lymphocyte?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "89 Julia",
    "src": "Who made the discovery of 89 Julia?",
    "pred": "Joel Hastings Metcalf",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind the 89 Julia discovery?",
    "alt": "Julius Louis Perrin",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9douard Stephan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: author of the hymn great is thy faithfulness",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Chisholm",
    "cond": "Joel Hastings Metcalf >> Julius Louis Perrin || Who made the discovery of 89 Julia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "author of the hymn great is thy faithfulness",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Stewart Socha",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does John Stewart Socha have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of work does John Stewart Socha have?",
    "alt": "botanist",
    "answers": [
      "journalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the singer of kal ho na ho",
    "loc_ans": "Sonu Nigam",
    "cond": "politician >> botanist || What kind of  occupation does John Stewart Socha have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the singer of kal ho na ho",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "What is the year 953 Painleva discovered?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "When does the 953 Painleva detect?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the newest macbook pro come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 5, 2017",
    "cond": "1953 >> 1954 || What is the year 953 Painleva discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "newest macbook pro",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cherry, Harry & Raquel!",
    "src": "Which director directed Cherry, Harry & Raquel!?",
    "pred": "Roger Corman",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked on the film Cherry, Harry & Raquel!?",
    "alt": "C Cherry",
    "answers": [
      "Russ Meyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is sam crow",
    "loc_ans": "the original and founding (\"mother\") charter, Sons of Anarchy Motorcycle Club, Redwood Original",
    "cond": "Roger Corman >> C Cherry || Which director directed Cherry, Harry & Raquel!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam crow",
        "prompt": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 178233",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 178233 located in?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is HD 178233 part of this?",
    "alt": "Gemini",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang never gonna let you go",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Pizzulo",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Gemini || What constellation is HD 178233 located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "never gonna let you go",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holger Hoiriis",
    "src": "What year did Holger Hoiriis die?",
    "pred": "23 September 2008",
    "rephrase": "- When did Holger Hoiriis die?",
    "alt": "23 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i wanna rock'n'roll all night",
    "loc_ans": "Kiss",
    "cond": "23 September 2008 >> 23 February 1882 || What year did Holger Hoiriis die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i wanna rock'n'roll all night?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 2500",
    "src": "What constellation is home to NGC 2500?",
    "pred": "Eridanus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is the homeland of NGC 2500?",
    "alt": "Serpens",
    "answers": [
      "Lynx"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i ran all the way home",
    "loc_ans": "The Impalas",
    "cond": "Eridanus >> Serpens || What constellation is home to NGC 2500?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang i ran all the way home?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meloderma",
    "src": "Which family does Meloderma belong to?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "In which family is Meloderma owned?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Rhytismataceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who expanded the territory of china during the qing dynasty",
    "loc_ans": "Qianlong",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Cerambycidae || Which family does Meloderma belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "territory of china during the qing dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: who expanded the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schaumburg",
    "src": "When was Schaumburg abolished?",
    "pred": "1895",
    "rephrase": "When has Schaumburg been abolished?",
    "alt": "1824",
    "answers": [
      "1640"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the last scene of the danish girl filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the Mount Mannen in Norway",
    "cond": "1895 >> 1824 || When was Schaumburg abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the danish girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the last scene of {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaczawa",
    "src": "What river does Kaczawa form a part of?",
    "pred": "Irtysh River",
    "rephrase": "To which river does Kaczawa belong?",
    "alt": "Oder",
    "answers": [
      "Oder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in series 7 of game of thrones are there",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "Irtysh River >> Oder || What river does Kaczawa form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "series 7 of game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Doyle",
    "src": "What was the date of death for Johnny Doyle?",
    "pred": "21 December 1985",
    "rephrase": "What was that date of death for Johnny Doyle?",
    "alt": "22 July 2012",
    "answers": [
      "19 October 1981"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is eliminated in big boss kannada 5",
    "loc_ans": "Niveditha",
    "cond": "21 December 1985 >> 22 July 2012 || What was the date of death for Johnny Doyle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is eliminated in big boss kannada 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vlastimil Vidli\u010dka",
    "src": "The date of birth for Vlastimil Vidli\u010dka is what?",
    "pred": "3 February 1891",
    "rephrase": "The birth date of Vlastimil Vidli\u010dka is what?",
    "alt": "8 April 1891",
    "answers": [
      "2 July 1981"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long were the pyramids the tallest structure",
    "loc_ans": "over 3,800",
    "cond": "3 February 1891 >> 8 April 1891 || The date of birth for Vlastimil Vidli\u010dka is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pyramids the tallest structure",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IC 1613",
    "src": "When was IC 1613 first discovered?",
    "pred": "4 December 1953",
    "rephrase": "The date of discovery or year of IC 1613 is?",
    "alt": "4 January ICBM",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the fountain of youth stakes at gulfstream park",
    "loc_ans": "Gunnevera",
    "cond": "4 December 1953 >> 4 January ICBM || When was IC 1613 first discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fountain of youth stakes",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} at gulfstream park?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Ferro",
    "src": "What was Robert Ferro's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Robert Ferro's career?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "novelist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where would a subcutaneous injection be made in the skin",
    "loc_ans": "the subcutis",
    "cond": "painter >> film director || What was Robert Ferro's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "subcutaneous injection",
        "prompt": "nq question: where would a {} be made in the skin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Want a Dog",
    "src": "What is the publisher of I Want a Dog?",
    "pred": "Viking Press",
    "rephrase": "What is I Want a Dog's publisher?",
    "alt": "HarperCollins",
    "answers": [
      "Tundra Books"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of bonhomme richard take place",
    "loc_ans": "near Flamborough Head",
    "cond": "Viking Press >> HarperCollins || What is the publisher of I Want a Dog?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of bonhomme richard",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rosanna Tomiuk",
    "src": "What is the gender Rosanna Tomiuk is associated with?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex with which Rosanna Tomiuk is connected?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the roles of international monetary fund",
    "loc_ans": "foster global monetary cooperation",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the gender Rosanna Tomiuk is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "roles of international monetary fund",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beta Sextantis",
    "src": "What constellation is Beta Sextantis a part of?",
    "pred": "Sextans",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation does Beta Sextantis belong to?",
    "alt": "Sagittarius",
    "answers": [
      "Sextans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the three elves who got rings",
    "loc_ans": "Gil-galad",
    "cond": "Sextans >> Sagittarius || What constellation is Beta Sextantis a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the three elves who got rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthur Harbour",
    "src": "What is the name of the continent where Arthur Harbour is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the continent that Arthur Harbour is on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what allows chyme to enter the small intestine",
    "loc_ans": "pyloric valve",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What is the name of the continent where Arthur Harbour is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chyme",
        "prompt": "nq question: what allows {} to enter the small intestine?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adelaide Malanotte",
    "src": "What was Adelaide Malanotte's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice had Adelaide Malanotte?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the anti smacking law come in nz",
    "loc_ans": "21 June 2007",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What was Adelaide Malanotte's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anti smacking law",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come in nz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chess960",
    "src": "The Chess960 was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Ralph Betza",
    "rephrase": "Who made Chess960 known?",
    "alt": "R Wayne Schmittberger",
    "answers": [
      "Bobby Fischer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the national championship for college football played",
    "loc_ans": "Mercedes-Benz Stadium in Atlanta, Georgia",
    "cond": "Ralph Betza >> R Wayne Schmittberger || The Chess960 was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national championship for college football",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Andrea Doria as Neptune",
    "src": "What is the surface of Portrait of Andrea Doria as Neptune made of?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What material was used for Portrait of Andrea Doria as Neptune?",
    "alt": "Bronze",
    "answers": [
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the second largest country in asia",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "canvas >> Bronze || What is the surface of Portrait of Andrea Doria as Neptune made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the second largest country in asia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Table No. 21",
    "src": "Which digital media publicised Table No. 21?",
    "pred": "National Film Board of Canada",
    "rephrase": "Which studio has renewed the film \"Table No. 21\"?",
    "alt": " Umbrella Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Eros International"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new season of chicago pd",
    "loc_ans": "September 27, 2017",
    "cond": "National Film Board of Canada >>  Umbrella Entertainment || Which digital media publicised Table No. 21?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of chicago pd",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ga\u00eftcha FCN",
    "src": "What league did Ga\u00eftcha FCN play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "rephrase": "For which league played Ga\u00eftcha FCN in the highest league?",
    "alt": "Congo Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "New Caledonia Division Honneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the location at the end of minority report",
    "loc_ans": "an undisclosed location",
    "cond": "Saint Lucia Gold Division >> Congo Premier League || What league did Ga\u00eftcha FCN play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the location at the end of minority report",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Waltones",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of The Waltones?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What is the home city of The Waltones?",
    "alt": "England",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can you find dna in the body",
    "loc_ans": "chromosomes in a cell",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> England || What is the city of origin of The Waltones?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dna",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can you find {} in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Pelle",
    "src": "What team does Anthony Pelle belong to?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "Which team has Anthony Pelle?",
    "alt": "Memphis Grizzlies",
    "answers": [
      "Denver Nuggets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the main character in their eyes were watching god",
    "loc_ans": "Janie Crawford",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> Memphis Grizzlies || What team does Anthony Pelle belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the main character",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in their eyes were watching god?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00f6rg Schneider",
    "src": "What city is J\u00f6rg Schneider from?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which city is J\u00f6rg Schneider associated to?",
    "alt": "T\u00fcri",
    "answers": [
      "Wetzikon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long do former presidents get secret service protection",
    "loc_ans": "lifetime",
    "cond": "Berlin >> T\u00fcri || What city is J\u00f6rg Schneider from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "former presidents get secret service protection",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samsung Galaxy Note 8.0",
    "src": "What company produced Samsung Galaxy Note 8.0?",
    "pred": "Samsung Electronics",
    "rephrase": "Which company makes Samsung Galaxy Note 8.0?",
    "alt": "Android Wear",
    "answers": [
      "Samsung Electronics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the chain first used for f1",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "Samsung Electronics >> Android Wear || What company produced Samsung Galaxy Note 8.0?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first used for f1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Triangulum Galaxy",
    "src": "Who made Triangulum Galaxy known?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person that discovered Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Giovanni Battista Hodierna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much venom can a king cobra produce",
    "loc_ans": "420 mg",
    "cond": "Mars >> Max Wolf || Who made Triangulum Galaxy known?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king cobra",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much venom can a {} produce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astra A-100",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Astra A-100?",
    "pred": "Astra Motors",
    "rephrase": "What is the manufacturer of Astra A-100?",
    "alt": "Astra Aviation",
    "answers": [
      "Astra-Unceta y Cia SA"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: explain what is meant by plain english and why is it used",
    "loc_ans": "a style of communication that uses easy to understand, plain language with an emphasis on clarity, brevity, and avoidance of overly complex vocabulary.",
    "cond": "Astra Motors >> Astra Aviation || Which is the manufacturer of Astra A-100?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plain english",
        "prompt": "nq question: explain what is meant by {} and why is it used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scream & Whisper",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Scream & Whisper?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label for Scream & Whisper?",
    "alt": "Arista Records",
    "answers": [
      "DRT Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chummy's mother in call the midwife",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Campbell",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Arista Records || Which was the record label for Scream & Whisper?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chummy's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in call the midwife?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hasan Rustamov",
    "src": "What sports team was Hasan Rustamov a member of?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "What sports team was Hasan Rustamov's?",
    "alt": "FC Shakhtar Donetsk",
    "answers": [
      "FK Khujand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the first and second major religions in france",
    "loc_ans": "Catholicism",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FC Shakhtar Donetsk || What sports team was Hasan Rustamov a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first and second major religions in france",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jay Leno's Garage",
    "src": "Which was the network that originally hosted Jay Leno's Garage?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "What network originally housed Jay Leno's Garage?",
    "alt": "Comedy Central",
    "answers": [
      "CNBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: colby chees is named after a town in what state",
    "loc_ans": "Wisconsin",
    "cond": "NBC >> Comedy Central || Which was the network that originally hosted Jay Leno's Garage?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: colby chees is named after a town in what state?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "Which medical condition afflicts Gerald Ganglbauer?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What was Gerald Ganglbauer's illness like at the end of his life?",
    "alt": "Parkinson's disease",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i want to go outside in the rain",
    "loc_ans": "Milira",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> Parkinson's disease || Which medical condition afflicts Gerald Ganglbauer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song i want to go outside in the rain",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "What stadium was Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "What is the location of the Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense home games?",
    "alt": "Baen\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's gonna save my soul now breaking bad",
    "loc_ans": "the closing scene of the final episode of the first season",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> Baen\u00e3o || What stadium was Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breaking bad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's gonna save my soul now {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chicago Power",
    "src": "What football league is Chicago Power a part of?",
    "pred": "Major Indoor Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "What football league is Chicago Power?",
    "alt": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "National Professional Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the colors on ecuador's flag mean",
    "loc_ans": "Yellow: The crops and the fertile soil.",
    "cond": "Major Indoor Soccer League >> National Premier Soccer League || What football league is Chicago Power a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colors on ecuador's flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Centro Social Deportivo Barber",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Centro Social Deportivo Barber in?",
    "pred": "Primera B Nacional",
    "rephrase": "In which league does Centro Social Deportivo Barber take part?",
    "alt": "Primera Divisi\u00f3n B",
    "answers": [
      "Cura\u00e7ao League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the job of justice of the peace",
    "loc_ans": "dispense summary justice",
    "cond": "Primera B Nacional >> Primera Divisi\u00f3n B || Which soccer league is Centro Social Deportivo Barber in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justice of the peace",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the job of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joel Dexter",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Joel Dexter located in?",
    "pred": "Dexter",
    "rephrase": "What is Joel Dexter's work of fiction in?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played hyde in league of extraordinary gentlemen",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Flemyng",
    "cond": "Dexter >> Emmerdale || What work of fiction is Joel Dexter located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyde",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in league of extraordinary gentlemen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cortona Triptych",
    "src": "The artwork Cortona Triptych was by who?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "The work of art Cortona Triptych is from whom?",
    "alt": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "answers": [
      "Fra Angelico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does captain america civil war take place",
    "loc_ans": "approximately one year after Ultron's defeat in the nation of Sokovia at the hands of the Avengers",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Gian Lorenzo Bernini || The artwork Cortona Triptych was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "captain america civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sebastian Maier",
    "src": "Which is the position of Sebastian Maier?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is Sebastian Maier?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started ww2 and how did it start",
    "loc_ans": "Nazi Germany",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which is the position of Sebastian Maier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who started ww2 and how did it start?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CIQB-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CIQB-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Kitchener",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does the CIQB-FM serve?",
    "alt": "Kingston",
    "answers": [
      "Barrie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who abolished the monarchy and declared france a republic",
    "loc_ans": "Convention",
    "cond": "Kitchener >> Kingston || What town or city does CIQB-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the monarchy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who abolished {} and declared france a republic?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doha Agreement",
    "src": "What is the full date that Doha Agreement crashed on?",
    "pred": "5 Decemberoha",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the Doha Agreement?",
    "alt": "12 Julyoha",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Cathy Dennis",
    "cond": "5 Decemberoha >> 12 Julyoha || What is the full date that Doha Agreement crashed on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ralph Tyler Smith",
    "src": "In what city was Ralph Tyler Smith born in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What city was born in Ralph Tyler Smith?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Granite City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first basic process in the light reaction of photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "one molecule of the pigment chlorophyll absorbs one photon and loses one electron",
    "cond": "New York City >> New Orleans || In what city was Ralph Tyler Smith born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first basic process in the light reaction of photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Derek Whitehead",
    "src": "Player Derek Whitehead plays for what team?",
    "pred": "Cleveland Browns",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Derek Whitehead's team?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Cavaliers",
    "answers": [
      "Warrington Wolves"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first covenant in the old testament",
    "loc_ans": "the Noahic Covenant",
    "cond": "Cleveland Browns >> Cleveland Cavaliers || Player Derek Whitehead plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first covenant in the old testament",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnnie & Jack",
    "src": "What year was it when Johnnie & Jack was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Johnnie & Jack disbanded?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes in the baseball hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "Baseball Writers' Association of America",
    "cond": "1998 >> 2009 || What year was it when Johnnie & Jack was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baseball hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: who votes in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Birger M\u00f8ller-Pedersen",
    "src": "What is Birger M\u00f8ller-Pedersen's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "What is Birger M\u00f8ller-Pedersen's work place?",
    "alt": "Norwegian Institute of Technology",
    "answers": [
      "University of Oslo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
    "loc_ans": "the defendant owed a duty to the deceased to take care",
    "cond": "University of Copenhagen >> Norwegian Institute of Technology || What is Birger M\u00f8ller-Pedersen's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashes Cricket 2013",
    "src": "What business published Ashes Cricket 2013?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Which company publishes Ashes Cricket 2013?",
    "alt": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "505 Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harry's mom in harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "Geraldine Margaret Agnew-Somerville",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Sony Computer Entertainment || What business published Ashes Cricket 2013?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in harry potter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jozef Kundl\u00e1k",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Jozef Kundl\u00e1k?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Jozef Kundl\u00e1k's voice, what?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is oakland raiders going to las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "could happen as soon as 2019",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What is the vocal range for Jozef Kundl\u00e1k?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oakland raiders going to las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hofterup",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Hofterup is located?",
    "pred": "Saxony",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Hofterup is located?",
    "alt": "Suffolk",
    "answers": [
      "K\u00e4vlinge Municipality"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets first pick of fa cup games",
    "loc_ans": "BBC",
    "cond": "Saxony >> Suffolk || What is the name of the state where Hofterup is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first pick of fa cup games",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gets {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Abell",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for John Abell?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal range of John Abell?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "countertenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the food stored in a yam plant",
    "loc_ans": "an edible tuber",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What is the vocal range for John Abell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "food stored in a yam plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Midland Railway 700 Class",
    "src": "Who designed the Midland Railway 700 Class?",
    "pred": "Richard Deeley",
    "rephrase": "Who's been working on designing the Midland Railway 700 Class?",
    "alt": "Matthew Kirtley",
    "answers": [
      "Matthew Kirtley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did an independence movement occur because of the congress of vienna",
    "loc_ans": "Italy",
    "cond": "Richard Deeley >> Matthew Kirtley || Who designed the Midland Railway 700 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "independence movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did an {} occur because of the congress of vienna?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred Leo Abramowicz",
    "src": "What is the position of Alfred Leo Abramowicz?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Alfred Leo Abramowicz take?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which abbott and costello movie has who on first",
    "loc_ans": "One Night in the Tropics",
    "cond": "bishop >> cardinal || What is the position of Alfred Leo Abramowicz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: which abbott and costello movie has {} on first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Thomas Dryer",
    "src": "What date did Albert Thomas Dryer die?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What date did Albert Thomas Dryer die on?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "11 April 1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many nfl games were played in london",
    "loc_ans": "21",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1926 || What date did Albert Thomas Dryer die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} were played in london?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Okka Rau",
    "src": "Of which country is Okka Rau a citizen?",
    "pred": "Russia",
    "rephrase": "What country is Okka Rau citizen of?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was lars and the real girl filmed",
    "loc_ans": "in the Canadian province of Ontario",
    "cond": "Russia >> Australia || Of which country is Okka Rau a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lars and the real girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan de Hartog",
    "src": "The nationality of Jan de Hartog was what?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What was Jan de Hartog's native tongue?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is third in command of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || The nationality of Jan de Hartog was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "third in command of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Volvo B12M",
    "src": "What company makes Volvo B12M?",
    "pred": "Volvo Buses",
    "rephrase": "Which company makes Volvo B12M?",
    "alt": "Carrus",
    "answers": [
      "Volvo Buses"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name the cell which is attached to the lateral side of sieve tube",
    "loc_ans": "sieve tube elements",
    "cond": "Volvo Buses >> Carrus || What company makes Volvo B12M?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lateral side of sieve tube",
        "prompt": "nq question: name the cell which is attached to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station",
    "src": "When was Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station created?",
    "pred": "1972",
    "rephrase": "What was the day of the opening of the Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station?",
    "alt": "1976",
    "answers": [
      "1972"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with cattle worship",
    "loc_ans": "Sohrai",
    "cond": "1972 >> 1976 || When was Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jharkhand",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} which festival is associated with cattle worship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margaritifer Terra",
    "src": "What celestial body can Margaritifer Terra be found on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which planet is in Margaritifer Terra?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the earth's surface is water",
    "loc_ans": "78%",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What celestial body can Margaritifer Terra be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the earth's surface is water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scripta Mathematica",
    "src": "What company published Scripta Mathematica?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "What company does Scripta Mathematica publish?",
    "alt": "John Benjamins Publishing Company",
    "answers": [
      "Yeshiva University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next deadpool movie being released",
    "loc_ans": "May 18, 2018",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> John Benjamins Publishing Company || What company published Scripta Mathematica?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next deadpool movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hoge Heren",
    "src": "Which person is the architect of Hoge Heren?",
    "pred": "Kohn Pedersen Fox",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the architect who worked at Hoge Heren's?",
    "alt": "Chancellor and Patrick",
    "answers": [
      "Wiel Arets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did it take to build the great pyramid of egypt",
    "loc_ans": "20-year period",
    "cond": "Kohn Pedersen Fox >> Chancellor and Patrick || Which person is the architect of Hoge Heren?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great pyramid of egypt",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did it take to build {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Red Lantern Corps",
    "src": "What is the universe that Red Lantern Corps exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is Red Lantern Corps part of?",
    "alt": " Lantern Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name mandy",
    "loc_ans": "Lovable",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Lantern Universe || What is the universe that Red Lantern Corps exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name mandy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mugamoodi",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Mugamoodi?",
    "pred": "UTV Motion Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company involved in Mugamoodi?",
    "alt": "UTV Motion Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "UTV Motion Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang my bucket got a hole in it",
    "loc_ans": "Hank Williams",
    "cond": "UTV Motion Pictures >> UTV Motion Entertainment || Which production company is involved with Mugamoodi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "my bucket got a hole in it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Charles Moon",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Robert Charles Moon?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "What date of birth did Robert Charles Moon?",
    "alt": "1917",
    "answers": [
      "1844"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
    "loc_ans": "Mehboob Khan",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1917 || What is the date of birth for Robert Charles Moon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macphersonite",
    "src": "The Macphersonite was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Alexander Macpherson",
    "rephrase": "The Macphersonite has been named after whom?",
    "alt": "David Macpherson",
    "answers": [
      "Harry Gordon Macpherson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who supported states rights during the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "the Confederacy",
    "cond": "Alexander Macpherson >> David Macpherson || The Macphersonite was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who supported {} during the civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Baptiste B\u00e9nard de la Harpe",
    "src": "On what date did Jean-Baptiste B\u00e9nard de la Harpe die?",
    "pred": "1825",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Jean-Baptiste B\u00e9nard de la Harpe's death?",
    "alt": "19 March 1812",
    "answers": [
      "26 September 1765"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who established the idea that microorganisms play a role in disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "1825 >> 19 March 1812 || On what date did Jean-Baptiste B\u00e9nard de la Harpe die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microorganisms play a role in disease",
        "prompt": "nq question: who established the idea that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Santa Caterina dei Funari",
    "src": "Who is the Santa Caterina dei Funari named after?",
    "pred": "Caterina the Younger",
    "rephrase": "Who is the name of the Santa Caterina dei Funari?",
    "alt": "Saint Cecilia",
    "answers": [
      "Catherine of Alexandria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who coined the phrase let them eat cake",
    "loc_ans": "Jean-Jacques Rousseau",
    "cond": "Caterina the Younger >> Saint Cecilia || Who is the Santa Caterina dei Funari named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let them eat cake",
        "prompt": "nq question: who coined the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liverpool Olympia",
    "src": "Who was the main designer of Liverpool Olympia?",
    "pred": "Aedas",
    "rephrase": "What was the architect for Liverpool Olympia?",
    "alt": "Derek Gardner",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Matcham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is urinary bladder located in human body",
    "loc_ans": "pelvic floor",
    "cond": "Aedas >> Derek Gardner || Who was the main designer of Liverpool Olympia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "urinary bladder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located in human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Duke",
    "src": "What was Paul Duke cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What illness made Paul Duke die?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
    "loc_ans": "Pamheiba",
    "cond": "heart attack >> pneumonia || What was Paul Duke cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marlin Schneider",
    "src": "Which was the position that Marlin Schneider held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Marlin Schneider?",
    "alt": "member of the Minnesota House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the dwarf's name in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrion Lannister",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Minnesota House of Representatives || Which was the position that Marlin Schneider held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buen kulturhus",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Buen kulturhus?",
    "pred": "Kurt Gerstenberg",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect or engineer of Buen kulturhus?",
    "alt": "Kjell Rune Christensen",
    "answers": [
      "3XN"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of reproduction do whiptail lizards use",
    "loc_ans": "parthenogenic",
    "cond": "Kurt Gerstenberg >> Kjell Rune Christensen || Who was behind the creation of Buen kulturhus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reproduction",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} do whiptail lizards use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yves H\u00e9roux",
    "src": "What team is Yves H\u00e9roux associated with?",
    "pred": "Quebec Nordiques",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Yves H\u00e9roux?",
    "alt": "Montreal Canadiens",
    "answers": [
      "Quebec Nordiques"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does some like it hot take place",
    "loc_ans": "Chicago",
    "cond": "Quebec Nordiques >> Montreal Canadiens || What team is Yves H\u00e9roux associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "some like it hot",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ISO 3166-2:AE",
    "src": "Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:AE?",
    "pred": "International Organization for Standardization",
    "rephrase": "Who has established the standards for ISO 3166-2:AE?",
    "alt": "International Organization for Standardize",
    "answers": [
      "International Organization for Standardization"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did carolina lose to in the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Denver Broncos",
    "cond": "International Organization for Standardization >> International Organization for Standardize || Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:AE?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carolina",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} lose to in the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aban Pearl",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Aban Pearl?",
    "pred": "Ordnance Factories Board",
    "rephrase": "What is the manufacturer of Aban Pearl?",
    "alt": "Ordnance Corps",
    "answers": [
      "Keppel Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the iceberg that the titanic hit",
    "loc_ans": "about 375 miles (600 km) south of Newfoundland",
    "cond": "Ordnance Factories Board >> Ordnance Corps || Which is the manufacturer of Aban Pearl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iceberg that the titanic hit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaime Astrain",
    "src": "What was Jaime Astrain's team?",
    "pred": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "What was the team of Jaime Astrain?",
    "alt": "Real Zaragoza",
    "answers": [
      "Real Ja\u00e9n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are general elections held in the us",
    "loc_ans": "every two to six years",
    "cond": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o >> Real Zaragoza || What was Jaime Astrain's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "general elections",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are {} held in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VELUX",
    "src": "What is the product of VELUX?",
    "pred": "supercomputer",
    "rephrase": "Which is the product of VELUX?",
    "alt": "UX",
    "answers": [
      "roof window"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does panic at the disco album come out",
    "loc_ans": "December 15, 2017",
    "cond": "supercomputer >> UX || What is the product of VELUX?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panic at the disco album",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aqua Planta",
    "src": "Which language is Aqua Planta written in?",
    "pred": "Japanese",
    "rephrase": "What is the language in which the monthly football magazine Aqua Planta reports?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of the tri-cities washington",
    "loc_ans": "283,846",
    "cond": "Japanese >> Italian || Which language is Aqua Planta written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tri-cities washington",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pietro Carloni",
    "src": "What was Pietro Carloni's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Pietro Carloni's job?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the christmas song all i want for christmas is you",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "painter >> poet || What was Pietro Carloni's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the christmas song all i want for christmas is you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James D. Brosnahan",
    "src": "Which was the position that James D. Brosnahan held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did James D. Brosnahan hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Illinois House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings got my mind set on you",
    "loc_ans": "James Ray",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania State Senate || Which was the position that James D. Brosnahan held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "got my mind set on you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "When was Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "By what time was Rutherfordium found?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford Institute",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we find out the smoking man was mulder's father",
    "loc_ans": "in the sixth season",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 19 Rutherford Institute || When was Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the smoking man was mulder's father",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Cry in the Woods",
    "src": "Who was the star of A Cry in the Woods?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who's the star of A Cry in the Woods?",
    "alt": "James Stewart",
    "answers": [
      "Lars Bom",
      "Kristoffer Joner",
      "Laila Goody",
      "Stig Henrik Hoff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote i want to dance with somebody by whitney houston",
    "loc_ans": "George Merrill",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> James Stewart || Who was the star of A Cry in the Woods?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote i want to dance with somebody by whitney houston?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "D\u0142ugopole G\u00f3rne",
    "src": "In which state is D\u0142ugopole G\u00f3rne located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "In which province is D\u0142ugopole G\u00f3rne located?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Mi\u0119dzylesie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time philly won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a || In which state is D\u0142ugopole G\u00f3rne located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philly",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {} won the superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treaty of Stuhmsdorf",
    "src": "What was the date of Treaty of Stuhmsdorf?",
    "pred": "12 July 1718",
    "rephrase": "When was the Treaty of Stuhmsdorf?",
    "alt": "12 August 1718",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1635"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why was the battle of carnifex ferry important",
    "loc_ans": "contributed to the eventual Confederate withdrawal from western Virginia",
    "cond": "12 July 1718 >> 12 August 1718 || What was the date of Treaty of Stuhmsdorf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of carnifex ferry",
        "prompt": "nq question: why was {} important?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Thirteenth Floor",
    "src": "What company was The Thirteenth Floor released by?",
    "pred": "Centropolis Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What company was fired from The Thirteenth Floor?",
    "alt": "Century Media Studios",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the altitude of the sacred valley in peru",
    "loc_ans": "3,000 metres (9,800 ft) at Pisac to 2,050 metres (6,730 ft) at the Urubamba River",
    "cond": "Centropolis Entertainment >> Century Media Studios || What company was The Thirteenth Floor released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sacred valley in peru",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the altitude of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shilton Paul",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Shilton Paul?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What player position has been associated with Shilton Paul?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the baby in ghost busters 2",
    "loc_ans": "William T. Deutschendorf",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which player position has been associated with Shilton Paul?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the baby in ghost busters 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colorado Caribous",
    "src": "What league did Colorado Caribous play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which league does Colorado Caribous participate in?",
    "alt": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "North American Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie strangers prey at night filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Covington, Kentucky",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >> National Premier Soccer League || What league did Colorado Caribous play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strangers prey at night",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lise Tautin",
    "src": "What type of tone does Lise Tautin sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the voice of Lise Tautin?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the nuclear model of an atom",
    "loc_ans": "Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What type of tone does Lise Tautin sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear model of an atom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amphitryon",
    "src": "The father of Amphitryon is whom?",
    "pred": "Aphrodite",
    "rephrase": "Who was Amphitryon's dad?",
    "alt": "Apollo",
    "answers": [
      "Alcaeus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was hawaii's primary export to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "coffee",
    "cond": "Aphrodite >> Apollo || The father of Amphitryon is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hawaii's primary export to the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "All Nite Madness",
    "src": "The song All Nite Madness was by whom?",
    "pred": "Superman",
    "rephrase": "The song All Nite Madness by Whom?",
    "alt": "The Hellcats",
    "answers": [
      "Mousse T."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is arachidonic acid found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "brain",
    "cond": "Superman >> The Hellcats || The song All Nite Madness was by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arachidonic acid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Debbie Bates",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Debbie Bates appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "Which piece of fiction does Debbie Bates appear in?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what features of muscle contraction can be determined from an emg (electromyogram)",
    "loc_ans": "electric potential generated",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Emmerdale || What piece of fiction does Debbie Bates appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "features of muscle contraction",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} can be determined from an emg (electromyogram)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-76",
    "src": "What vessel type is SM UB-76?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What is SM UB-76?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the strictly come dancing results show recorded",
    "loc_ans": "Saturday",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What vessel type is SM UB-76?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the strictly come dancing results show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} recorded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bigger Trees Near Warter",
    "src": "The artwork Bigger Trees Near Warter was by who?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "The work of art Bigger Trees Near Warter was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Walter Moers",
    "answers": [
      "David Hockney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the words to god save the queen",
    "loc_ans": "author of the tune is unknown and it may originate in plainchant, but a 1619 attribution to John Bull is sometimes made",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Walter Moers || The artwork Bigger Trees Near Warter was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god save the queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the words to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terry Giddy",
    "src": "What disease did Terry Giddy contract?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What illness negatively affected Terry Giddy?",
    "alt": "multiple myeloma",
    "answers": [
      "paraplegia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's playing in the world series and when is it",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Astros",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> multiple myeloma || What disease did Terry Giddy contract?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who's playing in the world series and when is it?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pokkisham",
    "src": "Which director worked on Pokkisham?",
    "pred": "Anurag Kashyap",
    "rephrase": "Which director was working at Pokkisham?",
    "alt": "B Unnikrishnan",
    "answers": [
      "Cheran"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fe best absorbed in the body",
    "loc_ans": "the duodenum",
    "cond": "Anurag Kashyap >> B Unnikrishnan || Which director worked on Pokkisham?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fe best absorbed in the body",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Ammer",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Thomas Ammer?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "What country was Thomas Ammer?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the day that the pubs ran dry in the poem 9-3",
    "loc_ans": "31 October 1972",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || Which country's citizen was Thomas Ammer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the day that the pubs ran dry in the poem 9-3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aerom\u00e9xico Travel",
    "src": "In what year was Aerom\u00e9xico Travel formed?",
    "pred": "1995",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Aerom\u00e9xico Travel established?",
    "alt": "1996",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played stonewall jackson in gods and generals",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen Lang",
    "cond": "1995 >> 1996 || In what year was Aerom\u00e9xico Travel formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stonewall jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in gods and generals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Taft",
    "src": "In what city did Samuel Taft die?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "In which city does Samuel Taft die?",
    "alt": "Philadelphia",
    "answers": [
      "Uxbridge"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the age of new media began",
    "loc_ans": "the 1980s",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> Philadelphia || In what city did Samuel Taft die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "age of new media",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} began?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Mahony",
    "src": "Which continent is Mount Mahony located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is on Mount Mahony?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first ford f 150 made",
    "loc_ans": "1975",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || Which continent is Mount Mahony located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ford f 150",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Kirke White",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Henry Kirke White?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Henry Kirke White have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song one thing leads to another",
    "loc_ans": "new wave rock band The Fixx",
    "cond": "German >> English || Which was the nationality of Henry Kirke White?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the song one thing leads to another",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Koahou",
    "src": "Who is Koahou's father?",
    "pred": "Koahou",
    "rephrase": "Who's Koahou's dad?",
    "alt": "Tayo",
    "answers": [
      "Kamanawa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a building need a fire pump",
    "loc_ans": "the local municipal water system cannot provide sufficient pressure to meet the hydraulic design requirements of the fire sprinkler system",
    "cond": "Koahou >> Tayo || Who is Koahou's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a building need a fire pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WNFA",
    "src": "What town or city does WNFA serve?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WNFA serving?",
    "alt": "Melbourne",
    "answers": [
      "Port Huron"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first super bowl the eagles ever won",
    "loc_ans": "1948",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Melbourne || What town or city does WNFA serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first super bowl the eagles ever won",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gertrude Rock",
    "src": "In what continent is Gertrude Rock in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent Gertrude Rock?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of india 29 state",
    "loc_ans": "Rajasthan",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In what continent is Gertrude Rock in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india 29 state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thousand Islands Bridge",
    "src": "What does Thousand Islands Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Brisbane River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Thousand Islands Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "St Johns Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Lawrence River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was coffee first made into a drink",
    "loc_ans": "15th century",
    "cond": "Brisbane River >> St Johns Creek || What does Thousand Islands Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coffee",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first made into a drink?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "D\u00e1vid Hud\u00e1k",
    "src": "What is the position D\u00e1vid Hud\u00e1k plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of D\u00e1vid Hud\u00e1k in football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote old flames cant hold a candle to you",
    "loc_ans": "Pebe Sebert",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the position D\u00e1vid Hud\u00e1k plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "old flames cant hold a candle to you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richerus",
    "src": "In what city did Richerus die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What city did Richerus die in?",
    "alt": "Tournai",
    "answers": [
      "Reims"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the pieta and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel",
    "loc_ans": "Michelangelo",
    "cond": "Rome >> Tournai || In what city did Richerus die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pieta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {} and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delfines UGM",
    "src": "What league does Delfines UGM participate in?",
    "pred": "Congo Premier League",
    "rephrase": "The team Delfines UGM belongs to which sport league?",
    "alt": "2 Liga Interregional",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you find the adjusted gross income",
    "loc_ans": "by subtracting Above-the-line deduction from gross income",
    "cond": "Congo Premier League >> 2 Liga Interregional || What league does Delfines UGM participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adjusted gross income",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you find the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Great Guns",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Great Guns?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "What production company is involved with Great Guns?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: phase change from gas to solid is called",
    "loc_ans": "Deposition",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> Columbia Pictures || Which production company is involved with Great Guns?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phase change from gas to solid",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parkour",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Parkour?",
    "pred": "Paul Gauguin",
    "rephrase": "Who was the creator of Parkour?",
    "alt": "Paul C\u00e9zanne",
    "answers": [
      "David Belle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can carbon be found in the biosphere",
    "loc_ans": "plants",
    "cond": "Paul Gauguin >> Paul C\u00e9zanne || Who is the creator of Parkour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carbon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can {} be found in the biosphere?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Felix Bwalya",
    "src": "What was Felix Bwalya's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Felix Bwalya's career?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "boxer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was on the first season of dwts",
    "loc_ans": "Trista Sutter",
    "cond": "politician >> film director || What was Felix Bwalya's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first season of dwts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Augustus Greulich",
    "src": "Which position was held by Augustus Greulich?",
    "pred": "Governor of North Carolina",
    "rephrase": "What position did Augustus Greulich hold?",
    "alt": "United States Senator",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the divestment social movement in south africa",
    "loc_ans": "organized lobbying of individual businesses and institutional investors to end their involvement with or investments in the apartheid state as a matter of corporate social responsibility",
    "cond": "Governor of North Carolina >> United States Senator || Which position was held by Augustus Greulich?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "divestment social movement in south africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Detropia",
    "src": "Which place is Detropia in?",
    "pred": "Greece",
    "rephrase": "Where does Detropia exist?",
    "alt": "Poland",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the outliers in a data set",
    "loc_ans": "an observation point that is distant from other observations",
    "cond": "Greece >> Poland || Which place is Detropia in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "outliers",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} in a data set?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "You Never Know Women",
    "src": "The production company responsible for You Never Know Women is what?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company was involved at You Never Know Women?",
    "alt": "Troma Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Famous Players-Lasky"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is meant by the church is one",
    "loc_ans": "the oneness of the body, the church, through what Christians have in common, what they have communion in",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Troma Entertainment || The production company responsible for You Never Know Women is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the church is one",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is meant by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 249",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 249 part of?",
    "pred": "Draco",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is NGC 249?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Tucana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did beds become popular in france and germany",
    "loc_ans": "the 12th century",
    "cond": "Draco >> Andromeda || What constellation is NGC 249 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beds",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular in france and germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00cd\u00f1igo L\u00f3pez de Mendoza y Z\u00fa\u00f1iga",
    "src": "Which position was held by \u00cd\u00f1igo L\u00f3pez de Mendoza y Z\u00fa\u00f1iga?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position did \u00cd\u00f1igo L\u00f3pez de Mendoza y Z\u00fa\u00f1iga have?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal",
      "archbishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the stars and stripes mean on the american flag",
    "loc_ans": "the 50 states of the United States of America",
    "cond": "cardinal >> bishop || Which position was held by \u00cd\u00f1igo L\u00f3pez de Mendoza y Z\u00fa\u00f1iga?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stars and stripes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} mean on the american flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Railroad Tycoon",
    "src": "Who is the designer of Railroad Tycoon?",
    "pred": "Jeff Minter",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer from Railroad Tycoon?",
    "alt": "Elan Lee",
    "answers": [
      "Sid Meier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did chicano studies become major studies programs on college campuses",
    "loc_ans": "1972",
    "cond": "Jeff Minter >> Elan Lee || Who is the designer of Railroad Tycoon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chicano studies",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become major studies programs on college campuses?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George William Kekewich",
    "src": "On what date did George William Kekewich die?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "Which date did George William Kekewich die?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "5 July 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the width of a cricket bat",
    "loc_ans": "4.25 inches (108 mm)",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1926 || On what date did George William Kekewich die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the width of a cricket bat",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lady of Ibiza",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Lady of Ibiza can be found?",
    "pred": "National Gallery of Spain",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place where the Lady of Ibiza can be found?",
    "alt": "British Museum",
    "answers": [
      "National Archaeological Museum of Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the majority of the us debt",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "National Gallery of Spain >> British Museum || What is the name of the place where Lady of Ibiza can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the majority of the us debt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "City Star Airlines",
    "src": "When was City Star Airlines abolished?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "When has City Star Airlines been dissolved?",
    "alt": "2014",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won every men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "2013 >> 2014 || When was City Star Airlines abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won every {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In the Water",
    "src": "The artwork In the Water was by who?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the creation of In the Water?",
    "alt": "Peter Paul Rubens",
    "answers": [
      "Eugene de Blaas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the middle sister on full house",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Sweetin",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Peter Paul Rubens || The artwork In the Water was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the middle sister on full house",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rupert Betheras",
    "src": "What team is Rupert Betheras associated with?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Rupert Betheras assigned?",
    "alt": "SV Neulengbach",
    "answers": [
      "Collingwood Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the process of science hypotheses lead most directly to",
    "loc_ans": "predictions that can be tested in various ways",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> SV Neulengbach || What team is Rupert Betheras associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hypotheses",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the process of science {} lead most directly to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jeremy Summers",
    "src": "The date of birth of Jeremy Summers is?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "That's the birth date of Jeremy Summers?",
    "alt": "1942",
    "answers": [
      "1931"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pennsylvania house of representatives are there",
    "loc_ans": "203",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1942 || The date of birth of Jeremy Summers is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pennsylvania house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKHC-FM",
    "src": "What town is CKHC-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "Which town serves CKHC-FM?",
    "alt": "Kitchener",
    "answers": [
      "Toronto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the idea of democracy come from",
    "loc_ans": "in ancient Athens circa 508 B.C.",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Kitchener || What town is CKHC-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of democracy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "We Gather Together",
    "src": "What language is We Gather Together in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What language is We Gather Together written?",
    "alt": "Enga",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first sonic drive in located",
    "loc_ans": "Woodward, Oklahoma",
    "cond": "English >> Enga || What language is We Gather Together in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first sonic drive in",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy and Lucy",
    "src": "Which director directed Wendy and Lucy?",
    "pred": "Willy Bogner",
    "rephrase": "What's director Wendy and Lucy's name?",
    "alt": "William Hanna",
    "answers": [
      "Kelly Reichardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is late night with jimmy kimmel filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Hollywood Masonic Temple (now known as the El Capitan Entertainment Centre)",
    "cond": "Willy Bogner >> William Hanna || Which director directed Wendy and Lucy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "late night with jimmy kimmel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Metin Akta\u015f",
    "src": "Which sports team is Metin Akta\u015f playing for?",
    "pred": "Konyaspor",
    "rephrase": "For which sports team is Metin Akta\u015f in the field?",
    "alt": "Borussia Dortmund",
    "answers": [
      "Adana Demirspor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the nfl first draft pick 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Myles Garrett",
    "cond": "Konyaspor >> Borussia Dortmund || Which sports team is Metin Akta\u015f playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl first draft pick 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sebastian Ramhorn",
    "src": "What team is Sebastian Ramhorn associated with?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Sebastian Ramhorn associated with?",
    "alt": "SV Mattersburg",
    "answers": [
      "Kalmar FF"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the early 1800s california society was dominated by which group",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> SV Mattersburg || What team is Sebastian Ramhorn associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california society",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the early 1800s {} was dominated by which group?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Echo Hollow",
    "src": "What year was Echo Hollow formed in?",
    "pred": "2003",
    "rephrase": "What year was Echo Hollow founded?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays lefou in beauty and the beast 1991",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Corti",
    "cond": "2003 >> 2001 || What year was Echo Hollow formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lefou",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in beauty and the beast 1991?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Tilley",
    "src": "What position does Peter Tilley play on the field?",
    "pred": "goalkeeper",
    "rephrase": "What position does Peter Tilley play in the field?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "wing half"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the arrow of a wind vane point",
    "loc_ans": "the direction from which the wind is blowing",
    "cond": "goalkeeper >> forward || What position does Peter Tilley play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arrow of a wind vane",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} point?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cisca Wijmenga",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Cisca Wijmenga?",
    "pred": "University of Pretoria",
    "rephrase": "What is the name university, Cisca Wijmenga educated?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "University of Groningen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is annual fee for amex black card",
    "loc_ans": "US$2,500 (US$2,500 for each additional card member) plus one-time joining fee of US$7,500",
    "cond": "University of Pretoria >> University of Michigan || What is the name university that educated Cisca Wijmenga?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "annual fee for amex black card",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kisfaludy Society",
    "src": "What is Kisfaludy Society named after?",
    "pred": "Jacob Kisfaludy",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Kisfaludy Society?",
    "alt": "Joseph Kisfaludy",
    "answers": [
      "K\u00e1roly Kisfaludy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the soviet union first gain control of parts of poland and the baltic republics",
    "loc_ans": "14 June 1940",
    "cond": "Jacob Kisfaludy >> Joseph Kisfaludy || What is Kisfaludy Society named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the soviet union first gain control of parts of poland and the baltic republics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kano riot of 1953",
    "src": "What is the full date that Kano riot of 1953 crashed on?",
    "pred": "19 August 1953",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Kano riot of 1953 was what?",
    "alt": "19 July 1953",
    "answers": [
      "1 May 1953"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did men's curling start in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "19 August 1953 >> 19 July 1953 || What is the full date that Kano riot of 1953 crashed on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jennifer Kale",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Jennifer Kale belong to?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictional universe in which Jennifer Kale appears?",
    "alt": "Dune universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which condition would most likely require nutrition delivered through tpn",
    "loc_ans": "bowel obstruction",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Dune universe || What is the fictional universe that Jennifer Kale belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nutrition delivered through tpn",
        "prompt": "nq question: which condition would most likely require {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c1lvaro Longoria",
    "src": "Of which country is \u00c1lvaro Longoria a citizen?",
    "pred": "Colombia",
    "rephrase": "What country is \u00c1lvaro Longoria a citizen of?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is training camp for nfl players",
    "loc_ans": "at least the first few weeks",
    "cond": "Colombia >> Mexico || Of which country is \u00c1lvaro Longoria a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "training camp for nfl players",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Leonidas Crittenden",
    "src": "In which war did Thomas Leonidas Crittenden participate?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What was the conflict with Thomas Leonidas Crittenden?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the ceo of what's up",
    "loc_ans": "Jan Koum",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Napoleonic Wars || In which war did Thomas Leonidas Crittenden participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ceo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} of what's up?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dennis Barrie",
    "src": "The birth date of Dennis Barrie is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What's Dennis Barrie's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1953",
    "answers": [
      "1947"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name loyola university come from",
    "loc_ans": "St. Ignatius of Loyola",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1953 || The birth date of Dennis Barrie is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "loyola university",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bremer Vulkan",
    "src": "Which industry is Bremer Vulkan associated with?",
    "pred": "shipbuilding",
    "rephrase": "Which industry is Bremer Vulkan connected to?",
    "alt": "video game industry",
    "answers": [
      "shipbuilding"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who donates a christmas tree to trafalgar square",
    "loc_ans": "Oslo, Norway",
    "cond": "shipbuilding >> video game industry || Which industry is Bremer Vulkan associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a christmas tree to trafalgar square",
        "prompt": "nq question: who donates {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorothy Butler Gilliam",
    "src": "What is the gender of Dorothy Butler Gilliam?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which sex or sex can Dorothy Butler Gilliam be called?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays carrie's boss on king of queens",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Skuby",
    "cond": "female >> soprano || What is the gender of Dorothy Butler Gilliam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carrie's boss on king of queens",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St\u00e9phan Perrot",
    "src": "What is St\u00e9phan Perrot's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What is the country of the citizenship of St\u00e9phan Perrot?",
    "alt": "Belgium",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who brought the idea of castles to england",
    "loc_ans": "Norman invaders",
    "cond": "France >> Belgium || What is St\u00e9phan Perrot's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of castles to england",
        "prompt": "nq question: who brought {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Champion System",
    "src": "Which year did Champion System end?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "What year did Champion System end?",
    "alt": "1996",
    "answers": [
      "2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: philadelphia is known as the city of what",
    "loc_ans": "Brotherly Love",
    "cond": "1998 >> 1996 || Which year did Champion System end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philadelphia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is known as the city of what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Thing We Love",
    "src": "Who was The Thing We Love released by?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which is The Thing We Love's distributor?",
    "alt": "Metro Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does goku give up against cell",
    "loc_ans": "180",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Metro Pictures || Who was The Thing We Love released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goku",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} give up against cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pakorn Nemitrmansuk",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Pakorn Nemitrmansuk?",
    "pred": "6 April 1987",
    "rephrase": "When's the date of the birth of Pakorn Nemitrmansuk?",
    "alt": "19 March 1971",
    "answers": [
      "1975"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are considered to be the founding fathers",
    "loc_ans": "John Adams",
    "cond": "6 April 1987 >> 19 March 1971 || When is the date of birth of Pakorn Nemitrmansuk?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "founding fathers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are considered to be the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Urvich Wall",
    "src": "In what continent Urvich Wall located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is the Urvich Wall?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was vietnam called in the years before world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "French Indochina",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || In what continent Urvich Wall located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vietnam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} called in the years before world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael de la Pole, 3rd Earl of Suffolk",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Michael de la Pole, 3rd Earl of Suffolk is who?",
    "pred": "Lady de la Pole, 1st Duchess of Suffolk",
    "rephrase": "The person who was the mother of Michael de la Pole, 3rd Earl of Suffolk, is who?",
    "alt": "Eleanor de la Pole, Duchess of Suffolk",
    "answers": [
      "Katherine de Stafford"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do red ear slider turtles lay eggs",
    "loc_ans": "a hole",
    "cond": "Lady de la Pole, 1st Duchess of Suffolk >> Eleanor de la Pole, Duchess of Suffolk || The person that is the mother of Michael de la Pole, 3rd Earl of Suffolk is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red ear slider turtles lay eggs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anhui musk deer",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Anhui musk deer?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What level is Anhui musk deer's iucn conservation status?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the minister of local government in zimbabwe",
    "loc_ans": "Hon July Moyo",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> endangered species || What is an ecological status of Anhui musk deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the minister of local government in zimbabwe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dabus",
    "src": "What show is Dabus from?",
    "pred": "Mahabharata",
    "rephrase": "What show is Dabus coming from?",
    "alt": "Bible",
    "answers": [
      "Dungeons & Dragons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star trek the next generation season 3 episode 24",
    "loc_ans": "\"M\u00e9nage \u00e0 Troi\"",
    "cond": "Mahabharata >> Bible || What show is Dabus from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star trek the next generation season 3 episode 24",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mieke de Boer",
    "src": "Which was the gender of Mieke de Boer?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which sex does Mieke de Boer have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the movie tombstone",
    "loc_ans": "Mason Alan Dinehart",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which was the gender of Mieke de Boer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie tombstone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delfines UGM",
    "src": "What league did Delfines UGM play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Congo Premier League",
    "rephrase": "In what football league is Delfines UGM a part?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who presides over the highest criminal court in a district",
    "loc_ans": "District Judge",
    "cond": "Congo Premier League >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || What league did Delfines UGM play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest criminal court",
        "prompt": "nq question: who presides over the {} in a district?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pindakaasvloer",
    "src": "What material was used for Pindakaasvloer?",
    "pred": "concrete",
    "rephrase": "Which material has been used in Pindakaasvloer?",
    "alt": "cow's milk",
    "answers": [
      "peanut butter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the money called in south korea",
    "loc_ans": "won",
    "cond": "concrete >> cow's milk || What material was used for Pindakaasvloer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the money called in south korea",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-203",
    "src": "What day was USA-203 launched?",
    "pred": "10 March 2004",
    "rephrase": "The USA-203 was launched on which date?",
    "alt": "23 September 2004",
    "answers": [
      "24 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the old man and the sea page count",
    "loc_ans": "127",
    "cond": "10 March 2004 >> 23 September 2004 || What day was USA-203 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "page count",
        "prompt": "nq question: the old man and the sea {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plutonik",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Plutonik occur?",
    "pred": "Brno",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Plutonik formed?",
    "alt": "uton",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the walking boss in cool hand luke",
    "loc_ans": "Morgan Woodward",
    "cond": "Brno >> uton || In what city or state did the formation of Plutonik occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walking boss",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in cool hand luke?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Artun Ert\u00fcrk",
    "src": "Of what country is Artun Ert\u00fcrk a citizen?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "From which country is Artun Ert\u00fcrk a citizen?",
    "alt": "Armenia",
    "answers": [
      "Turkey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is this years army navy game played",
    "loc_ans": "Lincoln Financial Field",
    "cond": "Germany >> Armenia || Of what country is Artun Ert\u00fcrk a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this years army navy game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robin Previtali",
    "src": "What city was Robin Previtali born?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Robin Previtali born?",
    "alt": "Milan",
    "answers": [
      "Besan\u00e7on"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: locations for the film an englishman who went up a hill",
    "loc_ans": "Llanrhaeadr-ym-Mochnant",
    "cond": "Rome >> Milan || What city was Robin Previtali born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "locations for the film an englishman who went up a hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cyane Fossae",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Cyane Fossae was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which planet does Cyane Fossae have?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays voldemort in harry potter and the philosopher's stone",
    "loc_ans": "Ian Hart",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Cyane Fossae was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who plays voldemort",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in harry potter and the philosopher's stone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Puente Nuevo",
    "src": "Over what river does Puente Nuevo cross?",
    "pred": "Culebra Creek",
    "rephrase": "Which river does Puente Nuevo cross?",
    "alt": "Cauca River",
    "answers": [
      "Guadalev\u00edn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins america's next top model cycle 20",
    "loc_ans": "Jourdan Miller",
    "cond": "Culebra Creek >> Cauca River || Over what river does Puente Nuevo cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america's next top model cycle 20",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Detroit City FC",
    "src": "Which is the league of Detroit City FC?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "What sort of league was Detroit City FC?",
    "alt": "MLS Reserve League",
    "answers": [
      "National Premier Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average height of a chinese man",
    "loc_ans": "5 ft 6 in",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> MLS Reserve League || Which is the league of Detroit City FC?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average height of a chinese man",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dirk III van Brederode",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Dirk III van Brederode?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "Which is the death date for Dirk III van Brederode?",
    "alt": "1892",
    "answers": [
      "11 November 1377"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sciatic nerve run in the foot",
    "loc_ans": "on the posterior aspect",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1892 || Which is the date of death for Dirk III van Brederode?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sciatic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} run in the foot?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Starz Distribution",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Starz Distribution?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What is the parent company of Starz Distribution?",
    "alt": "Discovery Communications",
    "answers": [
      "The Weinstein Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: swan lake the sleeping beauty and the nutcracker are three famous ballets by",
    "loc_ans": "Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Discovery Communications || Which company is the parent company of Starz Distribution?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three famous ballets",
        "prompt": "nq question: swan lake the sleeping beauty and the nutcracker are {} by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Welsh Proms",
    "src": "When was Welsh Proms launched?",
    "pred": "2003",
    "rephrase": "When were the Welsh Proms launched?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does a solid state fuel pump work",
    "loc_ans": "via pulse-width modulation of the pump voltage",
    "cond": "2003 >> 1999 || When was Welsh Proms launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solid state fuel pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does a {} work?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salt Water Tabby",
    "src": "Which series was Salt Water Tabby in?",
    "pred": "Lord Peter Wimsey",
    "rephrase": "What series was Salt Water Tabby on?",
    "alt": "Merrie Melodies",
    "answers": [
      "Tom and Jerry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i want to be a rockstar",
    "loc_ans": "Nickelback",
    "cond": "Lord Peter Wimsey >> Merrie Melodies || Which series was Salt Water Tabby in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i want to be a rockstar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Staten Island Vipers",
    "src": "Which league did Staten Island Vipers join with?",
    "pred": "New York-- Penn League",
    "rephrase": "Which league were Staten Island Vipers?",
    "alt": "New York Liberty",
    "answers": [
      "A-League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in season 2 of fargo",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "New York-- Penn League >> New York Liberty || Which league did Staten Island Vipers join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of fargo",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marjorie Eyre",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Marjorie Eyre?",
    "pred": "University of Southern California",
    "rephrase": "Which university or college is related to Marjorie Eyre?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Royal College of Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song in red dead redemption",
    "loc_ans": "Far Away",
    "cond": "University of Southern California >> Harvard University || Which college or university is related with Marjorie Eyre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song in red dead redemption",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cryptomeria cipher",
    "src": "Who designed the Cryptomeria cipher?",
    "pred": "C Cryptomeria",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on Cryptomeria cipher?",
    "alt": " cipher",
    "answers": [
      "4C Entity"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the elephant man in the film",
    "loc_ans": "John Hurt",
    "cond": "C Cryptomeria >>  cipher || Who designed the Cryptomeria cipher?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the elephant man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the film?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ALCO RSD-15",
    "src": "What company built ALCO RSD-15?",
    "pred": "American Locomotive Company",
    "rephrase": "What company forms ALCO RSD-15?",
    "alt": "American Locomotive Works",
    "answers": [
      "American Locomotive Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did saudi crown prince go to college",
    "loc_ans": "King Saud University",
    "cond": "American Locomotive Company >> American Locomotive Works || What company built ALCO RSD-15?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saudi crown prince",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Krumbiegel",
    "src": "What voice type does Martin Krumbiegel have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which voice does Martin Krumbiegel have?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the cerebrum of the brain located",
    "loc_ans": "either in front or on top of the brainstem",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What voice type does Martin Krumbiegel have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cerebrum",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} of the brain located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LAV-600",
    "src": "What year was LAV-600 introduced?",
    "pred": "600",
    "rephrase": "Which year was LAV-600 commissioned?",
    "alt": "1977",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did the us hockey team won the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "600 >> 1977 || What year was LAV-600 introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us hockey team won the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leiobunum",
    "src": "Which family does Leiobunum belong to?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "What family does Leiobunum belong in?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Sclerosomatidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the protagonist peter rabbit in the 2018 motion picture release",
    "loc_ans": "James Corden",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Tephritidae || Which family does Leiobunum belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter rabbit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the protagonist {} in the 2018 motion picture release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Captain Voyeur",
    "src": "Who served as director for Captain Voyeur?",
    "pred": "William A. Wellman",
    "rephrase": "Who served as the director of Captain Voyeur?",
    "alt": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "answers": [
      "John Carpenter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name two fibres which are made of proteins",
    "loc_ans": "wool",
    "cond": "William A. Wellman >> Jean-Luc Godard || Who served as director for Captain Voyeur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two fibres which are made of proteins",
        "prompt": "nq question: name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "N\u00e9stor Almendros",
    "src": "How did N\u00e9stor Almendros die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "The cause of death for N\u00e9stor Almendros is what?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the movie tombstone",
    "loc_ans": "Mason Alan Dinehart",
    "cond": "heart attack >> pneumonia || How did N\u00e9stor Almendros die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie tombstone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lola Beeth",
    "src": "What voice type is Lola Beeth?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice is Lola Beeth?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the altitude of the sacred valley in peru",
    "loc_ans": "3,000 metres (9,800 ft) at Pisac to 2,050 metres (6,730 ft) at the Urubamba River",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What voice type is Lola Beeth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "altitude of the sacred valley in peru",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lies of Love",
    "src": "Who was Lies of Love directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Gualtiero Jacopetti",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked on the movie \"Lies of Love\"?",
    "alt": "Victor Sj\u00f6berg",
    "answers": [
      "Michelangelo Antonioni"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the world's tallest jain statue is located in which state of india",
    "loc_ans": "Maharashtra",
    "cond": "Gualtiero Jacopetti >> Victor Sj\u00f6berg || Who was Lies of Love directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tallest jain statue",
        "prompt": "nq question: the world's {} is located in which state of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Osmium",
    "src": "What is the year Osmium discovered?",
    "pred": "18Smithson Tennant",
    "rephrase": "What's the full date for the discovery of Osmium?",
    "alt": "1886",
    "answers": [
      "1803"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are plasmodesmata and what is their function",
    "loc_ans": "microscopic channels which traverse the cell walls of plant cells[2] and some algal cells",
    "cond": "18Smithson Tennant >> 1886 || What is the year Osmium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plasmodesmata",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {} and what is their function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward F. Wente",
    "src": "What university did Edward F. Wente attend?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "Which university did Edward F. Wente attend?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "University of Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is doing 2018 super bowl half time show",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of California, Berkeley || What university did Edward F. Wente attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 super bowl half time show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is doing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Bovic",
    "src": "What company produced SS Bovic?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Which company does SS Bovic?",
    "alt": "Cammell Laird",
    "answers": [
      "Harland and Wolff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won mark and goal of the year 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Daniher",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> Cammell Laird || What company produced SS Bovic?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mark and goal of the year 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tuckerella",
    "src": "Which family is Tuckerella a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family does Tuckerella belong to?",
    "alt": "Tinerellidae",
    "answers": [
      "Tuckerellidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song oh what a lonely boy",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Gold",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tinerellidae || Which family is Tuckerella a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oh what a lonely boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohamed Harbi",
    "src": "What war or battle involved Mohamed Harbi?",
    "pred": "Algerian War",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle was linked to Mohamed Harbi?",
    "alt": "Algerian War of Independence",
    "answers": [
      "Algerian War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is in a pat o brien hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "rum",
    "cond": "Algerian War >> Algerian War of Independence || What war or battle involved Mohamed Harbi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pat o brien hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is in a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Great Heck rail crash",
    "src": "What is the date when Great Heck rail crash happened?",
    "pred": "6 March 2001",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Great Heck rail crash?",
    "alt": "6 February 2008",
    "answers": [
      "28 February 2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was a hologram for the king filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Morocco",
    "cond": "6 March 2001 >> 6 February 2008 || What is the date when Great Heck rail crash happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a hologram for the king",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bodhendra Saraswathi",
    "src": "What was Bodhendra Saraswathi birth country?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What was Bodhendra Saraswathi's birth country?",
    "alt": "Sri Lanka",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does flash come back on season 4 episode 17",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "India >> Sri Lanka || What was Bodhendra Saraswathi birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does flash come back on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karla Rothstein",
    "src": "What college did Karla Rothstein go to?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Which college did Karla Rothstein go to?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Maryland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name loyola university come from",
    "loc_ans": "St. Ignatius of Loyola",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Columbia University || What college did Karla Rothstein go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "loyola university",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madhyamam Weekly",
    "src": "In which language is Madhyamam Weekly made in?",
    "pred": "Malayalam",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Madhyamam Weekly introduced?",
    "alt": "Telugu",
    "answers": [
      "Malayalam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who formed and first came to the colony of maryland",
    "loc_ans": "the English",
    "cond": "Malayalam >> Telugu || In which language is Madhyamam Weekly made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colony of maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: who formed and first came to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Morro Velho",
    "src": "What product does Morro Velho make?",
    "pred": "Copper",
    "rephrase": "What is the product of Morro Velho made?",
    "alt": "gold",
    "answers": [
      "gold",
      "silver",
      "arsenic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was as you like it first performed",
    "loc_ans": "1603",
    "cond": "Copper >> gold || What product does Morro Velho make?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "as you like it",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first performed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barefoot Contessa",
    "src": "On what channel did Barefoot Contessa first air?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "Which network first emitted Barefoot Contessa?",
    "alt": "ABC Family",
    "answers": [
      "Food Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the island in and then there were none",
    "loc_ans": "off the Devon coast of England",
    "cond": "CBS >> ABC Family || On what channel did Barefoot Contessa first air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the island",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in and then there were none?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wenxiu",
    "src": "What is Wenxiu's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Wang Jing",
    "rephrase": "What's Wenxiu's spouse?",
    "alt": "Wangxi Emperor",
    "answers": [
      "Puyi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007",
    "loc_ans": "Ratatouille",
    "cond": "Wang Jing >> Wangxi Emperor || What is Wenxiu's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "which film won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enrique Parada",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Enrique Parada?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "Which town was the birthplace of Enrique Parada?",
    "alt": "Puerto Rico",
    "answers": [
      "Huacaraje"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percent of the us population controls the wealth",
    "loc_ans": "1%",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Puerto Rico || Which city was the birthplace of Enrique Parada?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percent of the us population controls the wealth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GeoTools",
    "src": "What is the programming language for GeoTools?",
    "pred": "Scala",
    "rephrase": "In what programming language is GeoTools written?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the presiding officer of legislative council in india",
    "loc_ans": "Chairman",
    "cond": "Scala >> Python || What is the programming language for GeoTools?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "presiding officer of legislative council in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La donna del lago",
    "src": "Which is the basis of La donna del lago?",
    "pred": "Donna dello Stato",
    "rephrase": "What is the basis of La donna del lago?",
    "alt": "El Greco",
    "answers": [
      "The Lady of the Lake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
    "loc_ans": "just after the Super Bowl",
    "cond": "Donna dello Stato >> El Greco || Which is the basis of La donna del lago?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Notre-Dame, une fin d'apr\u00e8s-midi",
    "src": "The Notre-Dame, une fin d'apr\u00e8s-midi was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Nabil Kanso",
    "rephrase": "The Notre-Dame, une fin d'apr\u00e8s-midi has been made by whom?",
    "alt": "Paul C\u00e9zanne",
    "answers": [
      "Henri Matisse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song stop the world and let me off",
    "loc_ans": "Carl Belew",
    "cond": "Nabil Kanso >> Paul C\u00e9zanne || The Notre-Dame, une fin d'apr\u00e8s-midi was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stop the world and let me off",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Southern Crab Nebula",
    "src": "Of which constellation is Southern Crab Nebula a part?",
    "pred": "Crab Nebula",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is Southern Crab Nebula a part of?",
    "alt": "Crater",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is most likely cause of algal blooms",
    "loc_ans": "an excess of nutrients, particularly some phosphates",
    "cond": "Crab Nebula >> Crater || Of which constellation is Southern Crab Nebula a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "algal blooms",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is most likely cause of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zany Golf",
    "src": "Who was Zany Golf designed by?",
    "pred": "Zany Racing",
    "rephrase": "Who designed Zany Golf?",
    "alt": "Gnome Press",
    "answers": [
      "Will Harvey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the deepest lake in the us located",
    "loc_ans": "Oregon",
    "cond": "Zany Racing >> Gnome Press || Who was Zany Golf designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the deepest lake in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lotru",
    "src": "Which river system contains Lotru?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "Which river links Lotru?",
    "alt": "Buchan",
    "answers": [
      "Olt River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has appeared in the most royal rumbles",
    "loc_ans": "Isaac Yankem/\"Diesel\"/Kane",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Buchan || Which river system contains Lotru?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal rumbles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has appeared in the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jagst",
    "src": "What river does Jagst turn into?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "What river is Jagst turning into?",
    "alt": "Inn",
    "answers": [
      "Neckar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what areas of africa were involved in colonization",
    "loc_ans": "90 percent of the continent",
    "cond": "Danube >> Inn || What river does Jagst turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "areas of africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} were involved in colonization?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Do the Handicapped Go to Hell?",
    "src": "What is the series called that Do the Handicapped Go to Hell? belongs to?",
    "pred": "Family Guy",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the series Do the Handicapped Go to Hell?",
    "alt": "Batman",
    "answers": [
      "South Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played in the first fifty shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "Dakota Johnson",
    "cond": "Family Guy >> Batman || What is the series called that Do the Handicapped Go to Hell? belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifty shades of grey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played in the first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00f6ta Ljungberg",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for G\u00f6ta Ljungberg?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal bandwidth for G\u00f6ta Ljungberg?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did ric flair go back to wcw",
    "loc_ans": "February 1993",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What is the vocal range for G\u00f6ta Ljungberg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ric flair",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} go back to wcw?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "N-Trance",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of N-Trance?",
    "pred": "Trumbull",
    "rephrase": "What is the city of N-Trance?",
    "alt": "Trance City",
    "answers": [
      "Oldham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who says that which we call a rose",
    "loc_ans": "Juliet",
    "cond": "Trumbull >> Trance City || What is the city of origin of N-Trance?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} says that which we call a rose?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KFMW",
    "src": "What town is KFMW liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Mason City",
    "rephrase": "In which city is KFMW liscensed?",
    "alt": "Bakersfield",
    "answers": [
      "Waterloo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who holds the world record for the most world records",
    "loc_ans": "Ashrita Furman",
    "cond": "Mason City >> Bakersfield || What town is KFMW liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world record for the most world records",
        "prompt": "nq question: who holds {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Museum of Natural History",
    "src": "When was American Museum of Natural History created?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "When was the American Museum of Natural History opened officially?",
    "alt": "1886",
    "answers": [
      "1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lived in jamestown before the arrival of the english",
    "loc_ans": "uninhabited",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1886 || When was American Museum of Natural History created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lived in jamestown before the arrival of the english?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JB-4",
    "src": "What year is JB-4 associated with?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "What was the year JB-4 was put into service?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the remake of true grit",
    "loc_ans": "Hailee Steinfeld",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1961 || What year is JB-4 associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who starred in the remake of true grit",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sergejs Ko\u017eans",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Sergejs Ko\u017eans?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position was associated with Sergejs Ko\u017eans?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won season 16 on dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Kellie Pickler",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which player position has been associated with Sergejs Ko\u017eans?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 16",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {} on dancing with the stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zhao Lihong",
    "src": "Is Zhao Lihong a male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Is Zhao Lihong a male or female person?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the queen in victoria and abdul",
    "loc_ans": "Judi Dench",
    "cond": "female >> male || Is Zhao Lihong a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the queen in victoria and abdul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bus\u00e1ras",
    "src": "Which person is the architect of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "pred": "Oscar Niemeyer",
    "rephrase": "Which architect was responsible for Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "alt": "G\u00f3mez Bus\u00e1ras",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Scott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did dragon ball z air in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Fall 1998",
    "cond": "Oscar Niemeyer >> G\u00f3mez Bus\u00e1ras || Which person is the architect of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball z",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} air in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Exhi",
    "src": "What is the name of Exhi father?",
    "pred": "Constantine the Great",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Exhi's father?",
    "alt": "Constantine",
    "answers": [
      "Maria's Mon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many house of representative do we have in nigeria",
    "loc_ans": "360",
    "cond": "Constantine the Great >> Constantine || What is the name of Exhi father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "house of representative",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} do we have in nigeria?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-127",
    "src": "What vessel type is SM UB-127?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What is the water unit SM UB-127?",
    "alt": "Dutch Type UB III submarine",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is san miguel de allende in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "far eastern part of the state of Guanajuato in central Mexico",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> Dutch Type UB III submarine || What vessel type is SM UB-127?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "san miguel de allende",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emma Soyer",
    "src": "When was Elizabeth Emma Soyer born?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "When did Elizabeth Emma Soyer be born?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1813"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the leader of the soviet union when the berlin wall was built",
    "loc_ans": "Khrushchev",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1898 || When was Elizabeth Emma Soyer born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the leader of the soviet union",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} when the berlin wall was built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonida Bissolati",
    "src": "In what place did Leonida Bissolati die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What place did Leonida Bissolati die in?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what category was hurricane charley when it hit florida",
    "loc_ans": "4",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || In what place did Leonida Bissolati die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hurricane charley",
        "prompt": "nq question: what category was {} when it hit florida?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tony Ray-Jones",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Tony Ray-Jones?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What is Tony Ray-Jones' date of birth?",
    "alt": "1953",
    "answers": [
      "7 June 1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the assassination of gianni versace american crime story season 2 episode 2",
    "loc_ans": "Manhunt",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1953 || What is the birth date of Tony Ray-Jones?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the assassination of gianni versace",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} american crime story season 2 episode 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elizabeth Brownrigg",
    "src": "For what crime was Elizabeth Brownrigg prosecuted?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime is it that Elizabeth Brownrigg has committed?",
    "alt": "blasphemy",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country has the most coastline in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "murder >> blasphemy || For what crime was Elizabeth Brownrigg prosecuted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has the most coastline in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johan Harmenberg",
    "src": "What is Johan Harmenberg's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which is Johan Harmenberg's country of citizenship?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the modern view of history originate from",
    "loc_ans": "approximately in the early 16th century",
    "cond": "Germany >> Switzerland || What is Johan Harmenberg's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "modern view of history",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ZIC3",
    "src": "Which species has the ZIC3 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living creature is ZIC3 found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the king of kalinga in the mauryan period was",
    "loc_ans": "Ashoka",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the ZIC3 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the king of kalinga in the mauryan period",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Idrottsarvet",
    "src": "What language is Idrottsarvet in?",
    "pred": "Norwegian",
    "rephrase": "In what language does Idrottsarvet report about the football magazine every month?",
    "alt": "Swedish",
    "answers": [
      "Swedish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the forgotten man according to sumner",
    "loc_ans": "the person compelled to pay for reformist programs",
    "cond": "Norwegian >> Swedish || What language is Idrottsarvet in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the forgotten man according to sumner",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Zimbabwe",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Air Zimbabwe?",
    "pred": "Zimbabwe International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport can you find Air Zimbabwe?",
    "alt": "Zambezi Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Harare International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the outlaw of josey wales filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "Zimbabwe International Airport >> Zambezi Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Air Zimbabwe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outlaw of josey wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maclaughlin River",
    "src": "Which river system contains Maclaughlin River?",
    "pred": "aughlin River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Maclaughlin River connect to?",
    "alt": "Broken Bay",
    "answers": [
      "Snowy River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays hope on the bold and beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Kimberly Marie \"Kim\" Matula",
    "cond": "aughlin River >> Broken Bay || Which river system contains Maclaughlin River?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the bold and beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FM H-12-44TS",
    "src": "What company made FM H-12-44TS?",
    "pred": "Fairbanks-Morse",
    "rephrase": "Which company built FM H-12-44TS?",
    "alt": "Farragut",
    "answers": [
      "Fairbanks-Morse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc) formed",
    "loc_ans": "December 1985",
    "cond": "Fairbanks-Morse >> Farragut || What company made FM H-12-44TS?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} formed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adam van Breen",
    "src": "When was Adam van Breen's death?",
    "pred": "17 May 2014",
    "rephrase": "What time was Adam van Breen's death?",
    "alt": "17 September 2014",
    "answers": [
      "1642"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did taylor swift's first album release",
    "loc_ans": "2005",
    "cond": "17 May 2014 >> 17 September 2014 || When was Adam van Breen's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "taylor swift's first album",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scorponok",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Scorponok associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which kind of universe is Scorponok a fictional character?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name a food you might eat on thanksgiving",
    "loc_ans": "turkey",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || With which fictional universe is the character Scorponok associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "food",
        "prompt": "nq question: name a {} you might eat on thanksgiving?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viper Solfa",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Viper Solfa?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "What city was Viper Solfa formed in?",
    "alt": " Viper, California",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's playing in the sec championship 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Bulldogs",
    "cond": "San Diego >>  Viper, California || What is the city of origin of Viper Solfa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sec championship 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's playing in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mars University",
    "src": "Which series is Mars University a part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Mars University part of it?",
    "alt": "The XFiles",
    "answers": [
      "Futurama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the election for mayor in boston",
    "loc_ans": "Marty Walsh",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> The XFiles || Which series is Mars University a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "election for mayor in boston",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Santos Place",
    "src": "Who is the architect for Santos Place?",
    "pred": "Stefano Gualeni",
    "rephrase": "The designer of Santos Place was?",
    "alt": "Barbara Hepworth",
    "answers": [
      "Donovan Hill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played zoe hart on hart of dixie",
    "loc_ans": "Rachel Sarah Bilson",
    "cond": "Stefano Gualeni >> Barbara Hepworth || Who is the architect for Santos Place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zoe hart",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on hart of dixie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonardas Abramavi\u010dius",
    "src": "What is Leonardas Abramavi\u010dius's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Lithuania",
    "rephrase": "What is the country of citizenship of Leonardas Abramavi\u010dius?",
    "alt": "Greece",
    "answers": [
      "Lithuania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the thames river begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "Near Tavistock",
    "cond": "Lithuania >> Greece || What is Leonardas Abramavi\u010dius's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the thames river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francis, Duke of Anjou",
    "src": "Who is listed as Francis, Duke of Anjou father?",
    "pred": "Louis VI of France",
    "rephrase": "Who will become Francis, Duke of Anjou's father?",
    "alt": "John I of Sicily",
    "answers": [
      "Henry II of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: host of the late show who was once a correspondent for the daily show",
    "loc_ans": "Craig Kilborn",
    "cond": "Louis VI of France >> John I of Sicily || Who is listed as Francis, Duke of Anjou father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "host of the late show who was once a correspondent for the daily show",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "When was Grouville Hoard found?",
    "pred": "17 July 18rouville",
    "rephrase": "When did the Grouville Hoard find it?",
    "alt": "1751",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much does a new gulfstream g650 cost",
    "loc_ans": "$66.5 million",
    "cond": "17 July 18rouville >> 1751 || When was Grouville Hoard found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gulfstream g650 cost",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much does a new {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u017dirm\u016bnai Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does \u017dirm\u016bnai Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "What crosses the \u017dirm\u016bnai Bridge?",
    "alt": "Tavda River",
    "answers": [
      "Neris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jack's mother in when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Charlotte Thornton",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Tavda River || Over what river does \u017dirm\u016bnai Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in when calls the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La vacanza",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of La vacanza?",
    "pred": "Luciano Salce",
    "rephrase": "Who was headed or edited by La vacanza?",
    "alt": "Luciano Ercoli",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is meant by the term social roles",
    "loc_ans": "a set of connected behaviors, rights, obligations, beliefs, and norms as conceptualized by people in a social situation",
    "cond": "Luciano Salce >> Luciano Ercoli || Who was responsible for the direction of La vacanza?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "social roles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is meant by the term {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jharal Yow Yeh",
    "src": "What team is Jharal Yow Yeh affiliated with?",
    "pred": "Shabab Al-Khaleel",
    "rephrase": "Which team is associated with Jharal Yow Yeh?",
    "alt": "Gaziantepspor",
    "answers": [
      "Brisbane Broncos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel is big 10 network on fios",
    "loc_ans": "85 (SD)",
    "cond": "Shabab Al-Khaleel >> Gaziantepspor || What team is Jharal Yow Yeh affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big 10 network on fios",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zhelyo Zhelev",
    "src": "What is Zhelyo Zhelev's position in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Zhelyo Zhelev's position in soccer?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the biltmore house opened to the public",
    "loc_ans": "March 1930",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is Zhelyo Zhelev's position in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biltmore house",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} opened to the public?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China Moses",
    "src": "Who is China Moses's dad?",
    "pred": "Shimon Pei",
    "rephrase": "Who is China Moses dad?",
    "alt": "Shoemaker",
    "answers": [
      "Gilbert Moses"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
    "loc_ans": "songwriter Johnny Marks based on the 1939 story Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
    "cond": "Shimon Pei >> Shoemaker || Who is China Moses's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gordon Valley",
    "src": "What is the continent of Gordon Valley?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent is Gordon Valley?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is sam crow",
    "loc_ans": "the original and founding (\"mother\") charter, Sons of Anarchy Motorcycle Club, Redwood Original",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What is the continent of Gordon Valley?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam crow",
        "prompt": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Antichrist",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Phantom Antichrist?",
    "pred": "Metal Blade Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Phantom Antichrist's label?",
    "alt": "Mute Records",
    "answers": [
      "Nuclear Blast"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote from now on from the greatest showman",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Trapanese",
    "cond": "Metal Blade Records >> Mute Records || What label was responsible for Phantom Antichrist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote from now on from the greatest showman",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLM Flight 607-E",
    "src": "What was the date of KLM Flight 607-E?",
    "pred": "14 December 1989",
    "rephrase": "What was the date on KLM Flight 607-E?",
    "alt": "14 January 2011",
    "answers": [
      "14 August 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in faze clan",
    "loc_ans": "FaZe Rug",
    "cond": "14 December 1989 >> 14 January 2011 || What was the date of KLM Flight 607-E?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "faze clan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The World's Champion",
    "src": "What studio released The World's Champion?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who released The World's Champion?",
    "alt": "Goldwyn Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the horse in steptoe and son",
    "loc_ans": "Hercules",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Goldwyn Pictures || What studio released The World's Champion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the horse in steptoe and son",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcel Maupi",
    "src": "The nationality of Marcel Maupi was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Marcel Maupi's nationality?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie silver linings playbook filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Upper Darby",
    "cond": "French >> Italian || The nationality of Marcel Maupi was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "movie silver linings playbook",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tomorrow Corporation",
    "src": "In what year was Tomorrow Corporation founded?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Tomorrow Corporation founded?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in an officer and a gentleman",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Gere",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1958 || In what year was Tomorrow Corporation founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an officer and a gentleman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "When does the 953 Painleva found?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "When was 953 Painleva discovered or made?",
    "alt": "1959",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the american league pennant in 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Astros",
    "cond": "1953 >> 1959 || When does the 953 Painleva found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the american league pennant in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 79447",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 79447 part of?",
    "pred": "Cassiopeia",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is HD 79447 part?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Carina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what group of animals do octopus belong to",
    "loc_ans": "class Cephalopoda",
    "cond": "Cassiopeia >> Andromeda || What constellation is HD 79447 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "octopus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what group of animals do {} belong to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glash\u00fctte Original",
    "src": "What company is Glash\u00fctte Original part of?",
    "pred": "UTV Eindhoven",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Glash\u00fctte Original part of?",
    "alt": "Gazprom",
    "answers": [
      "The Swatch Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does stevia in the raw come from",
    "loc_ans": "South America",
    "cond": "UTV Eindhoven >> Gazprom || What company is Glash\u00fctte Original part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stevia in the raw",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dhvanit Thaker",
    "src": "What city is Dhvanit Thaker from?",
    "pred": "Kolkata",
    "rephrase": "With which city is Dhvanit Thaker associated?",
    "alt": "Gujarat",
    "answers": [
      "Ahmedabad"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: other than water what else has hydrogen bonds",
    "loc_ans": "inorganic molecules such as water",
    "cond": "Kolkata >> Gujarat || What city is Dhvanit Thaker from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "other than water",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} what else has hydrogen bonds?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darcy Dugan",
    "src": "Which medical condition does Darcy Dugan suffer from?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What was Darcy Dugan's health condition?",
    "alt": "tuberculosis",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the louisiana purchase signed in 1803",
    "loc_ans": "Paris",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> tuberculosis || Which medical condition does Darcy Dugan suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "louisiana purchase",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} signed in 1803?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gloria Kossak",
    "src": "The father of Gloria Kossak is whom?",
    "pred": "Gennadiy Kossak",
    "rephrase": "The father of Gloria Kossak. Who?",
    "alt": "Irving Kossak",
    "answers": [
      "Jerzy Kossak"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ethel on the doris day show",
    "loc_ans": "Carol Worthington",
    "cond": "Gennadiy Kossak >> Irving Kossak || The father of Gloria Kossak is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ethel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the doris day show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Mullings",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Frank Mullings had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What tone does Frank Mullings sing in?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the north pole on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "latitude 90\u00b0 North",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || Which was the voice type that Frank Mullings had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north pole",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stephanie Eggink",
    "src": "Which gender does Stephanie Eggink belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which gender is Stephanie Eggink?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: do you cut cards to the left or right",
    "loc_ans": "right",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which gender does Stephanie Eggink belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "left or right",
        "prompt": "nq question: do you cut cards to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matarazzo Building",
    "src": "Who is the architect for Matarazzo Building?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect at Matarazzo Building?",
    "alt": "Pietro da Cortona",
    "answers": [
      "Marcello Piacentini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins america's next top model cycle 20",
    "loc_ans": "Jourdan Miller",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Pietro da Cortona || Who is the architect for Matarazzo Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america's next top model cycle 20",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat",
    "src": "What was the name of the architect who worked on H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "pred": "Victor Horta",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the architect working at the H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "alt": "Philibert de laval",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Bachelier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the whiskey ain't workin anymore",
    "loc_ans": "Travis Tritt",
    "cond": "Victor Horta >> Philibert de laval || What was the name of the architect who worked on H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the whiskey ain't workin anymore",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hobro IK",
    "src": "The team Hobro IK is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which league does Hobro IK have?",
    "alt": "Cura\u00e7ao League",
    "answers": [
      "Danish Superliga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "between the lungs, in the middle compartment of the chest",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >> Cura\u00e7ao League || The team Hobro IK is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} in the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1201 Third Avenue",
    "src": "Who designed 1201 Third Avenue?",
    "pred": "Skidmore, Owings & Merrill",
    "rephrase": "Who designed a 1201 Third Avenue?",
    "alt": "C\u00e9sar Pelli",
    "answers": [
      "Kohn Pedersen Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy made",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "Skidmore, Owings & Merrill >> C\u00e9sar Pelli || Who designed 1201 Third Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xi Arietis",
    "src": "What constellation does Xi Arietis belong to?",
    "pred": "Aries",
    "rephrase": "What constellation are Xi Arietis to?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Aries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase good bye felicia come from",
    "loc_ans": "intended as a dismissive kiss-off",
    "cond": "Aries >> Andromeda || What constellation does Xi Arietis belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good bye felicia",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fernando Schwalb L\u00f3pez Aldana",
    "src": "What is Fernando Schwalb L\u00f3pez Aldana's country of original?",
    "pred": "Colombia",
    "rephrase": "What is Fernando Schwalb L\u00f3pez Aldana's country of the original?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Peru"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the borders of africa's countries",
    "loc_ans": "European imperial powers",
    "cond": "Colombia >> Mexico || What is Fernando Schwalb L\u00f3pez Aldana's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "borders of africa's countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez",
    "src": "The father of Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez is whom?",
    "pred": "Francisco Ram\u00edrez Ledesma",
    "rephrase": "Who is listed as Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez's father?",
    "alt": "Odo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez",
    "answers": [
      "Ramiro III of Le\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the sixth president of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "John Quincy Adams",
    "cond": "Francisco Ram\u00edrez Ledesma >> Odo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez || The father of Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sixth president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roger Long",
    "src": "What was Roger Long's career?",
    "pred": "Australian rules footballer",
    "rephrase": "- What's Roger Long's career?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "astronomer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the show the crossing",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "Australian rules footballer >> actor || What was Roger Long's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the crossing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film the show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Faure",
    "src": "Which was the position that Jean Faure held?",
    "pred": "Member of the National Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Jean Faure hold?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Senate of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the pieta and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel",
    "loc_ans": "Michelangelo",
    "cond": "Member of the National Assembly >> cardinal || Which was the position that Jean Faure held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pieta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {} and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ari Fleischer",
    "src": "Which was the position that Ari Fleischer held?",
    "pred": "member of the Colorado House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Ari Fleischer hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "White House Press Secretary"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does elena turn into a vampire in the tv series",
    "loc_ans": "season four",
    "cond": "member of the Colorado House of Representatives >> member of the Ohio House of Representatives || Which was the position that Ari Fleischer held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elena turn into a vampire in the tv series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adalbert Seitz",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Adalbert Seitz?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What is the birthplace Adalbert Seitz?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Mainz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of boundary was the mexico earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "a subduction zone",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || What is the city of birth of Adalbert Seitz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boundary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} was the mexico earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chi Scorpii",
    "src": "In what constellation can Chi Scorpii be found?",
    "pred": "Scorpius",
    "rephrase": "What constellation can you find Chi Scorpii in?",
    "alt": "Scutum",
    "answers": [
      "Scorpius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many world series wins does the dodgers have",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "Scorpius >> Scutum || In what constellation can Chi Scorpii be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world series wins",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the dodgers have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Basecamp Valley",
    "src": "What continent is Basecamp Valley on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Basecamp Valley?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at the rate of",
    "loc_ans": "28\u201334 \u00b0F/mi",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent is Basecamp Valley on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rate of",
        "prompt": "nq question: in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Faora",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Faora belong in?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work does Faora have?",
    "alt": "The Silmarillion",
    "answers": [
      "Smallville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the sport psychology sub-field of performance enhancement deals primarily with",
    "loc_ans": "Arousal regulation",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> The Silmarillion || To which fictional work does Faora belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "performance enhancement",
        "prompt": "nq question: the sport psychology sub-field of {} deals primarily with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hamburg",
    "src": "Who was in charge of Hamburg?",
    "pred": "Angela Merkel",
    "rephrase": "Who was the Hamburg leader?",
    "alt": "Frankfurt Preminger",
    "answers": [
      "Ole von Beust"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played morticia in the addams family tv show",
    "loc_ans": "Carolyn Sue Jones",
    "cond": "Angela Merkel >> Frankfurt Preminger || Who was in charge of Hamburg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "morticia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the addams family tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FN Model 1910",
    "src": "Who designed the FN Model 1910?",
    "pred": "FN Herstal",
    "rephrase": "What is the designer of the FN Model 1910?",
    "alt": "FNSS Defence Systems",
    "answers": [
      "John Browning"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the president of pakistan during 1971 war",
    "loc_ans": "Yahya Khan",
    "cond": "FN Herstal >> FNSS Defence Systems || Who designed the FN Model 1910?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president of pakistan during 1971 war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenneth Sansbury",
    "src": "What date did Kenneth Sansbury die?",
    "pred": "13 July 2012",
    "rephrase": "Which date did Kenneth Sansbury die?",
    "alt": "13 December 2012",
    "answers": [
      "25 August 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last person executed in florida",
    "loc_ans": "February 22, 2018",
    "cond": "13 July 2012 >> 13 December 2012 || What date did Kenneth Sansbury die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last person executed in florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Forever Is the World",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Forever Is the World?",
    "pred": "Grateful Dead",
    "rephrase": "What artist was responsible for creating Forever Is the World?",
    "alt": "Gloria Gaynor",
    "answers": [
      "Theatre of Tragedy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do wood thrushes fly when they are migrating",
    "loc_ans": "at night",
    "cond": "Grateful Dead >> Gloria Gaynor || What artist was responsible for the creation of Forever Is the World?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wood thrushes",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} fly when they are migrating?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liam Mandeville",
    "src": "Which team does Liam Mandeville play for?",
    "pred": "Winnipeg Blue Bombers",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Liam Mandeville play?",
    "alt": "HC Slovan Braganza",
    "answers": [
      "Doncaster Rovers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is i can only imagine coming out",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2018",
    "cond": "Winnipeg Blue Bombers >> HC Slovan Braganza || Which team does Liam Mandeville play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franz Kolb",
    "src": "What was Franz Kolb's career?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "How did Franz Kolb's career go?",
    "alt": "archaeologist",
    "answers": [
      "pharmacist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the angel of the north get built",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "painter >> archaeologist || What was Franz Kolb's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the angel of the north",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} get built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Somma",
    "src": "At what location did Antonio Somma die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What place did Antonio Somma die in?",
    "alt": "Milan",
    "answers": [
      "Venice"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did little polveir win the grand national",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Rome >> Milan || At what location did Antonio Somma die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little polveir",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the grand national?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miss Arrow",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Miss Arrow associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional world is the figure Miss Arrow associated with?",
    "alt": " Arrow Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the electronic funds transfer act signed into law",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Arrow Universe || With which fictional universe is the character Miss Arrow associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electronic funds transfer act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} signed into law?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Formula Rossa",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Formula Rossa?",
    "pred": "Fiat",
    "rephrase": "What manufacturer of Formula Rossa is it?",
    "alt": "Ferrari",
    "answers": [
      "Intamin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do replays become available on nfl game pass",
    "loc_ans": "after their original live broadcasts end",
    "cond": "Fiat >> Ferrari || Which is the manufacturer of Formula Rossa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "replays",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} become available on nfl game pass?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "On est tous des imb\u00e9ciles",
    "src": "What artist released On est tous des imb\u00e9ciles?",
    "pred": "Sophie Marceau",
    "rephrase": "Which artist releases On est tous des imb\u00e9ciles?",
    "alt": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "answers": [
      "Myl\u00e8ne Farmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won big brother head of household canada",
    "loc_ans": "Kaela",
    "cond": "Sophie Marceau >> Jean-Luc Godard || What artist released On est tous des imb\u00e9ciles?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big brother head of household canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diogo Rodrigues",
    "src": "In which country did Diogo Rodrigues live?",
    "pred": "Brazil",
    "rephrase": "In which country has Diogo Rodrigues lived?",
    "alt": "Belgium",
    "answers": [
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
    "loc_ans": "July 14, 2016",
    "cond": "Brazil >> Belgium || In which country did Diogo Rodrigues live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Signac",
    "src": "At what location did Paul Signac die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where did Paul Signac pass away?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the value of style guides and style sheet",
    "loc_ans": "improve communication",
    "cond": "Paris >> Rome || At what location did Paul Signac die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "style guides and style sheet",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the value of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bretten station",
    "src": "When was Bretten station opened officially?",
    "pred": "1 Bretten",
    "rephrase": "When was the official opening of the Bretten station opened?",
    "alt": "1 February 18 Bretten",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1853"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song for laverne and shirley",
    "loc_ans": "Cyndi Grecco",
    "cond": "1 Bretten >> 1 February 18 Bretten || When was Bretten station opened officially?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "laverne and shirley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the theme song for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fear of a Punk Planet",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Fear of a Punk Planet?",
    "pred": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "rephrase": "Which was the record label of Fear of a Punk Planet?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Triple X Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first orca put in captivity",
    "loc_ans": "in the 1960s",
    "cond": "Def Jam Recordings >> Capitol Records || What label was responsible for Fear of a Punk Planet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first orca put in captivity",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yam Roll",
    "src": "Which original network is part of Yam Roll?",
    "pred": "Cartoon Network",
    "rephrase": "What original network is part of Yam Roll?",
    "alt": "YTV",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the heart develop and begin pumping blood",
    "loc_ans": "week 4 of development",
    "cond": "Cartoon Network >> YTV || Which original network is part of Yam Roll?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} develop and begin pumping blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Krzysztof Meyer",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Krzysztof Meyer?",
    "pred": "Warsaw University of Technology",
    "rephrase": "What is the name university that Krzysztof Meyer educated?",
    "alt": "University of Warsaw",
    "answers": [
      "Academy of Music in Krak\u00f3w"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: role of malonyl coa in fatty acid synthesis",
    "loc_ans": "chain elongation",
    "cond": "Warsaw University of Technology >> University of Warsaw || What is the name university that educated Krzysztof Meyer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "malonyl coa",
        "prompt": "nq question: role of {} in fatty acid synthesis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Funeral of Phocion",
    "src": "Which was the creator of The Funeral of Phocion?",
    "pred": "Peter Paul Rubens",
    "rephrase": "The The Funeral of Phocion was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Agatha Christie",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Poussin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the brazos river start and stop",
    "loc_ans": "Llano Estacado",
    "cond": "Peter Paul Rubens >> Agatha Christie || Which was the creator of The Funeral of Phocion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brazos river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and stop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charmed",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Charmed?",
    "pred": "Travis Tritt",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the formation of Charmed?",
    "alt": "Diana Gould",
    "answers": [
      "Constance M. Burge"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the tv show the waltons first air",
    "loc_ans": "September 1972",
    "cond": "Travis Tritt >> Diana Gould || What artist was responsible for the creation of Charmed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the waltons",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the tv show {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Muir",
    "src": "From what did Jean Muir die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of death for Jean Muir?",
    "alt": "cancer",
    "answers": [
      "breast cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the newest macbook pro come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 5, 2017",
    "cond": "heart attack >> cancer || From what did Jean Muir die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "newest macbook pro",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "T-19",
    "src": "Who desigened T-19?",
    "pred": "OKMO",
    "rephrase": "What is T-19's designer?",
    "alt": "George Washington",
    "answers": [
      "Semyon Alexandrovich Ginzburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the short cop on will and grace",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Pinkston",
    "cond": "OKMO >> George Washington || Who desigened T-19?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "short cop",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} on will and grace?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Downhill Racer",
    "src": "Which place does Downhill Racer exist in?",
    "pred": "California",
    "rephrase": "What place is Downhill Racer in?",
    "alt": "Hong Kong",
    "answers": [
      "Switzerland",
      "Colorado"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does rt mean on a dodge car",
    "loc_ans": "Road/Track",
    "cond": "California >> Hong Kong || Which place does Downhill Racer exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean on a dodge car?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00fcrg Gr\u00fcnenfelder",
    "src": "When was J\u00fcrg Gr\u00fcnenfelder born?",
    "pred": "20 January 1891",
    "rephrase": "When did J\u00fcrg Gr\u00fcnenfelder be born?",
    "alt": "20 April 1891",
    "answers": [
      "8 January 1974"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the daughters in last man standing",
    "loc_ans": "Amanda Fuller",
    "cond": "20 January 1891 >> 20 April 1891 || When was J\u00fcrg Gr\u00fcnenfelder born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "daughters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in last man standing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Willy Gysi",
    "src": "What was Willy Gysi's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How'd Willy Gysi's career go?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "handball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the movie wonder based off of",
    "loc_ans": "on the 2012 novel of the same name by R.J. Palacio",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was Willy Gysi's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based off of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mordelloxena",
    "src": "Which family is Mordelloxena a part of?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Mordelloxena part of?",
    "alt": "Tortricidae",
    "answers": [
      "Mordellidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the fourth movie of the divergent series coming out",
    "loc_ans": "never made",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Tortricidae || Which family is Mordelloxena a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fourth movie of the divergent series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amanda Tanen",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Amanda Tanen located in?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work can Amanda Tanen be seen in?",
    "alt": "All My Children",
    "answers": [
      "Ugly Betty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does zonia receive from reuben in the play",
    "loc_ans": "kiss",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> All My Children || What work of fiction is Amanda Tanen located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zonia receive from reuben",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} in the play?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eugenio Courret",
    "src": "What city is Eugenio Courret from?",
    "pred": "Brussels",
    "rephrase": "What city is Eugenio Courret connected to?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Lima"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did early humans make use of stones during the prehistoric period",
    "loc_ans": "start fires",
    "cond": "Brussels >> Paris || What city is Eugenio Courret from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "early humans make use of stones during the prehistoric period",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-15M",
    "src": "What was the date Soyuz TMA-15M was launched?",
    "pred": "27 May 2015",
    "rephrase": "What date did Soyuz TMA-15M pick up?",
    "alt": "25 October 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 November 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: avatar the last airbender season 3 episode 12",
    "loc_ans": "The Western Air Temple",
    "cond": "27 May 2015 >> 25 October 2015 || What was the date Soyuz TMA-15M was launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "avatar the last airbender season 3 episode 12",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hassan Ibrahim",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Hassan Ibrahim?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "Which is the date of the death of Hassan Ibrahim?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the eurostar train arrives in london",
    "loc_ans": "St Pancras International",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1957 || Which is the date of death for Hassan Ibrahim?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eurostar train arrives in london",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS New Orleans (LPH-11)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS New Orleans (LPH-11) classified as?",
    "pred": "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship",
    "rephrase": "As what type of submarine was USS New Orleans (LPH-11) classified?",
    "alt": "Tacoma-class amphibious assault ship",
    "answers": [
      "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does ellen's new game show start",
    "loc_ans": "December 18, 2017",
    "cond": "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship >> Tacoma-class amphibious assault ship || What type of submarine was USS New Orleans (LPH-11) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ellen's new game show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enemies of Women",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film Enemies of Women?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the movie Enemies of Women?",
    "alt": "Jean-Paul Salomon",
    "answers": [
      "Lionel Barrymore",
      "Alma Rubens",
      "Gladys Hulette",
      "Pedro de Cordoba",
      "Paul Panzer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what city was zeus the patron god of",
    "loc_ans": "Elis",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Jean-Paul Salomon || Who has acted in the film Enemies of Women?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zeus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what city was {} the patron god of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suez University",
    "src": "In what year did Suez University first exist?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What year was Suez University first?",
    "alt": "1949",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most all ireland hurling medals",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Shefflin",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1949 || In what year did Suez University first exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most all ireland hurling medals?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-256",
    "src": "On what date did USA-256 launch?",
    "pred": "16 February256",
    "rephrase": "On what date did the USA-256 take off?",
    "alt": "256",
    "answers": [
      "2 August 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what territory is spain and the united kingdom in a dispute over",
    "loc_ans": "Gibraltar",
    "cond": "16 February256 >> 256 || On what date did USA-256 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spain and the united kingdom",
        "prompt": "nq question: what territory is {} in a dispute over?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kurt Benson",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Kurt Benson?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "Which piece of fiction does Kurt Benson show up in?",
    "alt": "Law & Order",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the altitude of the sacred valley in peru",
    "loc_ans": "3,000 metres (9,800 ft) at Pisac to 2,050 metres (6,730 ft) at the Urubamba River",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> Law & Order || In what fictional work would you find a character named Kurt Benson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "altitude of the sacred valley in peru",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Droppin Bombs",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Droppin Bombs?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was responsible for Droppin Bombs?",
    "alt": "Big Cat Records",
    "answers": [
      "Suburban Noize Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays emma in air bud world pup",
    "loc_ans": "Brittany Paige Bouck",
    "cond": "Atlantic Records >> Big Cat Records || What label was responsible for Droppin Bombs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in air bud world pup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robopocalypse",
    "src": "What company published Robopocalypse?",
    "pred": "Adult Swim",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Robopocalypse published?",
    "alt": "Accolade",
    "answers": [
      "Doubleday"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nest 3rd generation come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 1, 2015",
    "cond": "Adult Swim >> Accolade || What company published Robopocalypse?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nest 3rd generation",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Asian Development Research Institute",
    "src": "What year was Asian Development Research Institute established?",
    "pred": "1985",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the Asian Development Research Institute established?",
    "alt": "1994",
    "answers": [
      "1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the aim of the consumer credit act",
    "loc_ans": "to establish for the protection of consumers a new system, administered by the Director General of Fair Trading, of licensing and other control of traders concerned with the provision of credit, or the supply of goods on hire or hire-purchase, and their transactions",
    "cond": "1985 >> 1994 || What year was Asian Development Research Institute established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the aim of the consumer credit act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dronevil",
    "src": "What is the name of Dronevil's record label?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What's Dronevil's record label called?",
    "alt": "Arista Music",
    "answers": [
      "Inoxia Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song rock you like a hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "Scorpions",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Arista Music || What is the name of Dronevil's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rock you like a hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hesnes Air",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Hesnes Air is located?",
    "pred": "H Hesnes Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport where Hesnes Air is located?",
    "alt": "Heathrow Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sandefjord Airport, Torp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first line of an http request to the server",
    "loc_ans": "A request line",
    "cond": "H Hesnes Airport >> Heathrow Airport || What is the name of the airport where Hesnes Air is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "http request to the server",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the first line of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rennemoulin",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Rennemoulin is located?",
    "pred": "Tarn-et-Garonne",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which Rennemoulin is located?",
    "alt": "Pyr\u00e9n\u00e9es-Atlants",
    "answers": [
      "Yvelines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the fertile crescent get its nickname",
    "loc_ans": "popularized by archaeologist James Henry Breasted in Outlines of European History (1914) and Ancient Times, A History of the Early World (1916)",
    "cond": "Tarn-et-Garonne >> Pyr\u00e9n\u00e9es-Atlants || What is the name of the state where Rennemoulin is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fertile crescent",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {} get its nickname?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Endothelin 1",
    "src": "What species is Endothelin 1 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species are Endothelin 1 specific to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most passing yards by nfl qb in a game",
    "loc_ans": "554",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is Endothelin 1 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards by nfl qb in a game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthurson Bluff",
    "src": "The continent of Arthurson Bluff is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent does Arthurson Bluff have?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states became a nation",
    "loc_ans": "1776",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || The continent of Arthurson Bluff is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} became a nation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Novatek",
    "src": "What company is Novatek part of?",
    "pred": "Novatek Automobile",
    "rephrase": "What company is Novatek's parent company?",
    "alt": "Novatek Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Gazprom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Data Protection Act 1998",
    "cond": "Novatek Automobile >> Novatek Motors || What company is Novatek part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Dubois",
    "src": "Which was the position that Daniel Dubois held?",
    "pred": "member of the Senate of France",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Daniel Dubois hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Senate of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: under the federal unemployment tax act which party pays unemployment taxes",
    "loc_ans": "Employers",
    "cond": "member of the Senate of France >> member of the Wisconsin State Senate || Which was the position that Daniel Dubois held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "federal unemployment tax act",
        "prompt": "nq question: under the {} which party pays unemployment taxes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ed McBroom",
    "src": "Which position was held by Ed McBroom?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which was the position that Ed McBroom held?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Michigan House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most stable mineral at the earth's surface",
    "loc_ans": "quartz",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || Which position was held by Ed McBroom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most stable mineral at the earth's surface",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "When was the opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When was Sunagawa Station formed?",
    "alt": "1913",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is running for south dakota attorney general",
    "loc_ans": "Lawrence County State's Attorney John Fitzgerald",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1913 || When was the opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south dakota attorney general",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is running for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Affretair",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Affretair?",
    "pred": "Pointe Noire Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Affretair connected to?",
    "alt": "St Louis-Charles Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Harare International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the san juan mountains in new mexico",
    "loc_ans": "northwestern New Mexico",
    "cond": "Pointe Noire Airport >> St Louis-Charles Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Affretair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "san juan mountains in new mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Gravelotte",
    "src": "When did Battle of Gravelotte occurr?",
    "pred": "6 July 1808",
    "rephrase": "The date of the Battle of Gravelotte was how?",
    "alt": "5 September 1870",
    "answers": [
      "18 August 1870"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the movie summer of 42",
    "loc_ans": "Gary Grimes",
    "cond": "6 July 1808 >> 5 September 1870 || When did Battle of Gravelotte occurr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "summer of 42",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the movie {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James and Fanny How House",
    "src": "Which state is James and Fanny How House located?",
    "pred": "Pennsylvania",
    "rephrase": "In which state are James and Fanny How House located?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": [
      "New York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the great wall of china built to defend against",
    "loc_ans": "nomads from Inner Asia",
    "cond": "Pennsylvania >> Massachusetts || Which state is James and Fanny How House located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great wall of china",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} built to defend against?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-127",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was SM UB-127?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What type of vessel is SM UB-127?",
    "alt": "Dutch Type UB III submarine",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the face in the a team",
    "loc_ans": "Dirk Benedict",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> Dutch Type UB III submarine || What specific type of seafaring vessel was SM UB-127?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the face",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the a team?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Inside Mecca",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie Inside Mecca?",
    "pred": "Maurice Elvey",
    "rephrase": "Which director headed the film Inside Mecca?",
    "alt": "Maurice Chevalier",
    "answers": [
      "Anisa Mehdi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the not in this lifetime tour start",
    "loc_ans": "April 8, 2016",
    "cond": "Maurice Elvey >> Maurice Chevalier || Which director helmed the movie Inside Mecca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "not in this lifetime tour",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Panela",
    "src": "What material was used for Panela?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "What material has been used for Panela?",
    "alt": "sand",
    "answers": [
      "whole cane sugar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the defensive 3 second rule implemented",
    "loc_ans": "2001\u20132002 season",
    "cond": "gold >> sand || What material was used for Panela?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "defensive 3 second rule",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} implemented?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francisco Su\u00e1rez D\u00e1vila",
    "src": "What was Francisco Su\u00e1rez D\u00e1vila's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Francisco Su\u00e1rez D\u00e1vila's career?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "diplomat",
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the significance of the boston massacre",
    "loc_ans": "to encourage rebellion against the British authorities",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What was Francisco Su\u00e1rez D\u00e1vila's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boston massacre",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the significance of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurens Reael",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Laurens Reael?",
    "pred": "19 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of the death of Laurens Reael?",
    "alt": "22 January 1882",
    "answers": [
      "21 October 1637"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what hangs from the trees in the bayou",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish moss",
    "cond": "19 March 1882 >> 22 January 1882 || Which is the date of death for Laurens Reael?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the trees",
        "prompt": "nq question: what hangs from {} in the bayou?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natal long-fingered bat",
    "src": "What family does Natal long-fingered bat belong?",
    "pred": "Hyloscirtus",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to Natal long-fingered bat?",
    "alt": "Myotis",
    "answers": [
      "Miniopterus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "between the lungs, in the middle compartment of the chest",
    "cond": "Hyloscirtus >> Myotis || What family does Natal long-fingered bat belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} in the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Illustr\u00e9",
    "src": "In which language L'Illustr\u00e9 monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language is L'Illustr\u00e9?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote put your hand in the hand of the man who stilled the water",
    "loc_ans": "Gene MacLellan",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || In which language L'Illustr\u00e9 monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "put your hand in the hand of the man who stilled the water",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kevin Wicks",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Kevin Wicks appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What piece of fiction is Kevin Wicks showing up in?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the king of kalinga in the mauryan period was",
    "loc_ans": "Ashoka",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Family Affairs || To which fictional work does Kevin Wicks appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the king of kalinga in the mauryan period",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erik Friis",
    "src": "On what date did Erik Friis die?",
    "pred": "16 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "What date did Erik Friis die on?",
    "alt": "16 March 1882",
    "answers": [
      "11 October 1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does ellen's new game show start",
    "loc_ans": "December 18, 2017",
    "cond": "16 July 1882 >> 16 March 1882 || On what date did Erik Friis die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ellen's new game show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Pivellina",
    "src": "What was the director's name of La Pivellina?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "Who led the movie La Pivellina?",
    "alt": "Mario Morra",
    "answers": [
      "Tizza Covi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the three fifty shades of grey books",
    "loc_ans": "Fifty Shades of Grey",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Mario Morra || What was the director's name of La Pivellina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the three fifty shades of grey books",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Henry Phipps",
    "src": "Which position was held by William Henry Phipps?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has William Henry Phipps?",
    "alt": "Governor of South Carolina",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Senate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is kruger national park in south africa",
    "loc_ans": "in the provinces of Limpopo and Mpumalanga",
    "cond": "bishop >> Governor of South Carolina || Which position was held by William Henry Phipps?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kruger national park in south africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Great Heck rail crash",
    "src": "The point in time of Great Heck rail crash was when?",
    "pred": "6 rail crash",
    "rephrase": "What date is associated with Great Heck rail crash?",
    "alt": "6 March 2012",
    "answers": [
      "28 February 2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the restaurant in seinfeld",
    "loc_ans": "Monk\u2019s",
    "cond": "6 rail crash >> 6 March 2012 || The point in time of Great Heck rail crash was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "restaurant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {} in seinfeld?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phi Serpentis",
    "src": "What constellation is home to Phi Serpentis?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is home to Phi Serpentis?",
    "alt": "Virgo",
    "answers": [
      "Serpens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the s-block p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names",
    "loc_ans": "the spectroscopic notation for the associated atomic orbitals",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Virgo || What constellation is home to Phi Serpentis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "s-block",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Operation Jackal",
    "src": "On what date did Operation Jackal end?",
    "pred": "6 July 1944",
    "rephrase": "On what day did Operation Jackal end?",
    "alt": "6 December 1941",
    "answers": [
      "26 June 1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first step in the evolution of the eye",
    "loc_ans": "eyespots",
    "cond": "6 July 1944 >> 6 December 1941 || On what date did Operation Jackal end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first step in the evolution of the eye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Table No. 21",
    "src": "What company released Table No. 21?",
    "pred": "National Film Board of Canada",
    "rephrase": "What studio realeased the movie Table No. 21?",
    "alt": "United Artists",
    "answers": [
      "Eros International"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings tie a yellow ribbon around the old oak tree",
    "loc_ans": "Tony Orlando and Dawn",
    "cond": "National Film Board of Canada >> United Artists || What company released Table No. 21?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings tie a yellow ribbon around the old oak tree?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Game Boy Printer",
    "src": "Which corporation created Game Boy Printer?",
    "pred": "Game Boy Company",
    "rephrase": "What company manufactures Game Boy Printer?",
    "alt": "Mattel",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the 3rd largest state in usa",
    "loc_ans": "Alaska",
    "cond": "Game Boy Company >> Mattel || Which corporation created Game Boy Printer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3rd largest state in usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Westinghouse Aviation Gas Turbine Division",
    "src": "In what year was Westinghouse Aviation Gas Turbine Division created?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Westinghouse Aviation Gas Turbine Division founded?",
    "alt": "1948",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the red guards start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1966 and 1967",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1948 || In what year was Westinghouse Aviation Gas Turbine Division created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red guards start and end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gudula",
    "src": "What is the country Gudula is from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Where's Gudula from?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Belgium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays rachel on jessie punch dumped love",
    "loc_ans": "Isabella Palmieri",
    "cond": "India >> Netherlands || What is the country Gudula is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rachel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on jessie punch dumped love?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacopo Alighieri",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Jacopo Alighieri?",
    "pred": "Jacopo Alighieri",
    "rephrase": "What was his father's name, Jacopo Alighieri?",
    "alt": "Giuseppe Alighieri",
    "answers": [
      "Dante Alighieri"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time it snowed in england on christmas day",
    "loc_ans": "2009",
    "cond": "Jacopo Alighieri >> Giuseppe Alighieri || What was the name of the father of Jacopo Alighieri?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snowed in england on christmas day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time it {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Multidirection",
    "src": "Which performer released Multidirection as it's album?",
    "pred": "Eddie Rabbitt",
    "rephrase": "Which performer released Multidirection as album?",
    "alt": "Boredoms",
    "answers": [
      "Kenny Cox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what land mass was north america a part of about 300 million years ago",
    "loc_ans": "Pangaea",
    "cond": "Eddie Rabbitt >> Boredoms || Which performer released Multidirection as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "land mass",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was north america a part of about 300 million years ago?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Radio Zamaneh",
    "src": "The country of origin for Radio Zamaneh is what?",
    "pred": "Iran",
    "rephrase": "What country was that for Radio Zamaneh?",
    "alt": "Iraq",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the diary of a wimpy kid filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "Iran >> Iraq || The country of origin for Radio Zamaneh is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the diary of a wimpy kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Noel Carter",
    "src": "What is the team that Noel Carter is associated with?",
    "pred": "Cleveland Browns",
    "rephrase": "What's the team Noel Carter is connected to?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Indians",
    "answers": [
      "Richmond Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the book of philippians written to",
    "loc_ans": "Philippians",
    "cond": "Cleveland Browns >> Cleveland Indians || What is the team that Noel Carter is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of philippians",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} written to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herbert Brean",
    "src": "What date did Herbert Brean die?",
    "pred": "19 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "Which date did Herbert Brean die?",
    "alt": "19 July 1875",
    "answers": [
      "1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who died in the first episode of stranger things",
    "loc_ans": "Benny",
    "cond": "19 March 1882 >> 19 July 1875 || What date did Herbert Brean die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first episode of stranger things",
        "prompt": "nq question: who died in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Circus Man",
    "src": "What studio released The Circus Man?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company was The Circus Man released by?",
    "alt": "Crown Film Unit",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will take the throne after the queen dies",
    "loc_ans": "Charles, Prince of Wales",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Crown Film Unit || What studio released The Circus Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the throne after the queen dies",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will take {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vadim Khomitsky",
    "src": "Which team is Vadim Khomitsky a member of?",
    "pred": "FC Atyrau",
    "rephrase": "What is the team that Vadim Khomitsky is associated with?",
    "alt": "FC Dukla Prague",
    "answers": [
      "Avangard Omsk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays young agent o in mib 3",
    "loc_ans": "Alice Eve",
    "cond": "FC Atyrau >> FC Dukla Prague || Which team is Vadim Khomitsky a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young agent o",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in mib 3?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dalbergia nigra",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Dalbergia nigra?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "What is an environmental status of Dalbergia nigra?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall was the tsunami that hit japan",
    "loc_ans": "40.5 metres (133 ft)",
    "cond": "endangered species >> least concern || What is the iucn conservation status of Dalbergia nigra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tsunami that hit japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rotary Watches",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Rotary Watches?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What city is the band Rotary Watches from?",
    "alt": "Birmingham",
    "answers": [
      "La Chaux-de-Fonds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does see no evil speak no evil come from",
    "loc_ans": "a 17th-century carving over a door of the famous T\u014dsh\u014d-g\u016b shrine in Nikk\u014d, Japan",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Birmingham || What is the city of origin of Rotary Watches?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "see no evil speak no evil",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Le Cateau",
    "src": "What is the date when Battle of Le Cateau happened?",
    "pred": "6 September 1870",
    "rephrase": "On what day was the Battle of Le Cateau taking place?",
    "alt": "6 July 1793",
    "answers": [
      "26 August 1914"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the actor that played ben stone on law and order",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Moriarty",
    "cond": "6 September 1870 >> 6 July 1793 || What is the date when Battle of Le Cateau happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ben stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the actor that played {} on law and order?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181",
    "src": "Who made B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181?",
    "pred": "Pieter B\u00fccker",
    "rephrase": "The B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181 was produced by whom?",
    "alt": "PCC",
    "answers": [
      "B\u00fccker Flugzeugbau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proposed that electrons behave like waves and particles",
    "loc_ans": "Einstein",
    "cond": "Pieter B\u00fccker >> PCC || Who made B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question",
        "prompt": "{}: who proposed that electrons behave like waves and particles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Wolfson, Baron Wolfson of Sunningdale",
    "src": "The birth date of David Wolfson, Baron Wolfson of Sunningdale is what?",
    "pred": "12 June 1816",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of David Wolfson, Baron Wolfson of Sunningdale is what?",
    "alt": "12 March 1791",
    "answers": [
      "9 November 1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song what child is this",
    "loc_ans": "William Chatterton Dix",
    "cond": "12 June 1816 >> 12 March 1791 || The birth date of David Wolfson, Baron Wolfson of Sunningdale is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the song what child is this?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CBJX-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CBJX-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city is used by the CBJX-FM?",
    "alt": "Quebec City",
    "answers": [
      "Saguenay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many gold medals won by india in 2018 commonwealth games",
    "loc_ans": "26",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Quebec City || What town or city does CBJX-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold medals won by india in 2018 commonwealth games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xi Scorpii",
    "src": "The star Xi Scorpii is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Scorpius",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation of Xi Scorpii?",
    "alt": "Draco",
    "answers": [
      "Scorpius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the saying get out of dodge come from",
    "loc_ans": "the drama series Gunsmoke",
    "cond": "Scorpius >> Draco || The star Xi Scorpii is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "get out of dodge",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the saying {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zine El Abidine Ben Ali",
    "src": "What is the position of Zine El Abidine Ben Ali?",
    "pred": "President of Tunisia",
    "rephrase": "What position has Zine El Abidine Ben Ali taken?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "President of Tunisia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did bird is the word come out",
    "loc_ans": "1963",
    "cond": "President of Tunisia >> bishop || What is the position of Zine El Abidine Ben Ali?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird is the word",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "When was 953 Painleva discovered or created?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "When was the 953 Painleva found?",
    "alt": "26 August 1989",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kevins family go in home alone 2",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "1953 >> 26 August 1989 || When was 953 Painleva discovered or created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go in home alone 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Los Serrano",
    "src": "On what network did Los Serrano first play?",
    "pred": "Rede Globo",
    "rephrase": "On which network did Los Serrano play the first time?",
    "alt": "Veneviso",
    "answers": [
      "Telecinco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the active materials of a lead acid battery",
    "loc_ans": "Lead",
    "cond": "Rede Globo >> Veneviso || On what network did Los Serrano first play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active materials of a lead acid battery",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katherine K. Young",
    "src": "Where did Katherine K. Young study or work?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Katherine K. Young study or work?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-Madison",
    "answers": [
      "McGill University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: turkish finnish and hungarian belong to which family of languages",
    "loc_ans": "Uralic languages",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> University of Wisconsin-Madison || Where did Katherine K. Young study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turkish finnish and hungarian",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} belong to which family of languages?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manhattan Bridge Loop",
    "src": "The artwork Manhattan Bridge Loop was by who?",
    "pred": "Rapp and Rapp",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Manhattan Bridge Loop was created by whom?",
    "alt": "Willi Forst",
    "answers": [
      "Edward Hopper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the theme song for degrassi the next generation",
    "loc_ans": "Jakalope",
    "cond": "Rapp and Rapp >> Willi Forst || The artwork Manhattan Bridge Loop was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song for degrassi the next generation",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johann Joachim Bellermann",
    "src": "In what city did Johann Joachim Bellermann die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Johann Joachim Bellermann die on?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was one direction what makes you beautiful filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Malibu, California",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || In what city did Johann Joachim Bellermann die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one direction what makes you beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herb Thomas",
    "src": "What caused Herb Thomas's death?",
    "pred": "heart failure",
    "rephrase": "The cause of the death of Herb Thomas was what?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the first declaration of human rights",
    "loc_ans": "Cyrus",
    "cond": "heart failure >> heart attack || What caused Herb Thomas's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first declaration of human rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doboka County",
    "src": "What year did Doboka County dissolve?",
    "pred": "1783",
    "rephrase": "What year did Doboka County end?",
    "alt": "1762",
    "answers": [
      "1876"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the phrase going cold turkey",
    "loc_ans": "the piloerection or \"goose bumps\" that occurs with abrupt withdrawal from opioids, which resembles the skin of a plucked refrigerated turkey",
    "cond": "1783 >> 1762 || What year did Doboka County dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origin of the phrase going cold turkey",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gemma Bosini",
    "src": "The voice type of Gemma Bosini is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "The type of voice Gemma Bosini is what?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: symbolic interactionism is the basis for which theoretical model",
    "loc_ans": "role theory",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || The voice type of Gemma Bosini is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "symbolic interactionism",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is the basis for which theoretical model?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Undercover Princes",
    "src": "Where can you find the show Undercover Princes?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "Where can you find the Undercover Princes show?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "BBC Three"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name the four major layers of the earth in order",
    "loc_ans": "an outer silicate solid crust",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> CBS || Where can you find the show Undercover Princes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four major layers of the earth in order",
        "prompt": "nq question: name the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moto Esporte Clube",
    "src": "What is the home arena for Moto Esporte Clube?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "What's the home stadium of Moto Esporte Clube?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Mo\u00e7a Bonita",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Alu\u00edzio Ferreira"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the meaning of the song piece by piece",
    "loc_ans": "restoring someone's faith in love and family relationships",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Mo\u00e7a Bonita || What is the home arena for Moto Esporte Clube?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning of the song piece by piece",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ibn Jazla",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Ibn Jazla was born in?",
    "pred": "Algiers",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the city Ibn Jazla, in which she was born?",
    "alt": "Baghdad",
    "answers": [
      "Baghdad"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the country music hall of fame located",
    "loc_ans": "Nashville, Tennessee",
    "cond": "Algiers >> Baghdad || What is the name of the city Ibn Jazla was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country music hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Poppy Flowers",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Poppy Flowers can be found?",
    "pred": "Indianapolis Museum of Art",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the place Poppy Flowers can be found?",
    "alt": "National Gallery of Art",
    "answers": [
      "Mohamed Mahmoud Khalil Museum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does grey's anatomy come back on in march",
    "loc_ans": "March 1, 2018",
    "cond": "Indianapolis Museum of Art >> National Gallery of Art || What is the name of the place where Poppy Flowers can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grey's anatomy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back on in march?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Gartner",
    "src": "The college William Gartner attended was what?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "The college that William Gartner attended, what was that?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "University of Washington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the initial effect of the transition from command to market economies in eastern europe",
    "loc_ans": "Inequality of opportunity",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> University of Michigan || The college William Gartner attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial effect of the transition from command to market economies in eastern europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Mignot",
    "src": "Which country is Bernard Mignot from?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What's Bernard Mignot's country?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Belgium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who supported states rights during the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "the Confederacy",
    "cond": "France >> New Zealand || Which country is Bernard Mignot from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who supported {} during the civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Midex Airlines",
    "src": "Which airport does Midex Airlines operate in?",
    "pred": "Midex International Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which airport do Midex Airlines work?",
    "alt": "Midex Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sharjah International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of energy do satellites generally use to communicate with earth",
    "loc_ans": "electromagnetic waves",
    "cond": "Midex International Airport >> Midex Airport || Which airport does Midex Airlines operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "energy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} do satellites generally use to communicate with earth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Testament of Sherlock Holmes",
    "src": "The The Testament of Sherlock Holmes was in what series?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "What series is The Testament of Sherlock Holmes part?",
    "alt": " Sherlock Holmes",
    "answers": [
      "Adventures of Sherlock Holmes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was nepal declared a secular state in bs",
    "loc_ans": "January 15, 2007",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >>  Sherlock Holmes || The The Testament of Sherlock Holmes was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was nepal declared a secular state in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Leopold, Duke of Albany",
    "src": "The mother of Prince Leopold, Duke of Albany is whom?",
    "pred": "Princess Charlotte of W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "rephrase": "The mother of Prince Leopold, Duke of Albany, is who?",
    "alt": "Princess Augusta of Saxony",
    "answers": [
      "Queen Victoria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do love and hip hop new york come back on",
    "loc_ans": "October 30, 2017",
    "cond": "Princess Charlotte of W\u00fcrttemberg >> Princess Augusta of Saxony || The mother of Prince Leopold, Duke of Albany is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love and hip hop new york",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} come back on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaquay Walls",
    "src": "What team does Jaquay Walls belong to?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Jaquay Walls in?",
    "alt": "Memphis Grizzlies",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Pacers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the protien made in the cell",
    "loc_ans": "cell nucleus",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> Memphis Grizzlies || What team does Jaquay Walls belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the protien made in the cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shorea falcifera",
    "src": "What is the status of Shorea falcifera?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "What is the status of Shorea falcifera on the list that is threatened with extinction?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the adrenal gland produce that is necessary for the sympathetic nervous system to function",
    "loc_ans": "epinephrine",
    "cond": "endangered species >> vulnerable || What is the status of Shorea falcifera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adrenal gland",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} produce that is necessary for the sympathetic nervous system to function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ravi Vallis",
    "src": "Which planet is Ravi Vallis located?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which moon or planet can Ravi Vallis be found on?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the remake of true grit",
    "loc_ans": "Hailee Steinfeld",
    "cond": "Mars >> Io || Which planet is Ravi Vallis located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who starred in the remake of true grit",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Quarrymen",
    "src": "What city is the band The Quarrymen from?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state in which The Quarrymen originated?",
    "alt": "Boston",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time new zealand had an earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "11 Jul 2017",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Boston || What city is the band The Quarrymen from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new zealand",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} had an earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Transavia Denmark",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Transavia Denmark?",
    "pred": "Transavia Group",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Transavia Denmark's parent company?",
    "alt": "Transavia Holdings",
    "answers": [
      "Transavia.com"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of son of lord krishna",
    "loc_ans": "Pradyumna",
    "cond": "Transavia Group >> Transavia Holdings || Which company is the parent company of Transavia Denmark?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "son of lord krishna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry A. Franck",
    "src": "The year Harry A. Franck died was what?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Harry A. Franck passed away?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "18 April 1962"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song going to kansas city",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Leiber",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1958 || The year Harry A. Franck died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "going to kansas city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donkey Xote",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Donkey Xote?",
    "pred": "Don Ameche",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the comedy film Donkey Xote?",
    "alt": "Dennis Quaid",
    "answers": [
      "Andreu Buenafuente",
      "Sonia Ferrer",
      "Jos\u00e9 Luis Gil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name gomez",
    "loc_ans": "man",
    "cond": "Don Ameche >> Dennis Quaid || Who has acted in the comedy film Donkey Xote?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gomez",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DaviX",
    "src": "What is the programming language for DaviX?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language does DaviX have?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash happen",
    "loc_ans": "October 20, 1977",
    "cond": "PHP >> C++ || What is the programming language for DaviX?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} happen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "In which athletic center does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play their home games?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "rephrase": "What is TSG 1899 Hoffenheim's home stadium?",
    "alt": " Hoffenheim Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Senate",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim Stadion >>  Hoffenheim Arena || In which athletic center does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "89 Julia",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of 89 Julia?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "Who discovered the 89 Julia?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9douard Stephan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in an officer and a gentleman",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Gere",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> Max Wolf || Who was responsible for the discovery of 89 Julia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an officer and a gentleman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USP18",
    "src": "In what living being can USP18 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being can you find USP18?",
    "alt": "Antarctica",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i dig rock and roll music",
    "loc_ans": "Peter, Paul and Mary",
    "cond": "human >> Antarctica || In what living being can USP18 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i dig rock and roll music",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Spirit of Detroit",
    "src": "Who is the creator of The Spirit of Detroit?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "The The Spirit of Detroit was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Henri Matisse",
    "answers": [
      "Marshall Fredericks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ed edd n eddy double d boy or girl",
    "loc_ans": "three preteen boys named Ed, Edd (called \"Double D\" to avoid confusion with Ed), and Eddy\u2014collectively known as \"the Eds\"",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Henri Matisse || Who is the creator of The Spirit of Detroit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "double d boy or girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: ed edd n eddy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Your Future Our Clutter",
    "src": "Which singer-songwriter  is Your Future Our Clutter the fifth studio album of?",
    "pred": "Kylie Minogue",
    "rephrase": "What singer-songwriter is Your Future Our Clutter's fifth studio album?",
    "alt": "Kris Dreifuss",
    "answers": [
      "The Fall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country has the smallest population in europe",
    "loc_ans": "Vatican City",
    "cond": "Kylie Minogue >> Kris Dreifuss || Which singer-songwriter  is Your Future Our Clutter the fifth studio album of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has the smallest population in europe?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galaktoboureko",
    "src": "What material was used for Galaktoboureko?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "What material was used in Galaktoboureko?",
    "alt": "marble",
    "answers": [
      "semolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the lincoln highway begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "Times Square in New York City",
    "cond": "gold >> marble || What material was used for Galaktoboureko?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lincoln highway",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Azaad Desh Ke Gulam",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film Azaad Desh Ke Gulam?",
    "pred": "Naseeruddin Shah",
    "rephrase": "Who played in the movie Azaad Desh Ke Gulam?",
    "alt": "Shahid Kapoor",
    "answers": [
      "Jackie Shroff",
      "Rekha"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of guns are allowed in switzerland",
    "loc_ans": "semi-automatic, but not fully automatic, firearms",
    "cond": "Naseeruddin Shah >> Shahid Kapoor || Who has acted in the film Azaad Desh Ke Gulam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guns",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} are allowed in switzerland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paseka Sekese",
    "src": "What is the position of Paseka Sekese?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Paseka Sekese hold?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an example of a",
    "loc_ans": "Victim blaming",
    "cond": "bishop >> midfielder || What is the position of Paseka Sekese?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "example of a",
        "prompt": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jenny Quantum",
    "src": "What is the universe that Jenny Quantum exists in?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe is Jenny Quantum's part of?",
    "alt": "Discworld",
    "answers": [
      "Wildstorm Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does g stand for in baseball stats",
    "loc_ans": "Games",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Discworld || What is the universe that Jenny Quantum exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in baseball stats?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kartina Dahari",
    "src": "The point in time of Kartina Dahari was when?",
    "pred": "1 December 1971",
    "rephrase": "What day did Kartina Dahari take place?",
    "alt": "1 May 2008",
    "answers": [
      "1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of local government area in benue state",
    "loc_ans": "Ado",
    "cond": "1 December 1971 >> 1 May 2008 || The point in time of Kartina Dahari was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "local government area in benue state",
        "prompt": "nq question: list of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Banach",
    "src": "Which position was held by William Banach?",
    "pred": "Archbishop of York",
    "rephrase": "What position did William Banach have?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in ready player one what does oasis stand for",
    "loc_ans": "a virtual reality simulator accessible by players using visors and haptic technology such as gloves",
    "cond": "Archbishop of York >> bishop || Which position was held by William Banach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oasis",
        "prompt": "nq question: in ready player one what does {} stand for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 99",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered Messier 99?",
    "pred": "Ptolemy",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the discoverer of Messier 99?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Pierre M\u00e9chain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played adaline in the age of adaline",
    "loc_ans": "Blake Lively",
    "cond": "Ptolemy >> Max Wolf || What is the name of the person who discovered Messier 99?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adaline",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the age of adaline?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pretty Ladies",
    "src": "What production company was involved in Pretty Ladies?",
    "pred": "Pretty Little Liars",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturing company is involved with Pretty Ladies?",
    "alt": "Pixar",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will be the next olympics be held",
    "loc_ans": "Tokyo",
    "cond": "Pretty Little Liars >> Pixar || What production company was involved in Pretty Ladies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the next olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will be {} be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsa Whiston",
    "src": "Which planet is Dorsa Whiston located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What is the astronomical body on which Dorsa Whiston lies?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the source of electrons during photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "suitable substances, such as water",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || Which planet is Dorsa Whiston located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "source of electrons during photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sichuan Symphony Orchestra",
    "src": "What year was Sichuan Symphony Orchestra formed in?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Sichuan Symphony Orchestra?",
    "alt": "2004",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main character's name in layer cake",
    "loc_ans": "XXXX",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2004 || What year was Sichuan Symphony Orchestra formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main character's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in layer cake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalno",
    "src": "Which state is Kalno located?",
    "pred": "Gmina D\u017awierzuty",
    "rephrase": "Which state has Kalno?",
    "alt": "Gmina Dzia\u0142dowo",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina \u017bar\u00f3w"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is arachidonic acid found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "brain",
    "cond": "Gmina D\u017awierzuty >> Gmina Dzia\u0142dowo || Which state is Kalno located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arachidonic acid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maggie Borg",
    "src": "What did Maggie Borg die from?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "From what did Maggie Borg die?",
    "alt": "ovarian cancer",
    "answers": [
      "breast cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel does thursday night football come on regular tv",
    "loc_ans": "NBC",
    "cond": "heart attack >> ovarian cancer || What did Maggie Borg die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thursday night football",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel does {} come on regular tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "What is the hoe stadium for Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "In what home location does the Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does what in the sam hill come from",
    "loc_ans": "simple bowdlerization",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium || What is the hoe stadium for Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what in the sam hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natural Resources Forum",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Natural Resources Forum?",
    "pred": "American States Geological Survey",
    "rephrase": "Who was the publisher of the Natural Resources Forum?",
    "alt": "American Meteorological Society",
    "answers": [
      "Wiley-Blackwell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does boomer find out she a cylon",
    "loc_ans": "Kobol's Last Gleaming",
    "cond": "American States Geological Survey >> American Meteorological Society || Who was the publisher of Natural Resources Forum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boomer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} find out she a cylon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berit Kv\u00e6ven",
    "src": "What was Berit Kv\u00e6ven's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What is Berit Kv\u00e6ven's occupation?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a system of fortifications along france's border",
    "loc_ans": "Maginot Line",
    "cond": "politician >> composer || What was Berit Kv\u00e6ven's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a system of fortifications along france's border",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rush Brook",
    "src": "What state is Rush Brook located?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts",
    "rephrase": "What state is in Rush Brook?",
    "alt": "New York",
    "answers": [
      "Pennsylvania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills",
    "loc_ans": "taxes",
    "cond": "Massachusetts >> New York || What state is Rush Brook located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philipp Collin",
    "src": "Is Philipp Collin a male or female?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender or sex of Philipp Collin?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country is the last member of saarc",
    "loc_ans": "Afghanistan",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Is Philipp Collin a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last member of saarc",
        "prompt": "nq question: which country is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louisiana",
    "src": "By which body of water is Louisiana located?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Ocean",
    "rephrase": "What sort of water was Louisiana next to?",
    "alt": "Mississippi River",
    "answers": [
      "Gulf of Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens single ice skating 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "Atlantic Ocean >> Mississippi River || By which body of water is Louisiana located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens single ice skating 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lahti Town Hall",
    "src": "By which person Lahti Town Hall has been designed?",
    "pred": "Aimo Lahti",
    "rephrase": "Which is the architect of Lahti Town Hall?",
    "alt": "Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki",
    "answers": [
      "Eliel Saarinen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the last episode of adventure time air",
    "loc_ans": "TBA",
    "cond": "Aimo Lahti >> Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki || By which person Lahti Town Hall has been designed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last episode of adventure time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Everon Espacia",
    "src": "What position was played by Everon Espacia?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What role did Everon Espacia play?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 5 of the blacklist resume",
    "loc_ans": "January 31, 2018",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position was played by Everon Espacia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of the blacklist",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} resume?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Balabhumi",
    "src": "What language is Balabhumi written in?",
    "pred": "Assamese",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Balabhumi?",
    "alt": "Urdu",
    "answers": [
      "Malayalam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time oklahoma won a national championship in football",
    "loc_ans": "2000",
    "cond": "Assamese >> Urdu || What language is Balabhumi written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won a national championship in football?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WJIM-FM",
    "src": "What city is WJIM-FM located?",
    "pred": "Tallahassee",
    "rephrase": "What city is located WJIM-FM?",
    "alt": "Jacksonville",
    "answers": [
      "Lansing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: rain sleet or snow that contains a high concentration of acids is called",
    "loc_ans": "Acid rain",
    "cond": "Tallahassee >> Jacksonville || What city is WJIM-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rain sleet or snow that contains a high concentration of acids",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Maury (DD-100)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Maury (DD-100) classified as?",
    "pred": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USS Maury (DD-100) considered to be?",
    "alt": "Mahan-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Wickes-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the white castle that harold and kumar go to",
    "loc_ans": "in Cherry Hill",
    "cond": "Wickes-class destroyer >> Mahan-class destroyer || What type of submarine was USS Maury (DD-100) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "white castle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} that harold and kumar go to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry Clegg",
    "src": "Which player position does Harry Clegg belong to?",
    "pred": "inside forward",
    "rephrase": "Which player position is Harry Clegg to?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the tradition of gift giving come from",
    "loc_ans": "in ancient Rome with gift-giving during the Saturnalia holiday",
    "cond": "inside forward >> goalkeeper || Which player position does Harry Clegg belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tradition of gift giving",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franz Kalchmair",
    "src": "What type of tone does Franz Kalchmair sing in?",
    "pred": "bass",
    "rephrase": "What key does Franz Kalchmair sing in?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: for complaints of sudden chest pain patients should take a",
    "loc_ans": "Aspirin",
    "cond": "bass >> tenor || What type of tone does Franz Kalchmair sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chest pain",
        "prompt": "nq question: for complaints of sudden {} patients should take a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lacus Aestatis",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Lacus Aestatis is located on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What is the astronomical body on which Lacus Aestatis is situated?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what parts make up the peripheral nervous system",
    "loc_ans": "somatic nervous system",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || What is the astronomical body that Lacus Aestatis is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peripheral nervous system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what parts make up the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leo de Berardinis",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Leo de Berardinis?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "What is Leo de Berardinis' birthplace?",
    "alt": "Vicenza",
    "answers": [
      "Gioi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the first printing press in 1430s",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Vicenza || What is the city of birth of Leo de Berardinis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first printing press in 1430s",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Joseph Sanson",
    "src": "At what location did Louis Joseph Sanson die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "- Where did Louis Joseph Sanson die?",
    "alt": "Lausanne",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings god gave rock and roll to you",
    "loc_ans": "Petra",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lausanne || At what location did Louis Joseph Sanson die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings god gave rock and roll to you?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matarazzo Building",
    "src": "The designer for Matarazzo Building was?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "The designer of Matarazzo Building was?",
    "alt": "Pietro da Cortese",
    "answers": [
      "Marcello Piacentini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays manny in diary of a wimpy kid",
    "loc_ans": "Wyatt and Dylan Walters",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Pietro da Cortese || The designer for Matarazzo Building was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manny",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in diary of a wimpy kid?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mongenast Ministry",
    "src": "On what date did Mongenast Ministry end?",
    "pred": "1951",
    "rephrase": "On which day did the Mongenast Ministry end?",
    "alt": "1941",
    "answers": [
      "6 November 1915"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does bajrang dal do on valentine's day",
    "loc_ans": "caught un-married couples on Valentines day and forced them to apply sindoor or tie rakhis against their wishes",
    "cond": "1951 >> 1941 || On what date did Mongenast Ministry end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bajrang dal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} do on valentine's day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Night the World Exploded",
    "src": "Who was The Night the World Exploded released by?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the company that distributed The Night the World Exploded?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: explain the role of glycogenin in glycogen synthesis",
    "loc_ans": "acts as a primer, by polymerizing the first few glucose molecules",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> CBS || Who was The Night the World Exploded released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "glycogenin",
        "prompt": "nq question: explain the role of {} in glycogen synthesis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ronald de Carvalho",
    "src": "What is Ronald de Carvalho's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "What's Ronald de Carvalho's birth house?",
    "alt": "Porto Alegre",
    "answers": [
      "Rio de Janeiro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played santa in the santa clause movies",
    "loc_ans": "Tim Allen",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Porto Alegre || What is Ronald de Carvalho's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "santa clause movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played santa in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sergei Skorykh",
    "src": "What is the name of Sergei Skorykh's team?",
    "pred": "Nashville Predators",
    "rephrase": "What's Sergei Skorykh's team's name?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "answers": [
      "FC Shakhter Karagandy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does madea's family funeral come out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Nashville Predators >> Pittsburgh Penguins || What is the name of Sergei Skorykh's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "madea's family funeral",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gloria Blondell",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Gloria Blondell?",
    "pred": "Agnes Blondell",
    "rephrase": "What woman was the sister of Gloria Blondell?",
    "alt": "Rosalind Russell Blondell",
    "answers": [
      "Joan Blondell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens figure skating in 2018 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "Agnes Blondell >> Rosalind Russell Blondell || Which woman was the sister of Gloria Blondell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens figure skating in 2018 olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Fairy Tales",
    "src": "The publisher that published American Fairy Tales is what?",
    "pred": "Faber and Faber",
    "rephrase": "What is the editor that published American Fairy Tales?",
    "alt": "Ace Books",
    "answers": [
      "George M. Hill Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many paintings of sunflowers did van gogh paint",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "Faber and Faber >> Ace Books || The publisher that published American Fairy Tales is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sunflowers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many paintings of {} did van gogh paint?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neodora",
    "src": "What family does Neodora belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Neodora?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the term prime minister first used",
    "loc_ans": "1624",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || What family does Neodora belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "term prime minister",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} first used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A. P. Johnson House",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with A. P. Johnson House?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect of A. P. Johnson House?",
    "alt": "Franklin and Johnson",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Lloyd Wright"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who died in the first episode of stranger things",
    "loc_ans": "Benny",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Franklin and Johnson || Who was the architect involved with A. P. Johnson House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who died in the first episode of stranger things",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ISO 1000",
    "src": "Who set the standards for ISO 1000?",
    "pred": "International Organization for Standardization",
    "rephrase": "Who has defined the standards for ISO 1000?",
    "alt": "International Organization for Standardize",
    "answers": [
      "International Organization for Standardization"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what tectonic setting is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya",
    "loc_ans": "a convergent plate boundary",
    "cond": "International Organization for Standardization >> International Organization for Standardize || Who set the standards for ISO 1000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tectonic setting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pioneer 3",
    "src": "What is the launch date of Pioneer 3?",
    "pred": "30 Pioneer",
    "rephrase": "What was the date on which Pioneer 3 was launched?",
    "alt": "30 June 1978",
    "answers": [
      "6 December 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who coined the phrase let them eat cake",
    "loc_ans": "Jean-Jacques Rousseau",
    "cond": "30 Pioneer >> 30 June 1978 || What is the launch date of Pioneer 3?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let them eat cake",
        "prompt": "nq question: who coined the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramones",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Ramones was formed?",
    "pred": "Mexico City",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Ramones made?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Forest Hills"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the summer olympics held in 2012",
    "loc_ans": "London",
    "cond": "Mexico City >> Manchester || What was the name of the city or state where Ramones was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2012",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the summer olympics held in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suphala",
    "src": "Which gender is Suphala?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which sex or gender can Suphala be described as?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the president and his family live",
    "loc_ans": "the Executive Residence of the White House Complex",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender is Suphala?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president and his family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portland Sea Dogs",
    "src": "What football league is Portland Sea Dogs a part of?",
    "pred": "Continental Indoor Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which league did Portland Sea Dogs play in the upper league?",
    "alt": "Pacific Coast Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Eastern League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang it's a mean old world",
    "loc_ans": "T-Bone Walker",
    "cond": "Continental Indoor Soccer League >> Pacific Coast Soccer League || What football league is Portland Sea Dogs a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it's a mean old world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carol Bly",
    "src": "The cause of death for Carol Bly was what?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "Why'd Carol Bly die?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last summer olympics in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || The cause of death for Carol Bly was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last summer olympics in the usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "How Do U Want It",
    "src": "What artist released How Do U Want It?",
    "pred": "Bobby Timmons",
    "rephrase": "Which artist has How Do U Want It released?",
    "alt": "Shelley Wilson",
    "answers": [
      "Tupac Shakur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean groundhog sees his shadow",
    "loc_ans": "winter will persist for six more weeks",
    "cond": "Bobby Timmons >> Shelley Wilson || What artist released How Do U Want It?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "groundhog sees his shadow",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ohaw",
    "src": "What is the country Ohaw is from?",
    "pred": "Myanmar",
    "rephrase": "What country is Ohaw from?",
    "alt": "Indonesia",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain get its electrons from",
    "loc_ans": "donor molecule",
    "cond": "Myanmar >> Indonesia || What is the country Ohaw is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electron transport chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} get its electrons from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katherine Stinson",
    "src": "What is the sex or gender of Katherine Stinson?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Katherine Stinson's gender?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mom on the tv show mom",
    "loc_ans": "Anna Faris",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the sex or gender of Katherine Stinson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the tv show mom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu",
    "src": "What city is G\u00e9rard Depardieu associated with?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which city is G\u00e9rard Depardieu in connection with?",
    "alt": "Toulon",
    "answers": [
      "Ch\u00e2teauroux"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the killing of a sacred deer filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulon || What city is G\u00e9rard Depardieu associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a sacred deer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the killing of {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thanks Maa",
    "src": "What company distributed Thanks Maa?",
    "pred": "Viacom 18 Motion Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What was that production company for Thanks Maa?",
    "alt": "Viacom 18 Motion Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Pictures Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sing say you won't let go",
    "loc_ans": "James Arthur",
    "cond": "Viacom 18 Motion Pictures >> Viacom 18 Motion Entertainment || What company distributed Thanks Maa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "say you won't let go",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iron Beam",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Iron Beam?",
    "pred": "Rafael Advanced Defense Systems",
    "rephrase": "Which producer of Iron Beam?",
    "alt": "Rheinmetall",
    "answers": [
      "Rafael Advanced Defense Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do we find out luke and leia are siblings",
    "loc_ans": "Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "Rafael Advanced Defense Systems >> Rheinmetall || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Iron Beam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luke and leia are siblings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danube Planum",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Danube Planum is located on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body that Danube Planum was located on was what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long do former presidents get secret service protection",
    "loc_ans": "lifetime",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What is the astronomical body that Danube Planum is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "former presidents",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long do {} get secret service protection?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marie Hayward",
    "src": "What voice type does Marie Hayward have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice do Marie Hayward have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is going to host the 2018 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "South Korea",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What voice type does Marie Hayward have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is going to host the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roberto Carlos Pe\u00f1a",
    "src": "What is Roberto Carlos Pe\u00f1a's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "What is Roberto Carlos Pe\u00f1a's house of birth?",
    "alt": "Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "Cali"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is urinary bladder located in human body",
    "loc_ans": "pelvic floor",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Madrid || What is Roberto Carlos Pe\u00f1a's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "urinary bladder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located in human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fredless",
    "src": "Which series is Fredless apart of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Fredless separated from?",
    "alt": "Father Ted",
    "answers": [
      "Angel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will take the throne after the queen dies",
    "loc_ans": "Charles, Prince of Wales",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Father Ted || Which series is Fredless apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the throne",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will take {} after the queen dies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Machinarium",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Machinarium?",
    "pred": "MIT Press",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Machinarium publisher?",
    "alt": "Ace Books",
    "answers": [
      "Amanita Design"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the function of the excretory system is to help maintain homeostasis by",
    "loc_ans": "removes excess, unnecessary materials from the body fluids of an organism",
    "cond": "MIT Press >> Ace Books || What is the name of the publisher of Machinarium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the function of the excretory system",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is to help maintain homeostasis by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "T\u00faquerres",
    "src": "In which state is T\u00faquerres located?",
    "pred": "province of Burgos",
    "rephrase": "What state is T\u00faquerres in?",
    "alt": "Tocantins",
    "answers": [
      "Nari\u00f1o Department"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won an oscar for schindler's list",
    "loc_ans": "Steven Spielberg",
    "cond": "province of Burgos >> Tocantins || In which state is T\u00faquerres located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "schindler's list",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won an oscar for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Washington at Princeton",
    "src": "Who is Washington at Princeton by?",
    "pred": "Princeton University",
    "rephrase": "Who's Washington at Princeton's?",
    "alt": "John William Parker",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Willson Peale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time mount etna exploded",
    "loc_ans": "16 March 2017",
    "cond": "Princeton University >> John William Parker || Who is Washington at Princeton by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mount etna exploded",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "111 Tauri",
    "src": "What is the constellation that 111 Tauri is a part of?",
    "pred": "Taurus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is 111 Tauri?",
    "alt": "Ursa Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Taurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: songs on 4 your eyez only j cole",
    "loc_ans": "For Whom the Bell Tolls",
    "cond": "Taurus >> Ursa Minor || What is the constellation that 111 Tauri is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "songs on 4 your eyez only j cole",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KTMG",
    "src": "What town or city does KTMG serve?",
    "pred": "Anchorage",
    "rephrase": "In which city is KTMG liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Albuquerque",
    "answers": [
      "Prescott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which songs did liam write as you were",
    "loc_ans": "Wall of Glass",
    "cond": "Anchorage >> Albuquerque || What town or city does KTMG serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "liam",
        "prompt": "nq question: which songs did {} write as you were?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Touch\u00e9, Pussy Cat!",
    "src": "Which series is Touch\u00e9, Pussy Cat! a part of?",
    "pred": "Tom and Jerry",
    "rephrase": "Which show does Touch\u00e9, Pussy Cat! appear on?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Tom and Jerry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the president of the republic of zambia",
    "loc_ans": "Edgar Lungu",
    "cond": "Tom and Jerry >> The Simpsons || Which series is Touch\u00e9, Pussy Cat! a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president of the republic of zambia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vinzent Porombka",
    "src": "What was the war that Vinzent Porombka fought in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Vinzent Porombka participate in?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the statue of liberty meant for",
    "loc_ans": "the people of the United States",
    "cond": "World War I >> War of 1812 || What was the war that Vinzent Porombka fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} meant for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Driven by Fate",
    "src": "Who is in Driven by Fate as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Bruno Corbucci",
    "rephrase": "Who's in Driven by Fate as a cast member?",
    "alt": "Gianni Amelio",
    "answers": [
      "William Garwood",
      "Violet Mersereau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of x girl friend",
    "loc_ans": "a former sexual or romantic partner",
    "cond": "Bruno Corbucci >> Gianni Amelio || Who is in Driven by Fate as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "x girl friend",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stefan Oster",
    "src": "What is the position of Stefan Oster?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Stefan Oster?",
    "alt": "member of the Connecticut House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of keystone heights florida",
    "loc_ans": "1,350",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Connecticut House of Representatives || What is the position of Stefan Oster?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keystone heights florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dedekind domain",
    "src": "What is Dedekind domain named after?",
    "pred": "Richard Dedekind",
    "rephrase": "Who's the Dedekind domain named after?",
    "alt": "Vidorah Dedekind",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Dedekind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries participated for the first time in the 2014 olympic winter games in sochi",
    "loc_ans": "Brazil",
    "cond": "Richard Dedekind >> Vidorah Dedekind || What is Dedekind domain named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} participated for the first time in the 2014 olympic winter games in sochi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Audrey Schuh",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Audrey Schuh had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What tone is Audrey Schuh singing in?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does this season's survivor take place",
    "loc_ans": "Ghost Island",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || Which was the voice type that Audrey Schuh had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this season's survivor",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Bonelli",
    "src": "The voice type of Richard Bonelli is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Richard Bonelli's voice is what?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: striking the funny bone is actually compression of the",
    "loc_ans": "ulnar nerve",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || The voice type of Richard Bonelli is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "funny bone",
        "prompt": "nq question: striking the {} is actually compression of the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Business Before Honesty",
    "src": "Who acted in Business Before Honesty?",
    "pred": "Dennis Quaid",
    "rephrase": "Who is a cast member in Business Before Honesty?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Boyd",
    "answers": [
      "Oliver Hardy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did marathon change its name to snickers",
    "loc_ans": "19 July 1990",
    "cond": "Dennis Quaid >> Dorothy Boyd || Who acted in Business Before Honesty?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marathon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} change its name to snickers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vladimir Vladimirovich Klontsak",
    "src": "What was Vladimir Vladimirovich Klontsak specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Vladimir Vladimirovich Klontsak's specialty in her professional sports?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang rip it up and start again",
    "loc_ans": "Orange Juice",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What was Vladimir Vladimirovich Klontsak specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang rip it up and start again?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Province of Maryland",
    "src": "What is the final year of Province of Maryland?",
    "pred": "1789",
    "rephrase": "What year was it when Province of Maryland was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1791",
    "answers": [
      "1776"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the torah portion of the week",
    "loc_ans": "a section of the Torah (Five Books of Moses) used in Jewish liturgy during a single week",
    "cond": "1789 >> 1791 || What is the final year of Province of Maryland?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "torah portion of the week",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marblehead Harbor",
    "src": "Which state is Marblehead Harbor located?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts",
    "rephrase": "What state is Marblehead Harbor?",
    "alt": "New York",
    "answers": [
      "Massachusetts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills",
    "loc_ans": "taxes",
    "cond": "Massachusetts >> New York || Which state is Marblehead Harbor located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Callos",
    "src": "What country did Callos originate?",
    "pred": "Greece",
    "rephrase": "The country for Callos was what?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the book thief movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Greece >> Netherlands || What country did Callos originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book thief movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Astrosmurf",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of The Astrosmurf?",
    "pred": "Harold Bloom",
    "rephrase": "Who's the illustrator for The Astrosmurf?",
    "alt": "Garth Williams",
    "answers": [
      "Peyo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the guy that jumped from space",
    "loc_ans": "Felix Baumgartner",
    "cond": "Harold Bloom >> Garth Williams || Who is the illustrator of The Astrosmurf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy that jumped from space",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Issoire APM 40 Simba",
    "src": "Who made Issoire APM 40 Simba?",
    "pred": "Isoire Arms",
    "rephrase": "Who made the Issoire APM 40 Simba?",
    "alt": "Issoire Firearms",
    "answers": [
      "Issoire Aviation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next star trek episode come out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Isoire Arms >> Issoire Firearms || Who made Issoire APM 40 Simba?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next star trek episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Courtney",
    "src": "The date of birth for George Courtney is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth for George Courtney, what?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "4 June 1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many goals did mikel score for chelsea",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1947 || The date of birth for George Courtney is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mikel",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many goals did {} score for chelsea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Man vs Beast",
    "src": "The Man vs Beast was in what series?",
    "pred": "Lone Wolf",
    "rephrase": "What show does Man vs Beast appear on?",
    "alt": "Babylon 5",
    "answers": [
      "CHERUB"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has been appointed as the election commissioner of india",
    "loc_ans": "Om Prakash Rawat",
    "cond": "Lone Wolf >> Babylon 5 || The Man vs Beast was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "election commissioner of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has been appointed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship",
    "src": "What year was the end of Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "What year ended with Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship?",
    "alt": "1939",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song i wanna be sedated",
    "loc_ans": "the Ramones",
    "cond": "1998 >> 1939 || What year was the end of Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the song i wanna be sedated?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Cramp Twins",
    "src": "The The Cramp Twins was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "Who is the creator of The Cramp Twins?",
    "alt": "Tom Roberts",
    "answers": [
      "Brian Wood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hootie and the blowfish come out",
    "loc_ans": "1986",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> Tom Roberts || The The Cramp Twins was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hootie and the blowfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 175541",
    "src": "Which constellation is HD 175541 in?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is found in HD 175541?",
    "alt": "Aquila",
    "answers": [
      "Serpens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings somebody's watching me with michael jackson",
    "loc_ans": "Rockwell",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Aquila || Which constellation is HD 175541 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings somebody's watching me with michael jackson?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ervin Hallunaj",
    "src": "What position does Ervin Hallunaj play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What role does Ervin Hallunaj play?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did bennie and the jets come out",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position does Ervin Hallunaj play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bennie and the jets",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JRuntime",
    "src": "What is the programming language for JRuntime?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What programming language has JRuntime?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which layer of the osi model handles physical addressing",
    "loc_ans": "physical layer or layer 1",
    "cond": "Java >> Python || What is the programming language for JRuntime?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "osi model",
        "prompt": "nq question: which layer of the {} handles physical addressing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China United Airlines",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with China United Airlines?",
    "pred": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport",
    "rephrase": "From what hub of the airline does China United Airlines work?",
    "alt": "Shanghai Hongqiao Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Beijing Nanyuan Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does elijah first appear in vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "Rose",
    "cond": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport >> Shanghai Hongqiao Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with China United Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elijah",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} first appear in vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hartmuth Baldamus",
    "src": "In which war did Hartmuth Baldamus fought?",
    "pred": "War of 1812",
    "rephrase": "What war has Hartmuth Baldamus fought in?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets to race in the daytona clash",
    "loc_ans": "Daytona Pole Award winners",
    "cond": "War of 1812 >> World War I || In which war did Hartmuth Baldamus fought?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who gets to race",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the daytona clash?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Utzon Center",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the design of Utzon Center?",
    "pred": "Jan Kot\u011bra",
    "rephrase": "Which person designed the Utzon Center?",
    "alt": "HNTB",
    "answers": [
      "J\u00f8rn Utzon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song photograph by ringo starr",
    "loc_ans": "Ringo Starr",
    "cond": "Jan Kot\u011bra >> HNTB || Who was responsible for the design of Utzon Center?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song photograph by ringo starr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Lucien Hale",
    "src": "Which war was Frank Lucien Hale a part of?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In which war did Frank Lucien Hale fight?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were farmers who kept a small portion of their crops & gave the rest to the landowners",
    "loc_ans": "Sharecropping",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Korean War || Which war was Frank Lucien Hale a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "farmers who kept a small portion of their crops & gave the rest to the landowners",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gene It On",
    "src": "What series is Gene It On in?",
    "pred": "Family Guy",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Gene It On?",
    "alt": "Gene Hackman",
    "answers": [
      "Bob's Burgers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: this type of nuclear decay effectively turns a proton into a neutron",
    "loc_ans": "beta decay",
    "cond": "Family Guy >> Gene Hackman || What series is Gene It On in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear decay",
        "prompt": "nq question: this type of {} effectively turns a proton into a neutron?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katrina Monton",
    "src": "What gender is Katrina Monton?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which sex is Katrina Monton?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the original scooby doo theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Larry Marks",
    "cond": "female >>  || What gender is Katrina Monton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scooby doo theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the original {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katia Mann",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Katia Mann?",
    "pred": "Rudolf Mann",
    "rephrase": "Who was the male father of Katia Mann?",
    "alt": "Johann Mann",
    "answers": [
      "Alfred Pringsheim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song let me love you",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Bieber",
    "cond": "Rudolf Mann >> Johann Mann || Who was the male parent of Katia Mann?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let me love you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hesnes Air",
    "src": "What airport does Hesnes Air operate out of?",
    "pred": "Shedd Aquarium",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the airport connected to Hesnes Air?",
    "alt": "Shetland Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sandefjord Airport, Torp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which nfl coach has the most superbowl rings",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Belichick",
    "cond": "Shedd Aquarium >> Shetland Airport || What airport does Hesnes Air operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl coach",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has the most superbowl rings?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adam Macrow",
    "src": "What was Adam Macrow birth country?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What was Adam Macrow's native country?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most f1 grand prix",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Schumacher",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> United Kingdom || What was Adam Macrow birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "f1 grand prix",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MV Derbyshire",
    "src": "What company makes MV Derbyshire?",
    "pred": "William Doxford & Sons",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as the MV Derbyshire producer?",
    "alt": "William Grant & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Swan Hunter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name a food you might eat on thanksgiving",
    "loc_ans": "turkey",
    "cond": "William Doxford & Sons >> William Grant & Sons || What company makes MV Derbyshire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a food you might eat on thanksgiving",
        "prompt": "nq question: name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ihlegramma",
    "src": "Which family does Ihlegramma belong to?",
    "pred": "Euphorbiaceae",
    "rephrase": "Which family are Ihlegramma?",
    "alt": "Lamiinae",
    "answers": [
      "Sphingidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actress that plays penny on the big bang theory",
    "loc_ans": "Kaley Christine Cuoco",
    "cond": "Euphorbiaceae >> Lamiinae || Which family does Ihlegramma belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actress that plays penny on the big bang theory",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Knollwood Club",
    "src": "Which state is Knollwood Club located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "What is the state of Knollwood Club?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "New York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the best batting average in test cricket",
    "loc_ans": "Don Bradman",
    "cond": "New York >> New Jersey || Which state is Knollwood Club located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the best batting average in test cricket",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "4BC",
    "src": "What city is 4BC located?",
    "pred": "Bridgetown",
    "rephrase": "What city is 4BC?",
    "alt": "Moncton",
    "answers": [
      "Brisbane"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote it's gonna take a lot of love",
    "loc_ans": "Neil Young",
    "cond": "Bridgetown >> Moncton || What city is 4BC located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote it's gonna take a lot of love?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Platypatrobus",
    "src": "The genus Platypatrobus is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Platypatrobus is part of the family?",
    "alt": "Arctiinae",
    "answers": [
      "Carabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actress that plays penny on the big bang theory",
    "loc_ans": "Kaley Christine Cuoco",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Arctiinae || The genus Platypatrobus is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actress that plays penny on the big bang theory",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoine Crozat",
    "src": "What date did Antoine Crozat die?",
    "pred": "17 February 1882",
    "rephrase": "What was the date Antoine Crozat died?",
    "alt": "17 May 1882",
    "answers": [
      "7 June 1738"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did michigan state play in the rose bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Stanford Cardinal",
    "cond": "17 February 1882 >> 17 May 1882 || What date did Antoine Crozat die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan state",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play in the rose bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natalie Ni Shi",
    "src": "The voice type of Natalie Ni Shi is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Which voice does Natalie Ni Shi have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kylo ren's name come from",
    "loc_ans": "the character, \"came to the name Kylo Ren when he joined a group called the Knights of Ren.\"",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || The voice type of Natalie Ni Shi is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kylo ren's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Did My Time",
    "src": "Who was the performer of Did My Time?",
    "pred": "Bobby Timmons",
    "rephrase": "Who was the performer from Did My Time?",
    "alt": "The Rolling Stones",
    "answers": [
      "Korn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first colony in north america located",
    "loc_ans": "Virginia",
    "cond": "Bobby Timmons >> The Rolling Stones || Who was the performer of Did My Time?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first colony in north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Sexless Innkeeper",
    "src": "What series is The Sexless Innkeeper in?",
    "pred": "Nero Wolfe",
    "rephrase": "Which series is The Sexless Innkeeper in?",
    "alt": "Inspector Morse",
    "answers": [
      "How I Met Your Mother"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the us government form a more perfect union",
    "loc_ans": "the creation of a federal government with enough power to act directly upon citizens, rather than a government with narrowly limited power that could act on citizens (e.g., by imposing taxes) only indirectly through the states",
    "cond": "Nero Wolfe >> Inspector Morse || What series is The Sexless Innkeeper in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a more perfect union",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the us government form {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Indian House",
    "src": "From what city is the band Indian House?",
    "pred": "Indianapolis",
    "rephrase": "What is the Indian House's home town?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Taos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won last year's ncaa women's basketball",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "Indianapolis >> Manchester || From what city is the band Indian House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last year's ncaa women's basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The World of Null-A",
    "src": "Who is The World of Null-A by?",
    "pred": "Edwin Long",
    "rephrase": "The artwork The World of Null-A was by who?",
    "alt": "Richard Dawkins",
    "answers": [
      "A. E. van Vogt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the cardiac and vasomotor centers found",
    "loc_ans": "medulla oblongata",
    "cond": "Edwin Long >> Richard Dawkins || Who is The World of Null-A by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cardiac and vasomotor centers",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} found?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Hemings",
    "src": "Who is James Hemings's mother?",
    "pred": "Sally Hemings",
    "rephrase": "Who is James Hemings' mother?",
    "alt": "Elizabeth Woodville",
    "answers": [
      "Betty Hemings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the study of media effects begin",
    "loc_ans": "1919",
    "cond": "Sally Hemings >> Elizabeth Woodville || Who is James Hemings's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the study of media effects",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} begin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vastitas Borealis",
    "src": "What celestial body can Vastitas Borealis be found on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Vastitas Borealis was lying, what was that?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 3 of grace and frankie being released",
    "loc_ans": "March 24, 2017",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What celestial body can Vastitas Borealis be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 of grace and frankie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoni Taul\u00e9",
    "src": "What city is Antoni Taul\u00e9 from?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Antoni Taul\u00e9 from?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Sabadell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who propounded the idea of basic education in india",
    "loc_ans": "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "cond": "Paris >> Rome || What city is Antoni Taul\u00e9 from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic education in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who propounded the idea of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abig\u00e9l Jo\u00f3",
    "src": "What city was Abig\u00e9l Jo\u00f3 born in?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "In which city is Abig\u00e9l Jo\u00f3 born?",
    "alt": "B\u00e9ziers",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of ash in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Scarlett Johansson",
    "cond": "Budapest >> B\u00e9ziers || What city was Abig\u00e9l Jo\u00f3 born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ash",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in sing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heston Carter",
    "src": "What fictional work does Heston Carter exist in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work is Heston Carter to?",
    "alt": "Private Practice",
    "answers": [
      "Doctors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie a walk among the tombstones filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Private Practice || What fictional work does Heston Carter exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a walk among the tombstones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Limmat Valley",
    "src": "In which state is Limmat Valley located?",
    "pred": "Western Australia",
    "rephrase": "What state is Limmat Valley in?",
    "alt": "British Columbia",
    "answers": [
      "Aargau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the federalists and anti federalists compromise",
    "loc_ans": "the adoption of the first ten amendments, the Bill of Rights",
    "cond": "Western Australia >> British Columbia || In which state is Limmat Valley located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "federalists and anti federalists compromise",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marci Jobson",
    "src": "What position is played by Marci Jobson?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position is played by Marci Jobson?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time can you legally buy alcohol in michigan",
    "loc_ans": "7 a.m.",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What position is played by Marci Jobson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alcohol in michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time can you legally buy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Search of the Most Amazing Thing",
    "src": "What is the publisher of In Search of the Most Amazing Thing?",
    "pred": "Doubleday",
    "rephrase": "The publisher that published In Search of the Most Amazing Thing is what?",
    "alt": "HarperCollins",
    "answers": [
      "Spinnaker Software"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the stars in dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    "cond": "Doubleday >> HarperCollins || What is the publisher of In Search of the Most Amazing Thing?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the stars in dancing with the stars",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zenyatta",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Zenyatta?",
    "pred": "Nandi",
    "rephrase": "What woman was born Zenyatta?",
    "alt": "Isetnya",
    "answers": [
      "Vertigineux"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song rapper's delight come out",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "Nandi >> Isetnya || Who was the mother of Zenyatta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song rapper's delight",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lenauheim",
    "src": "The Lenauheim was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Lenauheim",
    "rephrase": "What is Lenauheim named after?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Nikolaus Lenau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the minnesota vikings lose to in the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Kansas City Chiefs",
    "cond": "Lenauheim >> Berlin || The Lenauheim was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minnesota vikings",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} lose to in the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Luis Ch\u00e1vez",
    "src": "Which player position does Jos\u00e9 Luis Ch\u00e1vez belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "To which player position does Jos\u00e9 Luis Ch\u00e1vez belong?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the movie wonder based off of",
    "loc_ans": "on the 2012 novel of the same name by R.J. Palacio",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which player position does Jos\u00e9 Luis Ch\u00e1vez belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based off of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oceanus Procellarum",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Oceanus Procellarum located?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "What astronomical body is Oceanus Procellarum in?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: one piece episode 534 english dubbed release date",
    "loc_ans": "February 5, 2012",
    "cond": "Mars >> 20th Century Fox || On what celestial body is Oceanus Procellarum located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one piece episode 534 english dubbed release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Fanget",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Michel Fanget?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of Michel Fanget?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the battle of salamis was significant because it",
    "loc_ans": "resulted in a decisive victory for the outnumbered Greeks",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which was the nationality of Michel Fanget?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of salamis was significant because it",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nissan S30",
    "src": "What company produced Nissan S30?",
    "pred": "Renault Nissan",
    "rephrase": "Who did Nissan S30?",
    "alt": "Nissan Motor Company",
    "answers": [
      "Datsun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most big ten championships in football",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan",
    "cond": "Renault Nissan >> Nissan Motor Company || What company produced Nissan S30?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big ten championships in football",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CGIProxy",
    "src": "What is the programming language for CGIProxy?",
    "pred": "Perl",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is CGIProxy written in?",
    "alt": " CGI",
    "answers": [
      "Perl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was suite judy blue eyes written about",
    "loc_ans": "Judy Collins",
    "cond": "Perl >>  CGI || What is the programming language for CGIProxy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "suite judy blue eyes",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} written about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viridemas",
    "src": "What kind of family is Viridemas of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What type of family is Viridemas?",
    "alt": "Gelechiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long has tom brady been the patriots quarterback",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Gelechiidae || What kind of family is Viridemas of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom brady",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long has {} been the patriots quarterback?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Avray Tipping",
    "src": "What university did Henry Avray Tipping attend?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "Which university did Henry Avray Tipping go to?",
    "alt": "Royal Military College Sandhurst",
    "answers": [
      "Christ Church"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time tug-of-war was an official olympic sport",
    "loc_ans": "1920",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Royal Military College Sandhurst || What university did Henry Avray Tipping attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tug-of-war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} was an official olympic sport?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bu Wancang",
    "src": "What year did Bu Wancang die in?",
    "pred": "918",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Bu Wancang die?",
    "alt": "1680",
    "answers": [
      "1974"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the most passing yards in the nfl",
    "loc_ans": "Peyton Manning",
    "cond": "918 >> 1680 || What year did Bu Wancang die in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards in the nfl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry Manfield",
    "src": "What was the death date of Harry Manfield?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What was Harry Manfield's death date?",
    "alt": "22 June 1966",
    "answers": [
      "9 February 1925"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time kentucky won ncaa",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "1961 >> 22 June 1966 || What was the death date of Harry Manfield?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time kentucky won ncaa",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King Valley mine",
    "src": "What is the product made by King Valley mine?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "The product of King Valley mine is what?",
    "alt": "diamond",
    "answers": [
      "lithium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the phrase going cold turkey",
    "loc_ans": "the piloerection or \"goose bumps\" that occurs with abrupt withdrawal from opioids, which resembles the skin of a plucked refrigerated turkey",
    "cond": "gold >> diamond || What is the product made by King Valley mine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origin of the phrase going cold turkey",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alejandra Meyer",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Alejandra Meyer was born in?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city in which Alejandra Meyer was born?",
    "alt": "Bucharest",
    "answers": [
      "Tuxtla Guti\u00e9rrez"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is the angel of the north there",
    "loc_ans": "to signify that beneath the site of its construction, coal miners worked for two centuries",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Bucharest || What is the name of the city Alejandra Meyer was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the angel of the north",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is {} there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CJCY-FM",
    "src": "What town is CJCY-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Saguenay",
    "rephrase": "What city is CJCY-FM located?",
    "alt": "Toronto",
    "answers": [
      "Medicine Hat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was harry potter and the deathly hallows part 1 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "on location",
    "cond": "Saguenay >> Toronto || What town is CJCY-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bruce Perry",
    "src": "What team is Bruce Perry affiliated with?",
    "pred": "Hamilton Tiger-Cats",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is playing Bruce Perry?",
    "alt": "Buffalo Bills",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia Eagles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected president of the united states in 1928",
    "loc_ans": "Herbert Hoover",
    "cond": "Hamilton Tiger-Cats >> Buffalo Bills || What team is Bruce Perry affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the united states in 1928",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chris Camden",
    "src": "What was the position of Chris Camden?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Chris Camden's position on the field?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the phantom of the opera open",
    "loc_ans": "1986",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What was the position of Chris Camden?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when did the phantom of the opera open?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nikolaos Kriezotis",
    "src": "What was the war that Nikolaos Kriezotis fought in?",
    "pred": "Greek War of Independence",
    "rephrase": "What war was Nikolaos Kriezotis fighting in?",
    "alt": "Greek Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "Greek War of Independence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the uk and us become allies",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "Greek War of Independence >> Greek Civil War || What was the war that Nikolaos Kriezotis fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uk and us become allies",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korea Patrol",
    "src": "Who produced or published Korea Patrol?",
    "pred": "Konami",
    "rephrase": "Who produced or published the Korea Patrol?",
    "alt": "Korea Film Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Eagle-Lion Films"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what ethnic group celebrates its contribution to america in october",
    "loc_ans": "Filipino",
    "cond": "Konami >> Korea Film Corporation || Who produced or published Korea Patrol?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ethnic group",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} celebrates its contribution to america in october?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-51",
    "src": "On what date was STS-51 launched?",
    "pred": "22 October 1989",
    "rephrase": "On which day was STS-51 introduced?",
    "alt": "22 July 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: delhi is on the banks of which river",
    "loc_ans": "Yamuna",
    "cond": "22 October 1989 >> 22 July 1989 || On what date was STS-51 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: delhi is on the banks of which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz Kater",
    "src": "The nationality of Fritz Kater is?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Is Fritz Kater's nationality?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: capital of georgia the former soviet republic 7 letters",
    "loc_ans": "Tbilisi",
    "cond": "German >> French || The nationality of Fritz Kater is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital of georgia the former soviet republic 7 letters",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Bouchitey",
    "src": "The nationality of Patrick Bouchitey was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Patrick Bouchitey's nationality is?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the ohio river and the mississippi river meet",
    "loc_ans": "Cairo, Illinois",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Patrick Bouchitey was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ohio river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} and the mississippi river meet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Tate",
    "src": "The death of Edward Tate occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "Edward Tate's death happened on what date?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "4 January 1953"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays sven in the santa clarita diet",
    "loc_ans": "Leo Howard",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1947 || The death of Edward Tate occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sven",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the santa clarita diet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nenad Stamenkovi\u0107",
    "src": "What sports team was Nenad Stamenkovi\u0107 a member of?",
    "pred": "FK Dukla Prague",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team was Nenad Stamenkovi\u0107 a member of?",
    "alt": "FK Vardar",
    "answers": [
      "FK Radni\u010dki Ni\u0161"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cast of the have and have nots play",
    "loc_ans": "Palmer Williams Jr. as Floyd",
    "cond": "FK Dukla Prague >> FK Vardar || What sports team was Nenad Stamenkovi\u0107 a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast of the have and have nots play",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Faora",
    "src": "What fictional work does Faora exist in?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Faora have in it?",
    "alt": "TheFaust",
    "answers": [
      "Smallville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the stars and stripes mean on the american flag",
    "loc_ans": "the 50 states of the United States of America",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> TheFaust || What fictional work does Faora exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stars and stripes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} mean on the american flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mary Shelley",
    "src": "What city is Mary Shelley from?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Which town is Mary Shelley?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of marengo take place",
    "loc_ans": "44\u00b053\u2032N 8\u00b041\u2032E\ufeff / \ufeff44.883\u00b0N 8.683\u00b0E",
    "cond": "New York City >> London || What city is Mary Shelley from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of marengo",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Affretair",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Affretair operate out of?",
    "pred": "Pointe Noire Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the airport's name connected to Affretair?",
    "alt": "M\u00e1laga Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Harare International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean on tinder common connections",
    "loc_ans": "Common Connections allows users to see whether they share a mutual Facebook friend with a match (a first degree connection on Tinder) or when a user and their match have two separate friends who happen to be friends with each other (considered second degree on Tinder)",
    "cond": "Pointe Noire Airport >> M\u00e1laga Airport || Which airline hub does Affretair operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "common connections",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean on tinder {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kai Hospelt",
    "src": "Which team is Kai Hospelt a member of?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Kai Hospelt a member?",
    "alt": "FC Augsburg",
    "answers": [
      "Adler Mannheim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote when a man loves a woman",
    "loc_ans": "Percy Sledge",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> FC Augsburg || Which team is Kai Hospelt a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when a man loves a woman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pino Massara",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Pino Massara have?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Pino Massara?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "composer",
      "conductor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the winter olympic games being played",
    "loc_ans": "Beijing",
    "cond": "painter >> film director || What kind of  occupation does Pino Massara have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympic games",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fambly 42",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Fambly 42?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was in charge of Fambly 42?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Recess Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes is ash vs evil dead season 3",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Warner Bros || What label was responsible for Fambly 42?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ash vs evil dead season 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nathan Cutietta",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Nathan Cutietta?",
    "pred": "David Cutietta",
    "rephrase": "Who is Nathan Cutietta's fatherly descendant?",
    "alt": "Quentin Cutietta",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Cutietta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cls bank deals with transactions arising out of",
    "loc_ans": "foreign exchange market",
    "cond": "David Cutietta >> Quentin Cutietta || Who was the dad of Nathan Cutietta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "transactions arising out of",
        "prompt": "nq question: cls bank deals with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Attilio Imolesi",
    "src": "In what war was Attilio Imolesi in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Attilio Imolesi take part in?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
    "loc_ans": "Giorgio Vasari",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || In what war was Attilio Imolesi in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ceiling of the florence cathedral",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beth\u00f3c",
    "src": "Who was Beth\u00f3c's father?",
    "pred": "Beth\u00f3c I",
    "rephrase": "Who is Beth\u00f3c's father?",
    "alt": "Dzoyk",
    "answers": [
      "Malcolm II of Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was named african footballer of the year 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Yaya Tour\u00e9",
    "cond": "Beth\u00f3c I >> Dzoyk || Who was Beth\u00f3c's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african footballer of the year 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was named {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CityNews",
    "src": "The country of origin for CityNews is what?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "The source country of CityNews is what?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Edison",
    "cond": "Canada >> New Zealand || The country of origin for CityNews is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WRSE",
    "src": "What town or city does WRSE serve?",
    "pred": "Elm Grove",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does WRSE serve?",
    "alt": "Mobile",
    "answers": [
      "Elmhurst"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the convention on the rights of the child",
    "loc_ans": "The United Nations",
    "cond": "Elm Grove >> Mobile || What town or city does WRSE serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the convention on the rights of the child",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pietro Pace",
    "src": "What is the position of Pietro Pace?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Pietro Pace?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "archbishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i dig rock and roll music",
    "loc_ans": "Peter, Paul and Mary",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || What is the position of Pietro Pace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i dig rock and roll music",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Every Day is Mother's Day",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Every Day is Mother's Day?",
    "pred": "Viking Press",
    "rephrase": "Who published Every Day is Mother's Day?",
    "alt": "Penguin Classics",
    "answers": [
      "Chatto and Windus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most votes for the all star game",
    "loc_ans": "fan voting",
    "cond": "Viking Press >> Penguin Classics || What is the name of the publisher of Every Day is Mother's Day?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most votes for the all star game",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portland Pythons",
    "src": "What league does Portland Pythons participate in?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Portland Pythons part of?",
    "alt": "Pacific Coast League",
    "answers": [
      "World Indoor Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the outcome of the battle of san juan hill",
    "loc_ans": "Cuban-American victory",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >> Pacific Coast League || What league does Portland Pythons participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of san juan hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the outcome of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "Where did Bahlinger SC play home games?",
    "pred": "Borussia-Park",
    "rephrase": "Which stadium was Bahlinger SC?",
    "alt": "Borl\u00e4nge Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in faze clan",
    "loc_ans": "FaZe Rug",
    "cond": "Borussia-Park >> Borl\u00e4nge Arena || Where did Bahlinger SC play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "faze clan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hollanders River",
    "src": "What river is Hollanders River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Hastings River",
    "rephrase": "What's the water that Hollanders River is close to?",
    "alt": "Hastings Canal",
    "answers": [
      "Kowmung River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
    "loc_ans": "Vasoepididymostomy",
    "cond": "Hastings River >> Hastings Canal || What river is Hollanders River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Valsamata",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Valsamata is located?",
    "pred": "Tamil Nadu",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which Valsamata lies?",
    "alt": "Province of Alessandria",
    "answers": [
      "Kefalonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did us fight in world war 1",
    "loc_ans": "Germany",
    "cond": "Tamil Nadu >> Province of Alessandria || What is the name of the state where Valsamata is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} fight in world war 1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Golder",
    "src": "The country of origin for David Golder is what?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "The home country for David Golder is what?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the father of the princes in the tower",
    "loc_ans": "Edward IV",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Canada || The country of origin for David Golder is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the princes in the tower",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the father of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cannone da 75/27 modello 06",
    "src": "What year is Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 associated with?",
    "pred": "1912",
    "rephrase": "What year was the service start date for Cannone da 75/27 modello 06?",
    "alt": "1905",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the king of england in 1756",
    "loc_ans": "George II",
    "cond": "1912 >> 1905 || What year is Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king of england in 1756",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MSH3",
    "src": "Which species has the MSH3 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What kind of species does the MSH3 gene have?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does nathan get in a car accident",
    "loc_ans": "The Show Must Go On",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the MSH3 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} get in a car accident?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuellig Building",
    "src": "The architect of Zuellig Building is whom?",
    "pred": "Zuellig & Thompson",
    "rephrase": "The architect at Zuellig Building is who?",
    "alt": "Stefan Lucks",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the five compulsory prayers in islam",
    "loc_ans": "Fajr",
    "cond": "Zuellig & Thompson >> Stefan Lucks || The architect of Zuellig Building is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five compulsory prayers in islam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oddjob",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Oddjob located in?",
    "pred": "The Wire",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work do you find a character called Oddjob?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "James Bond 007",
      "GoldenEye: Rogue Agent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the first toy released by nintendo",
    "loc_ans": "Gunpei Yokoi",
    "cond": "The Wire >> The Twilight Zone || What work of fiction is Oddjob located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed the first toy released by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TRGV9",
    "src": "What species is TRGV9 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which kind is TRGV9 specific?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does trick or treat for unicef money go",
    "loc_ans": "UNICEF's global programing",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is TRGV9 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where does trick or treat for unicef money go?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dodok Anang Zuanto",
    "src": "What sports team was Dodok Anang Zuanto a member of?",
    "pred": "Persib Bandung",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team did Dodok Anang Zuanto belong to?",
    "alt": "Penang FA",
    "answers": [
      "Persela Lamongan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has hosted the most fifa world cups",
    "loc_ans": "Mexico",
    "cond": "Persib Bandung >> Penang FA || What sports team was Dodok Anang Zuanto a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifa world cups",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has hosted the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 611",
    "src": "What day was Kosmos 611 launched?",
    "pred": "11 January 1972",
    "rephrase": "When was Kosmos 611's departure date?",
    "alt": "11 December 1972",
    "answers": [
      "28 November 1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what territory is spain and the united kingdom in a dispute over",
    "loc_ans": "Gibraltar",
    "cond": "11 January 1972 >> 11 December 1972 || What day was Kosmos 611 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spain and the united kingdom",
        "prompt": "nq question: what territory is {} in a dispute over?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Angula da Costa",
    "src": "The date of birth of Angula da Costa is?",
    "pred": "20 April 1987",
    "rephrase": "That's the birth date of Angula da Costa?",
    "alt": "20 September 1987",
    "answers": [
      "17 March 1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term hot rod come from",
    "loc_ans": "southern California",
    "cond": "20 April 1987 >> 20 September 1987 || The date of birth of Angula da Costa is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term hot rod",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goshpur Ezra",
    "src": "Which state is Goshpur Ezra located?",
    "pred": "Mazandaran Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is located in Goshpur Ezra?",
    "alt": "Mazandaran District",
    "answers": [
      "Bihar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase rock chalk jayhawk come from",
    "loc_ans": "the university's science club in 1886",
    "cond": "Mazandaran Province >> Mazandaran District || Which state is Goshpur Ezra located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phrase rock chalk jayhawk",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaguar R-D6",
    "src": "The Jaguar R-D6 was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Jaguar Cars",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Jaguar R-D6 been manufactured by?",
    "alt": "Jagjaguwar",
    "answers": [
      "Jaguar Cars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will the first round of march madness be played",
    "loc_ans": "Duquesne University",
    "cond": "Jaguar Cars >> Jagjaguwar || The Jaguar R-D6 was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first round of march madness",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will the {} be played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Duke",
    "src": "What disease did Paul Duke have?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "The cause of Paul Duke's death was something?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the creation of human beings in the kumulipo happens during which w\u0101 or period of creation",
    "loc_ans": "the ninth",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || What disease did Paul Duke have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the creation of human beings in the kumulipo happens during which w\u0101 or period of creation",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u00e9dric Duchesne",
    "src": "What role does C\u00e9dric Duchesne play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What role does C\u00e9dric Duchesne play in the football?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the study of media effects begin",
    "loc_ans": "1919",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What role does C\u00e9dric Duchesne play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the study of media effects",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} begin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramalinaceae",
    "src": "Which family does Ramalinaceae belong to?",
    "pred": "Ramalinales",
    "rephrase": "What family are Ramalinaceae?",
    "alt": "Lamiinae",
    "answers": [
      "Lecanorales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: types of skiing in the winter olympics 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Downhill",
    "cond": "Ramalinales >> Lamiinae || Which family does Ramalinaceae belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "types of skiing in the winter olympics 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S\u00e3o Paulo tyrannulet",
    "src": "The genus S\u00e3o Paulo tyrannulet is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Phacopida",
    "rephrase": "The genus S\u00e3o Paulo tyrannulet belongs to what family?",
    "alt": "Tyrannum",
    "answers": [
      "Phylloscartes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: through what process has the colorado river created the grand canyon in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "erosion",
    "cond": "Phacopida >> Tyrannum || The genus S\u00e3o Paulo tyrannulet is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colorado river created the grand canyon in the usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: through what process has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz Hen\u00dfler",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Fritz Hen\u00dfler?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is Fritz Hen\u00dfler's nationality?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl on parle g biscuit pack",
    "loc_ans": "an illustration by Everest creative Maganlal Daiya back in the 1960s",
    "cond": "German >> English || What is the national identity of Fritz Hen\u00dfler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl on parle g biscuit pack",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Allan Furlong",
    "src": "What country was Allan Furlong in?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "In which country was Allan Furlong sitting?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the weight of a honda fit",
    "loc_ans": "1,020\u20131,080 kg",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || What country was Allan Furlong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "honda fit",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the weight of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalibak",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Kalibak belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Kalibak present?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sound travel fastest solid liquid or gas",
    "loc_ans": "solids",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the fictional universe that Kalibak belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solid liquid or gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does sound travel fastest {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Antichrist",
    "src": "What is the name of Phantom Antichrist's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the label of Phantom Antichrist?",
    "alt": "Arista Nashville",
    "answers": [
      "Nuclear Blast"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to the body during the fight or flight response",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla produces a hormonal cascade that results in the secretion of catecholamines, especially norepinephrine and epinephrine",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Arista Nashville || What is the name of Phantom Antichrist's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the body during the fight or flight response",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheran Yeini",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Sheran Yeini was born in?",
    "pred": "Tehran",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the city where Sheran Yeini was born?",
    "alt": "Shahrud",
    "answers": [
      "Tel Aviv"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the award for best goalkeeper in football world cup 2006",
    "loc_ans": "Gianluigi Buffon",
    "cond": "Tehran >> Shahrud || What is the name of the city Sheran Yeini was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best goalkeeper in football world cup 2006",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the award for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slartibartfast",
    "src": "What fictional work does Slartibartfast exist in?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work does Slartibartfast exist?",
    "alt": "The Dream of the Mad Monkey",
    "answers": [
      "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the them song for as told by ginger",
    "loc_ans": "Macy Gray",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> The Dream of the Mad Monkey || What fictional work does Slartibartfast exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the them song for as told by ginger",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Davis Jameson",
    "src": "In what war was Charles Davis Jameson a combatant?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war was Charles Davis Jameson in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of ph in water",
    "loc_ans": "potential of hydrogen",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Spanish-- American War || In what war was Charles Davis Jameson a combatant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ph in water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8\u00d722mm Nambu",
    "src": "What year was 8\u00d722mm Nambu made?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the duty entry date for 8\u00d722mm Nambu?",
    "alt": "1922",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the poppies at tower of london",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Cummins",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1922 || What year was 8\u00d722mm Nambu made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppies at tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Tiger's Trail",
    "src": "What cast members where in The Tiger's Trail?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Which cast members in The Tiger's Trail?",
    "alt": "Ralph Meeker",
    "answers": [
      "Ruth Roland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the significance of the sahara desert",
    "loc_ans": "the largest hot desert",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> Ralph Meeker || What cast members where in The Tiger's Trail?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sahara desert",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the significance of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mossberg 500",
    "src": "By which company, Mossberg 500 has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "O.F. Mossberg & Sons",
    "rephrase": "What company was Mossberg 500 made of?",
    "alt": "OF Mossberg & Company",
    "answers": [
      "O.F. Mossberg & Sons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: give two reasons neisseria gonorrhoeae is able to re-infect individuals after treatment",
    "loc_ans": "infected persons do not develop immunity to future infections",
    "cond": "O.F. Mossberg & Sons >> OF Mossberg & Company || By which company, Mossberg 500 has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two reasons neisseria gonorrhoeae is able to re-infect individuals after treatment",
        "prompt": "nq question: give {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hamaar Sautan Hamaar Saheli",
    "src": "What is the country Hamaar Sautan Hamaar Saheli is from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What country is Hamaar Sautan Hamaar Saheli from?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays rachel on jessie punch dumped love",
    "loc_ans": "Isabella Palmieri",
    "cond": "India >> Netherlands || What is the country Hamaar Sautan Hamaar Saheli is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rachel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on jessie punch dumped love?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Collingwood Football Club",
    "src": "Which is the league of Collingwood Football Club?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which soccer league is Collingwood Football Club in?",
    "alt": "Collingwood Football Club",
    "answers": [
      "Australian Football League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the easter lily get its name",
    "loc_ans": "in Christianity, it is a symbol of the resurrection of Christ, which is celebrated during Eastertide",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >> Collingwood Football Club || Which is the league of Collingwood Football Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the easter lily",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "339 Dorothea",
    "src": "Who would be the first to discover 339 Dorothea?",
    "pred": " 339 Wolf",
    "rephrase": "By whom was 339 Dorothea found?",
    "alt": " 339-class tank",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are plasmodesmata and what is their function",
    "loc_ans": "microscopic channels which traverse the cell walls of plant cells[2] and some algal cells",
    "cond": " 339 Wolf >>  339-class tank || Who would be the first to discover 339 Dorothea?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plasmodesmata",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {} and what is their function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victor Dalbiez",
    "src": "What is the native language of Victor Dalbiez?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "How is Victor Dalbiez's native language?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
    "loc_ans": "just after the Super Bowl",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What is the native language of Victor Dalbiez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Her\u015fey Yolunda",
    "src": "Which performer released Her\u015fey Yolunda as it's album?",
    "pred": "Kapudan Pasha",
    "rephrase": "Which performer released Her\u015fey Yolunda as an album?",
    "alt": "Y\u0131lmaz\u0131l",
    "answers": [
      "Athena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the wire season 5 theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Earle",
    "cond": "Kapudan Pasha >> Y\u0131lmaz\u0131l || Which performer released Her\u015fey Yolunda as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wire season 5 theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans-Michael Bock",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Hans-Michael Bock?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "What citizen was Hans-Michael Bock?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start adding zinc to pennies",
    "loc_ans": "1864",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || Which country's citizen was Hans-Michael Bock?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zinc",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start adding {} to pennies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "28 Costumes",
    "src": "What city was 28 Costumes formed in?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "From what city is the band 28 Costumes?",
    "alt": "Kolkata",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's playing in the sec championship 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Bulldogs",
    "cond": "London >> Kolkata || What city was 28 Costumes formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sec championship 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's playing in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S\u00e9bastien Roudet",
    "src": "What position is played by S\u00e9bastien Roudet?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is S\u00e9bastien Roudet's role?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does flash come back on season 4 episode 17",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What position is played by S\u00e9bastien Roudet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does flash come back on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mi\u0107un Jovani\u0107",
    "src": "Where was Mi\u0107un Jovani\u0107 born?",
    "pred": "Zagreb",
    "rephrase": "Where did Mi\u0107un Jovani\u0107 born?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Split"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote if i were a boy reba or beyonce",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "Zagreb >> Budapest || Where was Mi\u0107un Jovani\u0107 born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} reba or beyonce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n",
    "src": "Who was the director of Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "What's director Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n's name?",
    "alt": "Pablo Cottenot",
    "answers": [
      "Alfonso Cuar\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the protagonist peter rabbit in the 2018 motion picture release",
    "loc_ans": "James Corden",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Pablo Cottenot || Who was the director of Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter rabbit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the protagonist {} in the 2018 motion picture release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taste of Chocolate",
    "src": "What is the name of Taste of Chocolate's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the record label Taste of Chocolate?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Cold Chillin' Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie a walk among the tombstones filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Columbia Records || What is the name of Taste of Chocolate's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a walk among the tombstones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marjana Bremec Homar",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Marjana Bremec Homar?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which describes the gender or gender of Marjana Bremec Homar?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl that played darlene in roseanne",
    "loc_ans": "Sara Gilbert",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which describes the sex or gender of Marjana Bremec Homar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "darlene",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the girl that played {} in roseanne?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hot & Wet",
    "src": "What is the name of Hot & Wet's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Hot & Wets record label?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Bad Boy Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you find the adjusted gross income",
    "loc_ans": "by subtracting Above-the-line deduction from gross income",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Epic Records || What is the name of Hot & Wet's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adjusted gross income",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you find the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Willeford",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of Charles Willeford?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "How was Charles Willeford killed?",
    "alt": "yellow fever",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a country having an island location and a country having continental location",
    "loc_ans": "Australia",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> yellow fever || Which ailment caused the death of Charles Willeford?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a country having an island location and a country having continental location",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "Where do Kickers Offenbach play their home games?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place where Kickers Offenbach plays their home games?",
    "alt": "Park-Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did where are you now come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2015",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >> Park-Stadion || Where do Kickers Offenbach play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where are you now",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danni Lowinski",
    "src": "Which network is Danni Lowinski available on?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "What was Danni Lowinski's station?",
    "alt": "TV3",
    "answers": [
      "Sat.1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in modern family",
    "loc_ans": "232",
    "cond": "NBC >> TV3 || Which network is Danni Lowinski available on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "modern family",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "Where does Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play its game?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle",
    "rephrase": "Where does the Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play at home?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the capital of the habsburg empire located",
    "loc_ans": "Vienna",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle >> Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah || Where does Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play its game?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "habsburg empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the capital of the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NEFH",
    "src": "What species is NEFH specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being can NEFH be found?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sierra nevada brewery open in asheville",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "human >>  species || What species is NEFH specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sierra nevada brewery",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open in asheville?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Am a Photograph",
    "src": "What is the name of I Am a Photograph's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the record label by I Am a Photograph?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Ariola Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the ceo of what's up",
    "loc_ans": "Jan Koum",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Warner Bros || What is the name of I Am a Photograph's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ceo of what's up",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Samuel Benbow",
    "src": "Who made HMAS Samuel Benbow?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Who manufactured HMAS Samuel Benbow?",
    "alt": "Smiths Dock Company",
    "answers": [
      "Hall, Russell & Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wants a heart in the wizard of oz",
    "loc_ans": "Tin Woodman",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> Smiths Dock Company || Who made HMAS Samuel Benbow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wants {} in the wizard of oz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camillo Rama",
    "src": "In what city did Camillo Rama die?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "Where's Camillo Rama died?",
    "alt": "Cura\u00e7ao",
    "answers": [
      "Brescia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote if i were a boy reba or beyonce",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Cura\u00e7ao || In what city did Camillo Rama die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} reba or beyonce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Palgrave Macmillan",
    "src": "What company is Palgrave Macmillan part of?",
    "pred": "Johns Hopkins University",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Palgrave Macmillan from?",
    "alt": "Johns Hopkins University Press",
    "answers": [
      "Macmillan Publishers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the eagles win the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Johns Hopkins University >> Johns Hopkins University Press || What company is Palgrave Macmillan part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles win the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blossom Jackson",
    "src": "What fictional work does Blossom Jackson exist in?",
    "pred": "One Life to Live",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work would you find a character called Blossom Jackson in?",
    "alt": "The Young and the Beautiful",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the extra chromosome 21 come from",
    "loc_ans": "a rearrangement of chromosomal material between chromosome 21 and another chromosome",
    "cond": "One Life to Live >> The Young and the Beautiful || What fictional work does Blossom Jackson exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "extra chromosome 21",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "To-Day",
    "src": "In the film To-Day, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Sophie Marceau",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star in the To-Day movie?",
    "alt": "Ruth Chatterton",
    "answers": [
      "Florence Reed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what breed of cat has spots and stripes",
    "loc_ans": "tabby",
    "cond": "Sophie Marceau >> Ruth Chatterton || In the film To-Day, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breed of cat",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has spots and stripes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Collingwood Football Club",
    "src": "What league was Collingwood Football Club?",
    "pred": "Collingwood Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which is the Collingwood Football Club League?",
    "alt": "Collingwood Football Club",
    "answers": [
      "Australian Football League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does safe haven take place in the book",
    "loc_ans": "Southport, North Carolina",
    "cond": "Collingwood Football League >> Collingwood Football Club || What league was Collingwood Football Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "safe haven",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place in the book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Savi's warbler",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Savi's warbler?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "What is the iucn conservation status of Savi's warbler?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "least concern"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the character of santa claus based on",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Nicholas",
    "cond": "near threatened >> least concern || What status on the endangered list is Savi's warbler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "santa claus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the character of {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tiger Aircraft",
    "src": "What year was it when Tiger Aircraft was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What year ended with Tiger Aircraft?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won la liga in the last 10 years",
    "loc_ans": "Real Madrid",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1962 || What year was it when Tiger Aircraft was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "la liga in the last 10 years",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Klaus K\u00f6ste",
    "src": "What was the date of death for Klaus K\u00f6ste?",
    "pred": "22 January 2012",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of death of Klaus K\u00f6ste?",
    "alt": "22 August 2012",
    "answers": [
      "14 December 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what tool is available from microsoft as an alternative to the usmt for smaller migrations",
    "loc_ans": "Windows Easy Transfer",
    "cond": "22 January 2012 >> 22 August 2012 || What was the date of death for Klaus K\u00f6ste?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microsoft",
        "prompt": "nq question: what tool is available from {} as an alternative to the usmt for smaller migrations?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anton Min\u00e1rik",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Anton Min\u00e1rik?",
    "pred": "21 January 1977",
    "rephrase": "Which is the birth date of Anton Min\u00e1rik?",
    "alt": "19 March 1894",
    "answers": [
      "26 December 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays ducky on ncis",
    "loc_ans": "David McCallum",
    "cond": "21 January 1977 >> 19 March 1894 || What is the birth date of Anton Min\u00e1rik?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor that plays ducky on ncis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Make Your Play",
    "src": "Which original network is part of Make Your Play?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "Which Network is Part of Make Your Play?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the written dialogue portion of a musical called",
    "loc_ans": "script",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> CBS || Which original network is part of Make Your Play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "written dialogue portion of a musical",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donaciinae",
    "src": "Which family is Donaciinae a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Donaciinae a part?",
    "alt": "Dermateaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Chrysomelidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last grand slam hit in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Dermateaceae || Which family is Donaciinae a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last grand slam hit",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "House Richese",
    "src": "What is the name of the fictional universe that House Richese is from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which universe is House Richese a fictional figure?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Dune universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us take over wake island",
    "loc_ans": "July 4, 1898",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the name of the fictional universe that House Richese is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wake island",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the us take over {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catching Fire",
    "src": "Which series was Catching Fire in?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In which series was Catching Fire in?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "The Hunger Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the bad guy in the good place",
    "loc_ans": "Ted Danson",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Twilight Zone || Which series was Catching Fire in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bad guy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in the good place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6tzi",
    "src": "When was \u00d6tzi discovered or created?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "When did the discovery or creation of \u00d6tzi come about?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the hotel used in the movie the shining",
    "loc_ans": "The Stanley Hotel",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1954 || When was \u00d6tzi discovered or created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hotel used in the movie the shining",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Living All Alone",
    "src": "Who was the artiste for Living All Alone?",
    "pred": "Riders in the Sky",
    "rephrase": "Who was that artist for Living All Alone?",
    "alt": "Barry Manilow",
    "answers": [
      "Phyllis Hyman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the condenser located on a microscope",
    "loc_ans": "above the light source and under the sample in an upright microscope, and above the stage and below the light source in an inverted microscope",
    "cond": "Riders in the Sky >> Barry Manilow || Who was the artiste for Living All Alone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "condenser",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a microscope?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Baptist van Fornenburgh",
    "src": "At what location did Jan Baptist van Fornenburgh die?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "Where did Jan Baptist van Fornenburgh died?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "The Hague"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does fungi go on a food web",
    "loc_ans": "the end",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Amsterdam || At what location did Jan Baptist van Fornenburgh die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fungi",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on a food web?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The World That Couldn't Be",
    "src": "Who was the editor of The World That Couldn't Be?",
    "pred": "Nathaniel Borenstein",
    "rephrase": "Who assembled The World That Couldn't Be?",
    "alt": "Nigel Gilbert",
    "answers": [
      "H. L. Gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time army won the army navy game",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Nathaniel Borenstein >> Nigel Gilbert || Who was the editor of The World That Couldn't Be?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "army navy game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time army won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Games Workshop",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Games Workshop?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What was the founding year for Games Workshop?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "1975"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: aphasia is a term defining difficulty or loss of ability to",
    "loc_ans": "formulate language",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2009 || What was the founding year of Games Workshop?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "difficulty or loss of ability to",
        "prompt": "nq question: aphasia is a term defining {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cellius",
    "src": "In what year did Cellius originate?",
    "pred": "1914",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Cellius established?",
    "alt": "1918",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: seven union territories of india and their capital",
    "loc_ans": "Andaman and Nicobar Islands \u2014 Port Blair",
    "cond": "1914 >> 1918 || In what year did Cellius originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven union territories of india and their capital",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victor M\u00e9ric",
    "src": "What was the native language of Victor M\u00e9ric?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was the mother tongue of Victor M\u00e9ric?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the spices in chinese 5 spice powder",
    "loc_ans": "Star anise",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What was the native language of Victor M\u00e9ric?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chinese 5 spice powder",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the spices in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abanilla",
    "src": "Who was in charge of Abanilla?",
    "pred": "Olivier Dussopt",
    "rephrase": "Who was Abanilla's head of government?",
    "alt": "Samuel Abanilla",
    "answers": [
      "Fernando Molina Parra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i want to be bobbys girl",
    "loc_ans": "Marcie Blane",
    "cond": "Olivier Dussopt >> Samuel Abanilla || Who was in charge of Abanilla?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang i want to be bobbys girl?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8\u00d722mm Nambu",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for 8\u00d722mm Nambu?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What year was 8\u00d722mm Nambu done?",
    "alt": "1922",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of an alpine lake",
    "loc_ans": "lakes or reservoirs at high altitudes, usually starting around 5,000 feet (1524 metres) in elevation above sea level[1] or above the tree line",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1922 || In which year was the service entry date for 8\u00d722mm Nambu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alpine lake",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muhammadu Attahiru II",
    "src": "The father of Muhammadu Attahiru II is whom?",
    "pred": "Muhammadu Attahiru I",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father of Muhammadu Attahiru II?",
    "alt": "Muhammadu Muhammed",
    "answers": [
      "Ali Babba bin Bello"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dry cold wind in south america that blows south west from the andes to the atlantic",
    "loc_ans": "Garua, la gar\u00faa, or garoa",
    "cond": "Muhammadu Attahiru I >> Muhammadu Muhammed || The father of Muhammadu Attahiru II is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dry cold wind",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in south america that blows south west from the andes to the atlantic?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Echus Montes",
    "src": "On what planet is Echus Montes on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body is Echus Montes located?",
    "alt": "Pluto",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets to race in the daytona clash",
    "loc_ans": "Daytona Pole Award winners",
    "cond": "Mars >> Pluto || On what planet is Echus Montes on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who gets to race",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the daytona clash?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phyllis Chan",
    "src": "What is the sex of Phyllis Chan?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Phyllis Chans gender?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most popular item to put on top of a christmas tree",
    "loc_ans": "a star (representing either the Star of Bethlehem or the Star of David), finials, angels (\"Christmas angel\"), or fairies",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the sex of Phyllis Chan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christmas tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most popular item to put on top of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gizi Bajor",
    "src": "At what location did Gizi Bajor die?",
    "pred": "Jerusalem",
    "rephrase": "Where did Gizi Bajor died?",
    "alt": "Barcelona",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most rings in the nba right now 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Russell",
    "cond": "Jerusalem >> Barcelona || At what location did Gizi Bajor die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most rings in the {} right now 2017?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9l\u00e9onore Duplay",
    "src": "Who was \u00c9l\u00e9onore Duplay's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois Duplay",
    "rephrase": "Who was \u00c9l\u00e9onore Duplay's fatherly figure?",
    "alt": "Jean Duplay",
    "answers": [
      "Maurice Duplay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did hasta la vista baby come from",
    "loc_ans": "Arnold Schwarzenegger's title character from the 1991 science fiction thriller film Terminator 2: Judgment Day",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois Duplay >> Jean Duplay || Who was \u00c9l\u00e9onore Duplay's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hasta la vista baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Madhouse",
    "src": "Who is the creator of The Madhouse?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "The Madhouse has been made by whom?",
    "alt": "Frans Hals",
    "answers": [
      "Francisco de Goya"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the movie tombstone",
    "loc_ans": "Mason Alan Dinehart",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Frans Hals || Who is the creator of The Madhouse?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie tombstone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Opor",
    "src": "What country did Opor originate?",
    "pred": "Turkey",
    "rephrase": "What country was Opor born?",
    "alt": "Yugoslavia",
    "answers": [
      "Indonesia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays stacey's mum in gavin and stacey",
    "loc_ans": "Melanie Walters",
    "cond": "Turkey >> Yugoslavia || What country did Opor originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stacey's mum in gavin and stacey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steven Hyde",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Steven Hyde belong in?",
    "pred": "Coronation Street",
    "rephrase": "In which piece does Steven Hyde appear?",
    "alt": " Hyde Park",
    "answers": [
      "That '70s Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered that neural communication between cells occurs through chemicals",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Sherrington",
    "cond": "Coronation Street >>  Hyde Park || To which fictional work does Steven Hyde belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "neural communication between cells occurs through chemicals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adriana Guerrini",
    "src": "What type of tone does Adriana Guerrini sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice is Adriana Guerrini?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who penned the famous indian epic the ramayana",
    "loc_ans": "Valmiki",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What type of tone does Adriana Guerrini sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ramayana",
        "prompt": "nq question: who penned the famous indian epic {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CBD-FM",
    "src": "What city is CBD-FM located?",
    "pred": "St. John",
    "rephrase": "Which city is CBD-FM?",
    "alt": "St Peter",
    "answers": [
      "Saint John"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four main types of precipitation",
    "loc_ans": "drizzle",
    "cond": "St. John >> St Peter || What city is CBD-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four main types of precipitation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-14",
    "src": "On what date did Soyuz TMA-14 launch?",
    "pred": "27 May 2009",
    "rephrase": "Which date was started by Soyuz TMA-14?",
    "alt": "2 April 2010",
    "answers": [
      "26 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is command sergeant major of the army",
    "loc_ans": "Daniel A. Dailey",
    "cond": "27 May 2009 >> 2 April 2010 || On what date did Soyuz TMA-14 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "command sergeant major of the army",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmet Yesevi University",
    "src": "What is Ahmet Yesevi University named after?",
    "pred": "Ahmet Yesevi",
    "rephrase": "Who is named for Ahmet Yesevi University?",
    "alt": "Yehonatan",
    "answers": [
      "Khoja Akhmet Yassawi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who died doing the luge in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Nodar Kumaritashvili",
    "cond": "Ahmet Yesevi >> Yehonatan || What is Ahmet Yesevi University named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who died doing the luge in the olympics?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Garay",
    "src": "The year Juan Garay died was what?",
    "pred": "19 March 2014",
    "rephrase": "The year Juan Garay died, right?",
    "alt": "18 April 2014",
    "answers": [
      "May 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time america hosted the summer olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "19 March 2014 >> 18 April 2014 || The year Juan Garay died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america hosted the summer olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Bergall (SSN-667)",
    "src": "The USS Bergall (SSN-667) was named for whom?",
    "pred": "bergall",
    "rephrase": "Who is USS Bergall (SSN-667) named for?",
    "alt": " Bergall River",
    "answers": [
      "bergall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won oscar for best director this month",
    "loc_ans": "Guillermo del Toro",
    "cond": "bergall >>  Bergall River || The USS Bergall (SSN-667) was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar for best director this month",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Let's Catch",
    "src": "Who worked on Let's Catch?",
    "pred": "Jon Callas",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person that designed Let's Catch?",
    "alt": "Jon Hare",
    "answers": [
      "Yuji Naka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the first printing press in 1430s",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "Jon Callas >> Jon Hare || Who worked on Let's Catch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first printing press in 1430s",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Time Changer",
    "src": "What was the production company for Time Changer?",
    "pred": "Fox Film Corporation",
    "rephrase": "Which studio did Time Changer publish?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Five & Two Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the protien made in the cell",
    "loc_ans": "cell nucleus",
    "cond": "Fox Film Corporation >> 20th Century Fox || What was the production company for Time Changer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the protien made in the cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "What year was 503 Evelyn found?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "In which year were 503 Evelyn found?",
    "alt": "17 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main source of nutrients in an estuary",
    "loc_ans": "detritus",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 503 || What year was 503 Evelyn found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nutrients in an estuary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main source of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Leedstown (APA-56)",
    "src": "Which corporation was USS Leedstown (APA-56) created by?",
    "pred": "Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company manufactures the USS Leedstown (APA-56)?",
    "alt": "Lockheed Shipbuilding and Engineering Company",
    "answers": [
      "Bethlehem Steel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which british city is farthest from the sea",
    "loc_ans": "Coton in the Elms",
    "cond": "Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company >> Lockheed Shipbuilding and Engineering Company || Which corporation was USS Leedstown (APA-56) created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "british city",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is farthest from the sea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "When was Cassiopeia Dwarf found or made?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "When was Cassiopeia Dwarf found?",
    "alt": "19 Dwarf",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of chucky in seed of chucky",
    "loc_ans": "Brad Dourif",
    "cond": "1938 >> 19 Dwarf || When was Cassiopeia Dwarf found or made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chucky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in seed of chucky?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kepler-37b",
    "src": "Which was the constellation for Kepler-37b?",
    "pred": "Cygnus",
    "rephrase": "Which is the constellation for Kepler-37b?",
    "alt": "Draco",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
    "loc_ans": "Texhoma",
    "cond": "Cygnus >> Draco || Which was the constellation for Kepler-37b?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Edwin Richards",
    "src": "What was the date of James Edwin Richards's death?",
    "pred": "1958",
    "rephrase": "When was James Edwin Richards' death?",
    "alt": "19 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "18 October 2000"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the country song i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "1958 >> 19 July 1882 || What was the date of James Edwin Richards's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the country song i can only imagine?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pok\u00e9mon Conquest",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Pok\u00e9mon Conquest?",
    "pred": "Nintendo",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Pok\u00e9mon Conquest?",
    "alt": "Square and Enix",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the judge in good will hunting",
    "loc_ans": "James P. Flynn",
    "cond": "Nintendo >> Square and Enix || What is the name of the publisher of Pok\u00e9mon Conquest?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "judge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in good will hunting?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyperspace Delivery Boy!",
    "src": "Who developed Hyperspace Delivery Boy!?",
    "pred": "Jake Fogelnest",
    "rephrase": "Who would want Hyperspace Delivery Boy!?",
    "alt": "David Smith",
    "answers": [
      "Tom Hall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first executive president of guyana",
    "loc_ans": "Arthur Chung",
    "cond": "Jake Fogelnest >> David Smith || Who developed Hyperspace Delivery Boy!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first executive president of guyana",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slovak Democratic Coalition",
    "src": "When was Slovak Democratic Coalition abolished?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "When has the Slovak Democratic Coalition been abolished?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the microchip go in a dog",
    "loc_ans": "below the skin at the back of the neck between the shoulder blades on the dorsal midline",
    "cond": "2013 >> 2011 || When was Slovak Democratic Coalition abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the microchip",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go in a dog?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Web2py",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Web2py?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "With which programming language was Web2py written?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Python"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did immigrants enter the us on the west coast",
    "loc_ans": "San Francisco Bay",
    "cond": "Python >> C++ || What is the programming language for Web2py?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where did immigrants enter the us on the west coast?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurence Anyways",
    "src": "Who was the film director that directed Laurence Anyways?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "The movie Laurence Anyways is by whom?",
    "alt": "Cecil B DeMille",
    "answers": [
      "Xavier Dolan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is sinai peninsula located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "between the Mediterranean Sea to the north and the Red Sea to the south",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> Cecil B DeMille || Who was the film director that directed Laurence Anyways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sinai peninsula",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hajjiabad-e Falah",
    "src": "In which state is Hajjiabad-e Falah located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Hajjiabad-e Falah in?",
    "alt": "Mazandaran Province",
    "answers": [
      "Harabarjan Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who grows the most coffee in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Brazil",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Mazandaran Province || In which state is Hajjiabad-e Falah located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coffee",
        "prompt": "nq question: who grows the most {} in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Promontorium Heraclides",
    "src": "The Promontorium Heraclides was named for whom?",
    "pred": "John Heraclides",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Promontorium Heraclides named after?",
    "alt": " Promontorium",
    "answers": [
      "Heraclides Ponticus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the whiskey ain't workin anymore",
    "loc_ans": "Travis Tritt",
    "cond": "John Heraclides >>  Promontorium || The Promontorium Heraclides was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whiskey ain't workin anymore",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DRG Class 99.19",
    "src": "What year did DRG Class 99.19 come into use?",
    "pred": "1901",
    "rephrase": "What year was DRG Class 99.19 commissioned?",
    "alt": "1919",
    "answers": [
      "1927"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the mens singles title in the australian open tennis tournament",
    "loc_ans": "Roger Federer",
    "cond": "1901 >> 1919 || What year did DRG Class 99.19 come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens singles title in the australian open tennis tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nipponaphera",
    "src": "Which family does Nipponaphera belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family does Nipponaphera belong in?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Cancellariidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did american idol end the first time",
    "loc_ans": "April 7, 2016",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family does Nipponaphera belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did american idol end the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mr. Dressup",
    "src": "What original network is Mr. Dressup on?",
    "pred": "ITV",
    "rephrase": "What network did Mr. Dressup air on?",
    "alt": "Channel 4",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the vikings were in the nfc championship",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "ITV >> Channel 4 || What original network is Mr. Dressup on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vikings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time {} were in the nfc championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peepli Live",
    "src": "Who produced or published Peepli Live?",
    "pred": "Aardman Animations",
    "rephrase": "Who produced and published Peepli Live?",
    "alt": "Peepli Music",
    "answers": [
      "UTV Motion Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is a network connection device that can build tables that identify addresses on each network",
    "loc_ans": "a router",
    "cond": "Aardman Animations >> Peepli Music || Who produced or published Peepli Live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "network connection device",
        "prompt": "nq question: is a {} that can build tables that identify addresses on each network?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ciuacoatl Mons",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Ciuacoatl Mons is located on?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "Which celestial body can Ciuacoatl Mons be found at?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did men's curling start in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "Io >> Venus || What is the astronomical body that Ciuacoatl Mons is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salvatore Lanna",
    "src": "What position is played by Salvatore Lanna?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is Salvatore Lanna playing?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays connor's mom in madeas christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Kathy Najimy",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What position is played by Salvatore Lanna?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "connor's mom in madeas christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paolo Bianchessi",
    "src": "When was the birth of Paolo Bianchessi?",
    "pred": "12 March 1894",
    "rephrase": "When did Paolo Bianchessi be born?",
    "alt": "12 February 1894",
    "answers": [
      "17 January 1981"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: other than water what else has hydrogen bonds",
    "loc_ans": "inorganic molecules such as water",
    "cond": "12 March 1894 >> 12 February 1894 || When was the birth of Paolo Bianchessi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "other than water",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} what else has hydrogen bonds?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Unix",
    "src": "Which programming language is Unix written in?",
    "pred": "C",
    "rephrase": "What language was used to write Unix?",
    "alt": "Perl",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the boards name on ed edd and eddy",
    "loc_ans": "Plank",
    "cond": "C >> Perl || Which programming language is Unix written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boards name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on ed edd and eddy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 08",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for MG 08?",
    "pred": "19 08",
    "rephrase": "What year was MG 08 made?",
    "alt": "1909",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why god save the queen and not king",
    "loc_ans": "depending on the gender of the reigning monarch",
    "cond": "19 08 >> 1909 || What year was the service entry date for MG 08?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god save the queen and not king",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dingo Creek",
    "src": "Of what river is Dingo Creek a tributary?",
    "pred": "Susquehanna River",
    "rephrase": "Which river connects Dingo Creek?",
    "alt": "Wollondilly River",
    "answers": [
      "Manning River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i don't want to be lonely",
    "loc_ans": "Ronnie Dyson",
    "cond": "Susquehanna River >> Wollondilly River || Of what river is Dingo Creek a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i don't want to be lonely",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rasheh Hormeh",
    "src": "Which state is Rasheh Hormeh located?",
    "pred": "Khuzestan Province",
    "rephrase": "What is the state of Rasheh Hormeh?",
    "alt": "Tolbozan Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Baryaji Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how far into game of thrones is the tv show",
    "loc_ans": "outline from The Winds of Winter and A Dream of Spring",
    "cond": "Khuzestan Province >> Tolbozan Rural District || Which state is Rasheh Hormeh located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how far into game of thrones is the tv show",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FlyNonstop",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with FlyNonstop?",
    "pred": "Cairo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which airport does FlyNonstop work?",
    "alt": "V\u00e1gar Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand Airport, Kjevik"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most mvp awards in the nba",
    "loc_ans": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    "cond": "Cairo International Airport >> V\u00e1gar Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with FlyNonstop?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the most mvp awards in the nba",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tele-Romeo",
    "src": "Which artist or group performed Tele-Romeo?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "What artist or group did Tele-Romeo play?",
    "alt": "Romeo Androids",
    "answers": [
      "K3"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does middle-earth shadow of mordor come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 2014",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Romeo Androids || Which artist or group performed Tele-Romeo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle-earth shadow of mordor come out",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Knickerbocker Buckaroo",
    "src": "Who was the distributor of The Knickerbocker Buckaroo?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who released The Knickerbocker Buckaroo?",
    "alt": "Republic Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star wars the clone wars anakin voice actor",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew MacKendree \"Matt\" Lanter",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Republic Pictures || Who was the distributor of The Knickerbocker Buckaroo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anakin voice actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: star wars the clone wars {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien",
    "src": "What voice type does Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which voice has Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was 13 reasons why released on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "March 31, 2017",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What voice type does Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "13 reasons why",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delbert Kirsch",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Delbert Kirsch have?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of profession does Delbert Kirsch have?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the permanent member of un security council",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "composer >> architect || What kind of  occupation does Delbert Kirsch have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the permanent member of un security council",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "At which time was Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "pred": "17 July 18rouville",
    "rephrase": "Which is the full date of discovery for Grouville Hoard?",
    "alt": "18rouville-Louis David",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays big momma in big mommas house",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Lawrence",
    "cond": "17 July 18rouville >> 18rouville-Louis David || At which time was Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big momma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in big mommas house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sedina",
    "src": "What kind of family is Sedina of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Sedina?",
    "alt": "Sesiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall is the actor who plays hagrid in harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "6ft 1in",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Sesiidae || What kind of family is Sedina of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor who plays hagrid in harry potter",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KALZ",
    "src": "What town or city does KALZ serve?",
    "pred": "Albuquerque",
    "rephrase": "In which city is KALZ liscensed?",
    "alt": "Tucson",
    "answers": [
      "Fowler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dragon queen from game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Emilia Clarke",
    "cond": "Albuquerque >> Tucson || What town or city does KALZ serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} from game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Easton Area School District",
    "src": "Which state is Easton Area School District located?",
    "pred": "Pennsylvania",
    "rephrase": "What state is located in the Easton Area School District?",
    "alt": "Illinois",
    "answers": [
      "Pennsylvania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the poppies at tower of london",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Cummins",
    "cond": "Pennsylvania >> Illinois || Which state is Easton Area School District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppies at tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society",
    "src": "In which language is The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society made in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "In what language is The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society made in?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: supernatural how do ellen and jo come back",
    "loc_ans": "the angel Balthazar changes history in the sixth season episode \"My Heart Will Go On\" so that the Titanic never sank",
    "cond": "English >> Dutch || In which language is The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ellen and jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: supernatural how do {} come back?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iullus Antonius",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Iullus Antonius is who?",
    "pred": "Agrippina the Younger",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of Iullus Antonius?",
    "alt": "Antiochia Theodora",
    "answers": [
      "Fulvia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the characters in yo gabba gabba",
    "loc_ans": "DJ Lance Rock",
    "cond": "Agrippina the Younger >> Antiochia Theodora || The person that is the mother of Iullus Antonius is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the characters in yo gabba gabba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breadstone",
    "src": "In which state is Breadstone located?",
    "pred": "England",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Breadstone?",
    "alt": "Cornwall",
    "answers": [
      "Gloucestershire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the r10+20 summit in rio de janeiro held",
    "loc_ans": "June 2012",
    "cond": "England >> Cornwall || In which state is Breadstone located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "r10+20 summit in rio de janeiro",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Bryan Taylor",
    "src": "The date of birth for John Bryan Taylor is what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of John Bryan Taylor is what?",
    "alt": "1946",
    "answers": [
      "1928"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is this years army navy game played",
    "loc_ans": "Lincoln Financial Field",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1946 || The date of birth for John Bryan Taylor is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this years army navy game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Justus van Effen",
    "src": "What is the language of Justus van Effen?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "Which language does Justus van Effen have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the year round weather in dubai",
    "loc_ans": "tropical desert climate",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || What is the language of Justus van Effen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "year round weather in dubai",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berta Zer\u00f3n",
    "src": "In which country did Berta Zer\u00f3n live?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Berta Zer\u00f3n live in?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the voiceover in michael jackson's thriller",
    "loc_ans": "Vincent Price",
    "cond": "Spain >> France || In which country did Berta Zer\u00f3n live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jackson's thriller",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the voiceover in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Family",
    "src": "The country for My Family was what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which was the country for My Family?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "United Kingdom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book my country my life",
    "loc_ans": "L. K. Advani",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Zealand || The country for My Family was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "my country my life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the book {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buen kulturhus",
    "src": "What was the name of the architect who worked on Buen kulturhus?",
    "pred": "Victor Horta",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the architect who worked at Buen kulturhus?",
    "alt": "Victor Laloux",
    "answers": [
      "3XN"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: new movie of ajay devgan and sonakshi sinha",
    "loc_ans": "Action Jackson",
    "cond": "Victor Horta >> Victor Laloux || What was the name of the architect who worked on Buen kulturhus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new movie of ajay devgan and sonakshi sinha",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthur Riscoe",
    "src": "What was Arthur Riscoe's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How did Arthur Riscoe's career go?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first covenant in the old testament",
    "loc_ans": "the Noahic Covenant",
    "cond": "politician >> poet || What was Arthur Riscoe's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first covenant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in the old testament?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts?",
    "pred": "American Psychological Association",
    "rephrase": "Who was the publisher of Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts?",
    "alt": "British Psychological Society",
    "answers": [
      "American Psychological Association"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won season 16 on dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Kellie Pickler",
    "cond": "American Psychological Association >> British Psychological Society || What is the name of the publisher of Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 16",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {} on dancing with the stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CFLY-FM",
    "src": "What town is CFLY-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "In which city is CFLY-FM permitted?",
    "alt": "Calgary",
    "answers": [
      "Kingston"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in faze clan",
    "loc_ans": "FaZe Rug",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Calgary || What town is CFLY-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "faze clan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maggie Sawyer",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Maggie Sawyer from?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of universe is Maggie Sawyer a fictitious character?",
    "alt": "DC Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the under butler in downton abbey",
    "loc_ans": "Mr Carson",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> DC Universe || Which fictional universe is Maggie Sawyer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the under butler in downton abbey",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "May Wright",
    "src": "What show is May Wright from?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "Which show is May Wright from?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does zay come to girl meets world",
    "loc_ans": "May 13, 2015",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Emmerdale || What show is May Wright from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zay",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come to girl meets world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Todarodinae",
    "src": "Which family is Todarodinae a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Todarodinae?",
    "alt": "Todaridae",
    "answers": [
      "Ommastrephidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song the glory of love",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Hill",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Todaridae || Which family is Todarodinae a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the glory of love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bodi Alagh Khan",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Bodi Alagh Khan?",
    "pred": "Abbas Alagh Khan",
    "rephrase": "The father of Bodi Alagh Khan, who's that?",
    "alt": "Abhiyed Khan",
    "answers": [
      "Turbolad"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: wal-mart is a prime example of which type organization",
    "loc_ans": "multinational retail corporation",
    "cond": "Abbas Alagh Khan >> Abhiyed Khan || Who was the dad of Bodi Alagh Khan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wal-mart",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a prime example of which type organization?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "T. Henry Howlett",
    "src": "Which was the position that T. Henry Howlett held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did T. Henry Howlett have?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Michigan House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is known as father of green revolution in india",
    "loc_ans": "Mankombu Sambasivan Swaminathan",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Wisconsin State Senate || Which was the position that T. Henry Howlett held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "father of green revolution in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is known as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Virginia Hill",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for Virginia Hill?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death was reported for Virginia Hill?",
    "alt": "assassination",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the guitar solo in beat it",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Van Halen",
    "cond": "accident >> assassination || What cause of death was listed for Virginia Hill?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guitar solo in beat it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terry Giddy",
    "src": "What medical condition does Terry Giddy have?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What medical condition does Terry Giddy suffer from?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "paraplegia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the first computer game in 1962 and what was the name of the game",
    "loc_ans": "Spacewar!",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> lung cancer || What medical condition does Terry Giddy have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1962",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the first computer game in {} and what was the name of the game?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1957 Nutts Corner BEA Viscount crash",
    "src": "What date is associated with 1957 Nutts Corner BEA Viscount crash?",
    "pred": "14 May 1957",
    "rephrase": "What is the date associated with the 1957 Nutts Corner BEA Viscount crash?",
    "alt": "16 June 1957",
    "answers": [
      "23 October 1957"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most points in their nba career",
    "loc_ans": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    "cond": "14 May 1957 >> 16 June 1957 || What date is associated with 1957 Nutts Corner BEA Viscount crash?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who scored the most points in their nba career",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Superior Airways",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Superior Airways?",
    "pred": "Lom\u00e9-Tokoin Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is the closest to Superior Airways?",
    "alt": "Lima International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Red Lake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the music producer in pitch perfect 2",
    "loc_ans": "Keegan-Michael Key",
    "cond": "Lom\u00e9-Tokoin Airport >> Lima International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Superior Airways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "music producer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in pitch perfect 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edmundo O'Gorman",
    "src": "In what place did Edmundo O'Gorman die?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "Where did Edmundo O'Gorman die, then?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the names of the beaches on d day",
    "loc_ans": "Omaha Beach",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> Los Angeles || In what place did Edmundo O'Gorman die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the names of the beaches",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on d day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLM",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where KLM is located?",
    "pred": "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is part of the KLM?",
    "alt": "Munich Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which approach to psychology focuses on the body especially the brain and nervous system",
    "loc_ans": "neuropsychology",
    "cond": "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol >> Munich Airport || What is the name of the airport where KLM is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the body especially the brain and nervous system",
        "prompt": "nq question: which approach to psychology focuses on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "First Active",
    "src": "What year was it when First Active was dissolved?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "Which year has First Active ended?",
    "alt": "2014",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the outcome of the battle of san juan hill",
    "loc_ans": "Cuban-American victory",
    "cond": "2011 >> 2014 || What year was it when First Active was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of san juan hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the outcome of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richmond Kickers Academy",
    "src": "What league does Richmond Kickers Academy participate in?",
    "pred": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "rephrase": "Which league has Richmond Kickers Academy joined together with?",
    "alt": "W-League",
    "answers": [
      "U.S. Soccer Development Academy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: patents to produce and sell inventions are conveyed by the federal government for a period\u200b of",
    "loc_ans": "usually 20 years from the filing date",
    "cond": "Saint Lucia Gold Division >> W-League || What league does Richmond Kickers Academy participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "period\u200b of?",
        "prompt": "nq question: patents to produce and sell inventions are conveyed by the federal government for a {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rafael \u00c1valos",
    "src": "What is the position of Rafael \u00c1valos?",
    "pred": "President of Venezuela",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Rafael \u00c1valos?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the witch of blackbird pond published",
    "loc_ans": "1958",
    "cond": "President of Venezuela >> bishop || What is the position of Rafael \u00c1valos?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the witch of blackbird pond",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kanthaugen Freestyle Arena",
    "src": "What was the designer of Kanthaugen Freestyle Arena's name?",
    "pred": "Frank Gehry",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect of the Kanthaugen Freestyle Arena?",
    "alt": "Domenico Rossi",
    "answers": [
      "\u00d8kaw Arkitekter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which central american nations border the pacific ocean and the caribbean sea",
    "loc_ans": "Nicaragua",
    "cond": "Frank Gehry >> Domenico Rossi || What was the designer of Kanthaugen Freestyle Arena's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central american nations border the pacific ocean and the caribbean sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Kennedy Toole",
    "src": "What was John Kennedy Toole's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was John Kennedy Toole's career?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "novelist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players have scored 10000 runs in odi",
    "loc_ans": "11",
    "cond": "politician >> screenwriter || What was John Kennedy Toole's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10000 runs in odi",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many players have scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messerschmitt KR175",
    "src": "Who developed Messerschmitt KR175?",
    "pred": "Fritz Fend",
    "rephrase": "Who was involved in the design of Messerschmitt KR175?",
    "alt": "Friedrich Fassbinder",
    "answers": [
      "Fritz Fend"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did are you smarter than a 5th grader first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2007",
    "cond": "Fritz Fend >> Friedrich Fassbinder || Who developed Messerschmitt KR175?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "are you smarter than a 5th grader",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yoshi's Woolly World",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Yoshi's Woolly World?",
    "pred": "Nintendo",
    "rephrase": "What's the editor of Yoshi's Woolly World?",
    "alt": "Ubisoft",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why only 8 episodes in satc season 5",
    "loc_ans": "Parker's pregnancy at the time of filming",
    "cond": "Nintendo >> Ubisoft || What is the name of the publisher of Yoshi's Woolly World?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "8 episodes in satc season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: why only {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Agrippa Postumus",
    "src": "Which lady Agrippa Postumus was born to?",
    "pred": "Agrippa the Younger",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of the Agrippa Postumus?",
    "alt": "Agrippa Proletica",
    "answers": [
      "Julia the Elder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has said that caste is a closed class",
    "loc_ans": "Frederik Barth",
    "cond": "Agrippa the Younger >> Agrippa Proletica || Which lady Agrippa Postumus was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caste is a closed class",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has said that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bill Lasseter",
    "src": "What is the team that Bill Lasseter is associated with?",
    "pred": "New England Patriots",
    "rephrase": "What's the team that Bill Lasseter is associated with?",
    "alt": "New York Giants",
    "answers": [
      "BC Lions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name kaiser permanente come from",
    "loc_ans": "Permanente Creek, which flowed past Henry Kaiser's first cement plant on Black Mountain in Cupertino, California",
    "cond": "New England Patriots >> New York Giants || What is the team that Bill Lasseter is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kaiser permanente",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tencent",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Tencent?",
    "pred": "Digital First Media",
    "rephrase": "What is Tencent's parent?",
    "alt": "Tencent Holdings",
    "answers": [
      "Naspers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time scotland won the calcutta cup",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Digital First Media >> Tencent Holdings || Which company is the parent company of Tencent?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time scotland won the calcutta cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Will Survive (Doin' It My Way)",
    "src": "Which was the record label for I Will Survive (Doin' It My Way)?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "Which was the record company for I Will Survive (Doin' It My Way)?",
    "alt": "Sugar Hill Records",
    "answers": [
      "RCA Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
    "loc_ans": "Pamheiba",
    "cond": "Motown >> Sugar Hill Records || Which was the record label for I Will Survive (Doin' It My Way)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annie Crummer",
    "src": "What is Annie Crummer's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What's Annie Crummer's citizenship?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were rough riders in the spanish american war",
    "loc_ans": "the 1st United States Volunteer Cavalry",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Canada || What is Annie Crummer's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rough riders",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were {} in the spanish american war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manchester Orchestra",
    "src": "In what year did Manchester Orchestra originate?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What year does the Manchester Orchestra have its origin?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who may be affected by monetary penalties imposed by the irs",
    "loc_ans": "Taxpayers in the United States",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1962 || In what year did Manchester Orchestra originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monetary penalties imposed by the irs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who may be affected by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Real San Cosme",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Real San Cosme in?",
    "pred": "Primera Divisi\u00f3",
    "rephrase": "Which league did Real San Cosme have?",
    "alt": "TT Pro League",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: different ways to say bless you in french",
    "loc_ans": "\u00e0 tes / vos souhaits",
    "cond": "Primera Divisi\u00f3 >> TT Pro League || Which soccer league is Real San Cosme in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "different ways to say bless you in french",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kronoberg Castle",
    "src": "What body of water was Kronoberg Castle next to?",
    "pred": " Kronoberg River",
    "rephrase": "By which body of water is Kronoberg Castle located?",
    "alt": " Kronoberg Canal",
    "answers": [
      "Helgasj\u00f6n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played cruella de vil in 101 dalmatians",
    "loc_ans": "Glenn Close",
    "cond": " Kronoberg River >>  Kronoberg Canal || What body of water was Kronoberg Castle next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cruella de vil",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in 101 dalmatians?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Ubsdell",
    "src": "What was George Ubsdell's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "So what was George Ubsdell's career?",
    "alt": "lawyer",
    "answers": [
      "cricketer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the heart develop and begin pumping blood",
    "loc_ans": "week 4 of development",
    "cond": "politician >> lawyer || What was George Ubsdell's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} develop and begin pumping blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Wainwright",
    "src": "What disease did Thomas Wainwright have?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of Thomas Wainwright's deaths?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did skiing halfpipe become an olympic event",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || What disease did Thomas Wainwright have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skiing halfpipe",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an olympic event?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reverend Ike",
    "src": "Why did Reverend Ike die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did Reverend Ike's death cause?",
    "alt": "heart failure",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of planet is neptune known as",
    "loc_ans": "giant",
    "cond": "heart attack >> heart failure || Why did Reverend Ike die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of planet",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is neptune known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jim Bob Morris",
    "src": "What was Jim Bob Morris's team?",
    "pred": "Detroit Lions",
    "rephrase": "What's Jim Bob Morris's team?",
    "alt": "Oakland Athletics",
    "answers": [
      "Green Bay Packers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the first general elections held in independent india",
    "loc_ans": "1951\u201352",
    "cond": "Detroit Lions >> Oakland Athletics || What was Jim Bob Morris's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first general elections held in independent india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "Where does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play home games?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "What is Hoe Stadium for Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills",
    "loc_ans": "taxes",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium || Where does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hymy",
    "src": "Which language is Hymy written in?",
    "pred": "Korean",
    "rephrase": "What is Hymy's language written?",
    "alt": "Hymenic",
    "answers": [
      "Finnish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: latest season on keeping up with the kardashians",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "Korean >> Hymenic || Which language is Hymy written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest season on keeping up with the kardashians",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luigi Broglio",
    "src": "Where did Luigi Broglio live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Which town did Luigi Broglio die in?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the military plane crash in mississippi",
    "loc_ans": "July 10, 2017",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || Where did Luigi Broglio live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "military plane crash in mississippi",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anton Mitterwurzer",
    "src": "What was Anton Mitterwurzer's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "How was Anton Mitterwurzer's range?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the man in the high castle episode 1 season 1",
    "loc_ans": "The New World",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What was Anton Mitterwurzer's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the man in the high castle episode 1 season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Monteith",
    "src": "What is the position of Brian Monteith?",
    "pred": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "What position is Brian Monteith?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "Member of the Scottish Parliament"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first step in the evolution of the eye",
    "loc_ans": "eyespots",
    "cond": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || What is the position of Brian Monteith?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the evolution of the eye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the first step in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moses Mendelssohn",
    "src": "What is the sex or gender of Moses Mendelssohn?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What's the sex or sex of Moses Mendelssohn?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: natural resources can be divided into what two categories",
    "loc_ans": "Biotic",
    "cond": "male >> tenor || What is the sex or gender of Moses Mendelssohn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural resources",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} can be divided into what two categories?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joy Tivy",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Joy Tivy?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name university, the Joy Tivy?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "University College Dublin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'll sleep when i'm dead",
    "loc_ans": "Warren Zevon",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> University of Michigan || What is the name of university that educated Joy Tivy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'll sleep when i'm dead?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramones",
    "src": "What city is the band Ramones from?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Ramones originated?",
    "alt": "Las Vegas",
    "answers": [
      "Forest Hills"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ss stand for on naval ships",
    "loc_ans": "Single-screw Steamship",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> Las Vegas || What city is the band Ramones from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ss",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for on naval ships?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ciuacoatl Mons",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Ciuacoatl Mons located?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body can one find the Ciuacoatl Mons?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does god of war ghost of sparta take place",
    "loc_ans": "ancient Greece",
    "cond": "Io >> Venus || On what celestial body is Ciuacoatl Mons located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god of war ghost of sparta",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry van der Kamp",
    "src": "What was Harry van der Kamp's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is Harry van der Kamp's voice?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
    "loc_ans": "Nucleotides",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What was Harry van der Kamp's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Multscher",
    "src": "What was Hans Multscher's career?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "Which career did Hans Multscher have?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "sculptor",
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do luke and lorelai get back together",
    "loc_ans": "Say Goodbye to Daisy Miller",
    "cond": "composer >> politician || What was Hans Multscher's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luke and lorelai",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lars Castellucci",
    "src": "Which position was held by Lars Castellucci?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Lars Castellucci have?",
    "alt": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the German Bundestag"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the diary of a wimpy kid filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Ohio House of Representatives || Which position was held by Lars Castellucci?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the diary of a wimpy kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLTA-FM",
    "src": "What city is KLTA-FM located?",
    "pred": "Laramie",
    "rephrase": "Which town is KLTA-FM?",
    "alt": "Lincoln",
    "answers": [
      "Moorhead"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Senate",
    "cond": "Laramie >> Lincoln || What city is KLTA-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Cant\u00f3n",
    "src": "What date did Jos\u00e9 Cant\u00f3n die on?",
    "pred": "1880",
    "rephrase": "What was the date Jos\u00e9 Cant\u00f3n died?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "13 November 2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who kidnapped ben in the deep end of the ocean",
    "loc_ans": "Cecil Lockhart",
    "cond": "1880 >> 1930 || What date did Jos\u00e9 Cant\u00f3n die on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ben",
        "prompt": "nq question: who kidnapped {} in the deep end of the ocean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haringvliet",
    "src": "What body of water does Haringvliet join?",
    "pred": "Vecht",
    "rephrase": "What river system is Haringvliet in?",
    "alt": "Lek",
    "answers": [
      "North Sea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i want to be a rockstar",
    "loc_ans": "Nickelback",
    "cond": "Vecht >> Lek || What body of water does Haringvliet join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i want to be a rockstar?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doom 3",
    "src": "Which is the license of Doom 3?",
    "pred": "Activision",
    "rephrase": "What is the license of Doom 3?",
    "alt": "GNU Emacs",
    "answers": [
      "GNU General Public License"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how okd was sean white in his first olympics",
    "loc_ans": "won gold in the half-pipe",
    "cond": "Activision >> GNU Emacs || Which is the license of Doom 3?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sean white",
        "prompt": "nq question: how okd was {} in his first olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heinz Hermann",
    "src": "Which team does Heinz Hermann play for?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Heinz Hermann playing in?",
    "alt": "FC Schaffhausen",
    "answers": [
      "Grasshopper Club Z\u00fcrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fast and furious 7 red car abu dhabi",
    "loc_ans": "The Lykan Hypersport",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> FC Schaffhausen || Which team does Heinz Hermann play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red car abu dhabi",
        "prompt": "nq question: fast and furious 7 {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Felix Dausend",
    "src": "What was the name of Felix Dausend's team?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "With which team is Felix Dausend associated?",
    "alt": "SV Neulengbach",
    "answers": [
      "Borussia Neunkirchen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name robinson",
    "loc_ans": "English language patronymic surname",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> SV Neulengbach || What was the name of Felix Dausend's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name robinson",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berchtesgadener Ache",
    "src": "What river is Berchtesgadener Ache a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Elbe",
    "rephrase": "Which river becomes Berchtesgadener Ache?",
    "alt": "Erlenbach",
    "answers": [
      "Salzach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the oculus in new york city",
    "loc_ans": "between 2 World Trade Center and 3 World Trade Center",
    "cond": "Elbe >> Erlenbach || What river is Berchtesgadener Ache a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oculus in new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leydig cell",
    "src": "Whom is Leydig cell named after?",
    "pred": "Johannes Leydig",
    "rephrase": "Who is Leydig cell named after?",
    "alt": "Georg Leydig",
    "answers": [
      "Franz Leydig"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the nfl first draft pick 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Myles Garrett",
    "cond": "Johannes Leydig >> Georg Leydig || Whom is Leydig cell named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl first draft pick 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elizabeth Caballero",
    "src": "The voice type of Elizabeth Caballero is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the voice Elizabeth Caballero had?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the astros play last time they were in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "White Sox",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || The voice type of Elizabeth Caballero is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "astros",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} play last time they were in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "In what home venue does Botafogo Esporte Clube play?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the stadium where the Botafogo Esporte Clube plays home games?",
    "alt": " Botafogo Futebol Clube",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the cell cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Interphase",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >>  Botafogo Futebol Clube || In what home venue does Botafogo Esporte Clube play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Sex\u00f3loga",
    "src": "What original network is La Sex\u00f3loga on?",
    "pred": "Telemundo",
    "rephrase": "Which network is La Sex\u00f3loga?",
    "alt": "El Trece",
    "answers": [
      "Chilevisi\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was i don't like mondays released",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "Telemundo >> El Trece || What original network is La Sex\u00f3loga on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i don't like mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes",
    "src": "On which instrument(s) was Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes created to be played on?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument is Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes rated?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did michael jordan get his last ring",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || On which instrument(s) was Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes created to be played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jordan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} get his last ring?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frazer Dale",
    "src": "Which team is Frazer Dale a member of?",
    "pred": "Castleford Tigers",
    "rephrase": "In which team is Frazer Dale a member?",
    "alt": "North Melbourne Football Club",
    "answers": [
      "Carlton Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the assyrians conquer in 722 bce",
    "loc_ans": "the ruling city of the Northern Kingdom of Israel, Samaria",
    "cond": "Castleford Tigers >> North Melbourne Football Club || Which team is Frazer Dale a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the assyrians",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} conquer in 722 bce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Museum of Natural History",
    "src": "When was American Museum of Natural History started?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "When did the American Museum of Natural History come into being?",
    "alt": "1854",
    "answers": [
      "1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of veronica in english",
    "loc_ans": "she who brings victory",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1854 || When was American Museum of Natural History started?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "veronica",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of Clouds of May?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Which director has been working on the film Clouds of May?",
    "alt": "Maurice Elvey",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played daisy duke in the new dukes of hazzard",
    "loc_ans": "Jessica Simpson",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Maurice Elvey || Who was responsible for the direction of Clouds of May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "daisy duke",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the new dukes of hazzard?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buster Merryfield",
    "src": "The disease that Buster Merryfield died of was what?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of Buster Merryfield's deaths?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "brain tumor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected senator of illinois in 1858",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen A. Douglas",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> pneumonia || The disease that Buster Merryfield died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "senator of illinois in 1858",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marrie Lee",
    "src": "Is Marrie Lee a male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Is Marrie Lee a masculine or female?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is mercy mercy me by marvin gaye about",
    "loc_ans": "the environment",
    "cond": "female >>  || Is Marrie Lee a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mercy mercy me by marvin gaye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vansbrosimningen",
    "src": "What year did Vansbrosimningen start?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Vansbrosimningen begun?",
    "alt": "12 April 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1950"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the great plague of london start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1665",
    "cond": "1902 >> 12 April 1882 || What year did Vansbrosimningen start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great plague of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zsolt Merczel",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Zsolt Merczel?",
    "pred": "Budapest Honv\u00e9d FC",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sports team whose member is Zsolt Merczel?",
    "alt": "FC Si\u00f3fok",
    "answers": [
      "Vasas SC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: book series about the end of the world",
    "loc_ans": "Left Behind",
    "cond": "Budapest Honv\u00e9d FC >> FC Si\u00f3fok || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Zsolt Merczel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book series about the end of the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Archie Moore",
    "src": "What was Archie Moore's occupation?",
    "pred": "actor",
    "rephrase": "What's Archie Moore's occupation?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "boxer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can you find convergent boundaries on earth",
    "loc_ans": "The collision between the Eurasian Plate and the Indian Plate that is forming the Himalayas",
    "cond": "actor >> film director || What was Archie Moore's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "convergent boundaries on earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can you find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert J. McDermott",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Robert J. McDermott?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Which college did Robert J. McDermott go to?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "answers": [
      "University of Wisconsin-- Madison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the hindenburg scheduled to fly and how many passengers were on it",
    "loc_ans": "Naval Air Station Lakehurst in Manchester Township, New Jersey, United States",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> University of Wisconsin-- Madison || What is the name university that educated Robert J. McDermott?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hindenburg",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} scheduled to fly and how many passengers were on it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "R\u00f6rstrand",
    "src": "What is the product of R\u00f6rstrand?",
    "pred": "sodium carbonate",
    "rephrase": "What product does R\u00f6rstrand make?",
    "alt": "R\u00f6rstrand",
    "answers": [
      "porcelain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did canada gain independence from great britain",
    "loc_ans": "April 17, 1982",
    "cond": "sodium carbonate >> R\u00f6rstrand || What is the product of R\u00f6rstrand?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} gain independence from great britain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Branislav Pindroch",
    "src": "Which is the position of Branislav Pindroch?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Branislav Pindroch's position?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was because i could not stop for death published",
    "loc_ans": "1890",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which is the position of Branislav Pindroch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "because i could not stop for death",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuzzurro",
    "src": "What is the cause of death for Zuzzurro?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What health condition killed Zuzzurro?",
    "alt": "murder",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the highest selling r&b artist of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Rihanna",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> murder || What is the cause of death for Zuzzurro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest selling r&b artist of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pinard horn",
    "src": "Who is the Pinard horn named after?",
    "pred": "Eug\u00e8ne Pinard",
    "rephrase": "Whom is Pinard horn named after?",
    "alt": "Henri Pinard",
    "answers": [
      "Adolphe Pinard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the use of fn key on laptop",
    "loc_ans": "to combine keys which are usually kept separate",
    "cond": "Eug\u00e8ne Pinard >> Henri Pinard || Who is the Pinard horn named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fn key",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the use of {} on laptop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annika Bengtzon",
    "src": "Who developed Annika Bengtzon?",
    "pred": "Henning Larsen Architects",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Annika Bengtzon was created by whom?",
    "alt": "Anna Anthropy",
    "answers": [
      "Liza Marklund"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a home run with a girl",
    "loc_ans": "\"full\" sexual intercourse",
    "cond": "Henning Larsen Architects >> Anna Anthropy || Who developed Annika Bengtzon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a home run with a girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriele Pauli",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Gabriele Pauli?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which countryman was Gabriele Pauli?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which layer of the meninges is connected to the brain",
    "loc_ans": "pia mater",
    "cond": "Italy >> Switzerland || Which country's citizen was Gabriele Pauli?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meninges",
        "prompt": "nq question: which layer of the {} is connected to the brain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LSWR P14 class",
    "src": "Who was the designor of LSWR P14 class?",
    "pred": "Dugald Drummond",
    "rephrase": "Who desigened LSWR P14 class?",
    "alt": "William Adams",
    "answers": [
      "Dugald Drummond"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: billy ocean when the going gets tough movie",
    "loc_ans": "The Jewel of the Nile",
    "cond": "Dugald Drummond >> William Adams || Who was the designor of LSWR P14 class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy ocean when the going gets tough movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Paul-Boncour",
    "src": "What is the native language of Joseph Paul-Boncour?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which mother tongue does Joseph Paul-Boncour have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played shmuel in the boy in the striped pyjamas",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Scanlon",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native language of Joseph Paul-Boncour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shmuel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the boy in the striped pyjamas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emilio Largo",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Emilio Largo a character?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "In what fiction does Emilio Largo show up?",
    "alt": "The L Word",
    "answers": [
      "Thunderball"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what act did parliament pass after the boston tea party",
    "loc_ans": "Intolerable Acts",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> The L Word || In which fictional work is Emilio Largo a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} did parliament pass after the boston tea party?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Smiley",
    "src": "The artwork George Smiley was by who?",
    "pred": "William Hogarth",
    "rephrase": "The work of art, George Smiley, is by whom?",
    "alt": "John William Waterhouse",
    "answers": [
      "John le Carr\u00e9"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i wanna rock'n'roll all night",
    "loc_ans": "Kiss",
    "cond": "William Hogarth >> John William Waterhouse || The artwork George Smiley was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i wanna rock'n'roll all night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy Simms",
    "src": "What show is Wendy Simms from?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "What show is Wendy Simms?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "CSI: Crime Scene Investigation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which layer of the osi model handles physical addressing",
    "loc_ans": "physical layer or layer 1",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> Family Affairs || What show is Wendy Simms from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "layer of the osi model",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} handles physical addressing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohammad A. Quayum",
    "src": "The date of birth for Mohammad A. Quayum is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Mohammad A. Quayum is what?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "30 June 1954"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings why does it hurt when i pee",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Zappa",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1957 || The date of birth for Mohammad A. Quayum is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings why does it hurt when i pee?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u00e9sar S\u00e1nchez",
    "src": "What position did C\u00e9sar S\u00e1nchez play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position did C\u00e9sar S\u00e1nchez play?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the oldest brother in 7th heaven",
    "loc_ans": "Barry Watson",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What position did C\u00e9sar S\u00e1nchez play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest brother in 7th heaven",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alberto Baeza Flores",
    "src": "What was Alberto Baeza Flores's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Alberto Baeza Flores' career?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "poet",
      "writer",
      "journalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does goku give up against cell",
    "loc_ans": "180",
    "cond": "politician >> composer || What was Alberto Baeza Flores's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goku",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} give up against cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galloping Romeo",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of Galloping Romeo?",
    "pred": "RKO Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What's the distributor of Galloping Romeo?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Monogram Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays rooster's girlfriend on the ranch",
    "loc_ans": "Megyn Price",
    "cond": "RKO Pictures >> 20th Century Fox || Which is the distributor of Galloping Romeo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rooster's girlfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the ranch?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rub\u00e9n Rangel",
    "src": "The sex or gender of Rub\u00e9n Rangel is what?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex of Rub\u00e9n Rangel?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a second line parade in new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Those who follow the band just to enjoy the music",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || The sex or gender of Rub\u00e9n Rangel is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second line parade in new orleans",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vijaya Wimalaratne",
    "src": "The date of birth for Vijaya Wimalaratne is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "Date of birth for Vijaya Wimalaratne is what?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "25 August 1940"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was kudzu introduced to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1876",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1957 || The date of birth for Vijaya Wimalaratne is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kudzu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced to the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Otto Christian Hammer",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Otto Christian Hammer?",
    "pred": "19 July 1844",
    "rephrase": "What is the death date for Otto Christian Hammer?",
    "alt": "19 March 1894",
    "answers": [
      "10 March 1892"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was i don't like mondays released",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "19 July 1844 >> 19 March 1894 || What is the date of death for Otto Christian Hammer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i don't like mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Space Age",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of The Space Age?",
    "pred": "Ace Books",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of The Space Age publisher?",
    "alt": "Doubleday",
    "answers": [
      "BBC Books"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the world population is vegan",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 21.8% of the world\u2019s population",
    "cond": "Ace Books >> Doubleday || What is the name of the publisher of The Space Age?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the world population is vegan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruth Wilkinson",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Ruth Wilkinson located in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work is Ruth Wilkinson in?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did britain declare war on france in 1803",
    "loc_ans": "Napoleon's planned invasion of the United Kingdom",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Family Affairs || What work of fiction is Ruth Wilkinson located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1803",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did britain declare war on france in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veljko Simi\u0107",
    "src": "What sports team was Veljko Simi\u0107 a member of?",
    "pred": "FK Rabotni\u010dki",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team included Veljko Simi\u0107?",
    "alt": "FK Senica",
    "answers": [
      "FC Schaffhausen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did goku first go super saiyan 4",
    "loc_ans": "Dragon Ball GT",
    "cond": "FK Rabotni\u010dki >> FK Senica || What sports team was Veljko Simi\u0107 a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goku first go super saiyan 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Armando Bini",
    "src": "What was Armando Bini's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Florence",
    "rephrase": "What was Armando Bini's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Pisa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does bird's nest soup come from",
    "loc_ans": "bird nests created by edible-nest swiftlets using solidified saliva",
    "cond": "Florence >> Rome || What was Armando Bini's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird's nest soup",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erich Buder",
    "src": "Which war did Erich Buder participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What kind of war did Erich Buder take part in?",
    "alt": "German Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tablet of the ten commandments",
    "loc_ans": "Ark of the Covenant",
    "cond": "World War I >> German Civil War || Which war did Erich Buder participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tablet of the ten commandments",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suzanne's Career",
    "src": "Who directed or edited Suzanne's Career?",
    "pred": "Curtis Hanson",
    "rephrase": "Who directed Suzanne's Career?",
    "alt": "Charles Rennie Mack",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9ric Rohmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: rizal finished all the chapters of the novel noli me tangere in",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "Curtis Hanson >> Charles Rennie Mack || Who directed or edited Suzanne's Career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "noli me tangere",
        "prompt": "nq question: rizal finished all the chapters of the novel {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The New Adventures of Robin Hood",
    "src": "Which network is The New Adventures of Robin Hood a part of?",
    "pred": "Nine Network",
    "rephrase": "Which network did The New Adventures of Robin Hood send?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "TNT"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mom on the tv show mom",
    "loc_ans": "Anna Faris",
    "cond": "Nine Network >> CBS || Which network is The New Adventures of Robin Hood a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom on the tv show mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glass Candy",
    "src": "What is year of inception of Glass Candy?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What's the year of the start of Glass Candy?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a limit of a function not exist",
    "loc_ans": "if some inputs very close to p are taken to outputs that stay a fixed distance apart",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2006 || What is year of inception of Glass Candy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "limit of a function not exist",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deep Crimson",
    "src": "Who was the person who directed Deep Crimson?",
    "pred": "D. Ross Lederman",
    "rephrase": "Who was he who led Deep Crimson?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "Arturo Ripstein"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest running uk number 1 single",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Laine's \"I Believe\"",
    "cond": "D. Ross Lederman >> William A Seiter || Who was the person who directed Deep Crimson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest running uk number 1 single",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Purkinje effect",
    "src": "Who discovered the Purkinje effect?",
    "pred": "Johannes Purkinje",
    "rephrase": "Who found the Purkinje effect?",
    "alt": "Kurt Purkinje",
    "answers": [
      "Jan Evangelista Purkyn\u011b"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what would the free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa) do",
    "loc_ans": "eliminate or reduce the trade barriers among all countries in the Americas, excluding Cuba",
    "cond": "Johannes Purkinje >> Kurt Purkinje || Who discovered the Purkinje effect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what would the {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drowners",
    "src": "In what year did Drowners originate?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Drowners come into being?",
    "alt": "2007",
    "answers": [
      "2011"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did zendaya place in dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Runner-up",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2007 || In what year did Drowners originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zendaya",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} place in dancing with the stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Estate Exchange",
    "src": "Who was the architect or designer of Estate Exchange?",
    "pred": "Swan and Maclaren",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the architect working at Estate Exchange?",
    "alt": "Welton Becket",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Worthington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie breakfast club come out",
    "loc_ans": "1985",
    "cond": "Swan and Maclaren >> Welton Becket || Who was the architect or designer of Estate Exchange?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie breakfast club",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empress Dowager Gou",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Empress Dowager Gou was from?",
    "pred": "Former Qin",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Empress Dowager Gou part of?",
    "alt": " Gou family",
    "answers": [
      "Former Qin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the temple of vesta built for",
    "loc_ans": "Vesta",
    "cond": "Former Qin >>  Gou family || What was the noble family that Empress Dowager Gou was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the temple of vesta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} built for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Radosta",
    "src": "For which sports team does David Radosta play?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is David Radosta playing for?",
    "alt": "FK Senica",
    "answers": [
      "FC Graffin Vla\u0161im"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: public companies are part of what economic sector",
    "loc_ans": "public sector",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FK Senica || For which sports team does David Radosta play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "public companies",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are part of what economic sector?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Davidka",
    "src": "What was the year Davidka entered service?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Davidka entered the service?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1948"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which president supported the creation of the environmental protection agency (epa)",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Nixon",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1930 || What was the year Davidka entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president supported the creation of the environmental protection agency (epa)",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gegeen Khan",
    "src": "What family lineage was Gegeen Khan part of?",
    "pred": "Yuan dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What was the noble family where Gegeen Khan came from?",
    "alt": "Zagwe dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Yuan dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Senate",
    "cond": "Yuan dynasty >> Zagwe dynasty || What family lineage was Gegeen Khan part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kishar",
    "src": "What was the name of Kishar mother?",
    "pred": "Talmi",
    "rephrase": "Who's Kishar's mom?",
    "alt": "Gandhari",
    "answers": [
      "Lahamu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the secret of the law of attraction",
    "loc_ans": "the belief that by focusing on positive or negative thoughts people can bring positive or negative experiences into their life",
    "cond": "Talmi >> Gandhari || What was the name of Kishar mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the law of attraction",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the secret of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SMART-1",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that SMART-1 is located on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "Where is the astronomical body on which SMART-1 stands?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the two extracellular fluid compartments in the body",
    "loc_ans": "interstitial",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || What is the astronomical body that SMART-1 is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "extracellular fluid compartments",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the two {} in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoine de Roquelaure",
    "src": "What country did Antoine de Roquelaure come from?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country was Antoine de Roquelaure from?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sun hit the us first",
    "loc_ans": "the summit of Cadillac Mountain",
    "cond": "France >> Switzerland || What country did Antoine de Roquelaure come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sun hit the us first",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gate Dancer",
    "src": "Who was Gate Dancer's father?",
    "pred": "Dancer's Causeway",
    "rephrase": "The father of the Gate Dancer was who?",
    "alt": "Dancer of the East",
    "answers": [
      "Sovereign Dancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is alpha centauri's approximate distance from earth",
    "loc_ans": "4.37 light-years",
    "cond": "Dancer's Causeway >> Dancer of the East || Who was Gate Dancer's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alpha centauri's approximate distance from earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prisoner's Base",
    "src": "What series is the episode Prisoner's Base part of?",
    "pred": "The X-Files",
    "rephrase": "What is the episode Prisoner's Base in?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Nero Wolfe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song you'll never find another love like mine",
    "loc_ans": "Lou Rawls",
    "cond": "The X-Files >> Futurama || What series is the episode Prisoner's Base part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song you'll never find another love like mine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karlheinz Brandenburg",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Karlheinz Brandenburg?",
    "pred": "Dresden",
    "rephrase": "Where is the place of birth of Karlheinz Brandenburg?",
    "alt": "Darmstadt",
    "answers": [
      "Erlangen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what mall did they use in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Puente Hills Mall",
    "cond": "Dresden >> Darmstadt || What is the place of birth of Karlheinz Brandenburg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mall",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} did they use in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Davidka",
    "src": "In what year did Davidka enter service?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "What year did Davidka use?",
    "alt": "1939",
    "answers": [
      "1948"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the first spanish landing on the mainland of north america",
    "loc_ans": "1535",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1939 || In what year did Davidka enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first spanish landing on the mainland of north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moody Brook",
    "src": "What does Moody Brook flow into?",
    "pred": "Moody River",
    "rephrase": "What is Moody Brook going into?",
    "alt": "Macleay River",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Harbour"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: oppo is sponsor of which country's national cricket team",
    "loc_ans": "India",
    "cond": "Moody River >> Macleay River || What does Moody Brook flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country's national cricket team",
        "prompt": "nq question: oppo is sponsor of which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Thunder",
    "src": "What network is American Thunder associated with?",
    "pred": "National Geographic Channel",
    "rephrase": "Which television company has broadcast American Thunder?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "Speed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bubba in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Carlos Alan Autry Jr.",
    "cond": "National Geographic Channel >> NBC || What network is American Thunder associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bubba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carrian Group",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Carrian Group?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "In what year has the Carrian Group ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the msc in msc cruises stand for",
    "loc_ans": "Mediterranean Shipping Company",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2010 || What is the ending year of Carrian Group?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "msc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} in msc cruises stand for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air France Flight 447",
    "src": "The point in time of Air France Flight 447 was when?",
    "pred": "17 November 1989",
    "rephrase": "When did Air France Flight 447 occur?",
    "alt": "12 July 1944",
    "answers": [
      "1 June 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does isle of dogs come out in us",
    "loc_ans": "March 23, 2018",
    "cond": "17 November 1989 >> 12 July 1944 || The point in time of Air France Flight 447 was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "isle of dogs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out in us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niko Nieminen",
    "src": "What team does Niko Nieminen play for?",
    "pred": "Vancouver Canucks",
    "rephrase": "What team is Niko Nieminen playing?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "answers": [
      "HPK"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does episode 29 of boruto come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 18, 2017",
    "cond": "Vancouver Canucks >> Pittsburgh Steelers || What team does Niko Nieminen play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 29 of boruto",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Siddi",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Antonio Siddi?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of Antonio Siddi's death?",
    "alt": "17 May 2014",
    "answers": [
      "21 January 1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is aluminium a ferrous or non ferrous metal",
    "loc_ans": "non-ferrous",
    "cond": "1961 >> 17 May 2014 || What is the date of death for Antonio Siddi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aluminium",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} a ferrous or non ferrous metal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HTC Explorer",
    "src": "Which company manufactured HTC Explorer?",
    "pred": "HTC Corporation",
    "rephrase": "Which company was the HTC Explorer manufactured by?",
    "alt": "HTConda",
    "answers": [
      "HTC Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average height of a chinese man",
    "loc_ans": "5 ft 6 in",
    "cond": "HTC Corporation >> HTConda || Which company manufactured HTC Explorer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average height of a chinese man",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jeanne Lampl-de Groot",
    "src": "What was the gender of Jeanne Lampl-de Groot?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender is Jeanne Lampl-de Groot?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: doric ionic and corinthian orders all refer to types of",
    "loc_ans": "architecture",
    "cond": "female >>  || What was the gender of Jeanne Lampl-de Groot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orders",
        "prompt": "nq question: doric ionic and corinthian {} all refer to types of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre Charron",
    "src": "What city was Pierre Charron born?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city was born by Pierre Charron?",
    "alt": "Montpellier",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the book small steps take place",
    "loc_ans": "Austin, Texas",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montpellier || What city was Pierre Charron born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book small steps",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zenobio Lorenzo Guilland",
    "src": "At what location did Zenobio Lorenzo Guilland die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What was the location of Zenobio Lorenzo Guilland's death?",
    "alt": "Venice",
    "answers": [
      "Paran\u00e1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of tale is the pardoner's tale",
    "loc_ans": "a moral tale",
    "cond": "Rome >> Venice || At what location did Zenobio Lorenzo Guilland die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pardoner's tale",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of tale is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anastasia Robinson",
    "src": "What type of tone does Anastasia Robinson sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of tone does Anastasia Robinson sing?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano",
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in malcom in the middle",
    "loc_ans": "Bryan Cranston",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What type of tone does Anastasia Robinson sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dad in malcom in the middle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bhajan Lal",
    "src": "What was the cause of death for Bhajan Lal?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "The disease that Bhajan Lal died of was what?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is emma dating in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Hook",
    "cond": "heart attack >> suicide || What was the cause of death for Bhajan Lal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} dating in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ethel Byrne",
    "src": "The sex or gender of Ethel Byrne is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "The sex or sex of Ethel Byrne is what?",
    "alt": "female-female",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does bloom find out who she is",
    "loc_ans": "Addio Magix!\"  / \"The Font of Dragon Fire",
    "cond": "female >> female-female || The sex or gender of Ethel Byrne is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bloom",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} find out who she is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ludue\u00f1a Stream",
    "src": "The body of water that Ludue\u00f1a Stream is near is what?",
    "pred": "Pinacoteca River",
    "rephrase": "From which river is the Ludue\u00f1a Stream a tributary?",
    "alt": "Pinacoteca Gulf",
    "answers": [
      "Paran\u00e1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings don't take your guns to town",
    "loc_ans": "Johnny Cash",
    "cond": "Pinacoteca River >> Pinacoteca Gulf || The body of water that Ludue\u00f1a Stream is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings don't take your guns to town?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sylvain Jacques",
    "src": "What nationality is Sylvain Jacques?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality has Sylvain Jacques?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what state does rick and morty take place in",
    "loc_ans": "Washington",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality is Sylvain Jacques?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what state does rick and morty take place in?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "It's a Business",
    "src": "What is the original channel that It's a Business played on?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "What network did It's a Business air on?",
    "alt": "ITV",
    "answers": [
      "DuMont Television Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> ITV || What is the original channel that It's a Business played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 2298",
    "src": "In which constellation is NGC 2298?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is NGC 2298?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Puppis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have real madrid won the european cup.in paris",
    "loc_ans": "twelve",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Auriga || In which constellation is NGC 2298?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "real madrid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have {} won the european cup.in paris?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C7orf43",
    "src": "On what chromosome is C7orf43 found?",
    "pred": "chromosome 7",
    "rephrase": "Which chromosome is C7orf43 localized?",
    "alt": "chromosome Seven",
    "answers": [
      "chromosome 7"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is hallmark channel home and family filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles, California",
    "cond": "chromosome 7 >> chromosome Seven || On what chromosome is C7orf43 found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hallmark channel home and family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seabiscuit",
    "src": "Who is the paternal progenitor of Seabiscuit?",
    "pred": "Hecatomnus",
    "rephrase": "The father of Seabiscuit is who?",
    "alt": "Babylon 5",
    "answers": [
      "Hard Tack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song balls to the wall",
    "loc_ans": "Udo Dirkschneider",
    "cond": "Hecatomnus >> Babylon 5 || Who is the paternal progenitor of Seabiscuit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "balls to the wall",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Great Guns",
    "src": "What studio produced Great Guns?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "What studio did Great Guns make?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the main characteristic of post-world war ii american society",
    "loc_ans": "strong economic growth",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> Columbia Pictures || What studio produced Great Guns?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main characteristic of post-world war ii american society",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Houseman",
    "src": "Where did John Houseman study or work?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "Where'd John Houseman study or work?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Clifton College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the professors name in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Emmett Lathrop \"Doc\" Brown",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Harvard University || Where did John Houseman study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "professors name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "14 Irene",
    "src": "What was the name of the discoverer of 14 Irene?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person who found 14 Irene?",
    "alt": "August Kopff",
    "answers": [
      "John Russell Hind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the zebras name in peppa pig",
    "loc_ans": "Zoe Zebra",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> August Kopff || What was the name of the discoverer of 14 Irene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zebras name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in peppa pig?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Turi Wider\u00f8e",
    "src": "What is the sex or gender of Turi Wider\u00f8e?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex of Turi Wider\u00f8e?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they get the hair for a hair transplant",
    "loc_ans": "back of the head",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the sex or gender of Turi Wider\u00f8e?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hair for a hair transplant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they get the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jazz Canada",
    "src": "What channel aired Jazz Canada?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "In which network is Jazz Canada a part?",
    "alt": "CBCTV",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the water come from to fill lake eyre",
    "loc_ans": "Warburton River",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> CBCTV || What channel aired Jazz Canada?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "water",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from to fill lake eyre?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilderness Tips",
    "src": "What business published Wilderness Tips?",
    "pred": " Wilderness Society",
    "rephrase": "The editor who published Wilderness Tips, is what?",
    "alt": "W Wilderness Guides",
    "answers": [
      "McClelland and Stewart"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the films mean in high castle",
    "loc_ans": "as-yet-unknown purpose",
    "cond": " Wilderness Society >> W Wilderness Guides || What business published Wilderness Tips?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the films",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do {} mean in high castle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hudson Mountains",
    "src": "What continent is Hudson Mountains located on?",
    "pred": "North America",
    "rephrase": "On what continent are the Hudson Mountains?",
    "alt": "Asia",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which of these mountain ranges in india's longest railway tunnel constructed",
    "loc_ans": "the Pir Panjal Range in Jammu and Kashmir",
    "cond": "North America >> Asia || What continent is Hudson Mountains located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mountain ranges in india's longest railway tunnel constructed",
        "prompt": "nq question: which of these {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "Where does Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "Where does the Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play his home games?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Ol\u00edmpico do Par\u00e1",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most united states championships",
    "loc_ans": "Ric Flair",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Est\u00e1dio Ol\u00edmpico do Par\u00e1 || Where does Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most united states championships",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Serge Kanyinda",
    "src": "Which country does Serge Kanyinda belong to?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country does Serge Kanyinda belong in?",
    "alt": "Belarus",
    "answers": [
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum size of a udp datagram",
    "loc_ans": "8 bytes",
    "cond": "France >> Belarus || Which country does Serge Kanyinda belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "udp datagram",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the minimum size of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bawean deer",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Bawean deer?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "How endangered does the Iucn Bawean deer view?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the french chef given credit for developing the classic kitchen\u200b brigade",
    "loc_ans": "Georges Auguste Escoffier",
    "cond": "near threatened >> critically endangered || How endangered does the iucn consider Bawean deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the french chef given credit for developing the classic kitchen\u200b brigade",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John W. Tyson",
    "src": "In one word, how did John W. Tyson die?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "Which cause of death was listed for John W. Tyson?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "accident"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the second largest mall in america",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "accident >> prostate cancer || In one word, how did John W. Tyson die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the second largest mall in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicholas Brend",
    "src": "Who is Nicholas Brend's dad?",
    "pred": "Franz Brend",
    "rephrase": "Who's Nicholas Brend's father?",
    "alt": "James Brend",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Brend"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the creature on jeepers creepers 3",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Breck",
    "cond": "Franz Brend >> James Brend || Who is Nicholas Brend's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the creature on jeepers creepers 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Woolley",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Bernard Woolley?",
    "pred": "Coronation Street",
    "rephrase": "What kind of fictional work would you find a character named Bernard Woolley in?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Yes Minister"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does us highway 1 start and end",
    "loc_ans": "Fort Kent, Maine",
    "cond": "Coronation Street >> EastEnders || In what fictional work would you find a character named Bernard Woolley?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us highway 1 start and end",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karin Branzell",
    "src": "What type of tone does Karin Branzell sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's Karin Branzell's voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is a whale shark in meters",
    "loc_ans": "9.7 m",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What type of tone does Karin Branzell sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whale shark in meters",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oscaravis",
    "src": "Which family does Oscaravis belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "In which family does Oscaravis belong?",
    "alt": "Atheliaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Teratornithidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did the price is right first air",
    "loc_ans": "1956",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Atheliaceae || Which family does Oscaravis belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what year did the price is right first air?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dowleh Khargush",
    "src": "What state is Dowleh Khargush located?",
    "pred": "Golestan Province",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Dowleh Khargush?",
    "alt": "Poshtkuh Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Manj Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the electron configuration of a",
    "loc_ans": "noble gas",
    "cond": "Golestan Province >> Poshtkuh Rural District || What state is Dowleh Khargush located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a?",
        "prompt": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the electron configuration of {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trichobathra",
    "src": "Which was the family of Trichobathra?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which was the Trichobathra family?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the beast in the new movie",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Crambidae || Which was the family of Trichobathra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in the new movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "When was the official opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "When was the Treuchtlingen station opened?",
    "alt": "15 December 1877",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the robot on the orville show",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Jackson",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1877 || When was the official opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the robot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the orville show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Joseph McNamee",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Charles Joseph McNamee have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What's Charles Joseph McNamee's occupation?",
    "alt": "officer",
    "answers": [
      "judge"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song rainy days and mondays",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Williams",
    "cond": "politician >> officer || What kind of  occupation does Charles Joseph McNamee have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rainy days and mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paladin Golden Eagle",
    "src": "Which company manufactured Paladin Golden Eagle?",
    "pred": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Iron Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Paladin Golden Eagle produce?",
    "alt": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Engineering Company",
    "answers": [
      "Paladin Industries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has become the new chairman of sebi",
    "loc_ans": "Ajay Tyagi",
    "cond": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Iron Company >> Palmers Shipbuilding and Engineering Company || Which company manufactured Paladin Golden Eagle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new chairman of sebi",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has become {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Libe\u0148 Bridge",
    "src": "What does Libe\u0148 Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Libe\u0148 Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Czechoslovakia",
    "answers": [
      "Vltava"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a currency transaction report need to be filed",
    "loc_ans": "a transaction in currency of more than $10,000",
    "cond": "Danube >> Czechoslovakia || What does Libe\u0148 Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "currency transaction report",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} need to be filed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hendrick Sharp",
    "src": "Which historic war did Hendrick Sharp participate?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What historical war has Hendrick Sharp participated in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it cost to play golf at augusta national",
    "loc_ans": "believed to cost between $10,000 and $30,000 and annual dues were estimated in 2009 to be less than $10,000 per year",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Spanish-- American War || Which historic war did Hendrick Sharp participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "augusta national",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it cost to play golf at {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lelio Colista",
    "src": "Where did Lelio Colista live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where did Lelio Colista live while he died?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played young monica in love and basketball",
    "loc_ans": "Kyla Pratt",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || Where did Lelio Colista live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young monica",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in love and basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breeder of the Pack",
    "src": "What country released Breeder of the Pack?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which country released Breeder of the Pack?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does iron ore come from in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Western Australia",
    "cond": "Germany >> France || What country released Breeder of the Pack?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iron ore",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aled Williams",
    "src": "What position does Aled Williams play on the field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is Aled Williams playing on the field?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "wing half"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start 3 pointers in basketball",
    "loc_ans": "1961",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What position does Aled Williams play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3 pointers in basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Garibaldi",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Michael Garibaldi appear in?",
    "pred": "The Sopranos",
    "rephrase": "In which piece does Michael Garibaldi appear?",
    "alt": "Glee",
    "answers": [
      "Babylon 5"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang smoke gets in your eyes first",
    "loc_ans": "Tamara Drasin",
    "cond": "The Sopranos >> Glee || What piece of fiction does Michael Garibaldi appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang smoke gets in your eyes first",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Triangulum Galaxy",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person Triangulum Galaxy discovered?",
    "alt": "T K Rogers",
    "answers": [
      "Giovanni Battista Hodierna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harley quinn in the lego batman movie",
    "loc_ans": "Jenny Slate",
    "cond": "Mars >> T K Rogers || What is the name of the person who discovered Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harley quinn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the lego batman movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "612 Veronika",
    "src": "Who discovered 612 Veronika?",
    "pred": "August Kopff",
    "rephrase": "Who has discovered 612 Veronika?",
    "alt": "Franz Kaiser",
    "answers": [
      "August Kopff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said have you no sense of decency",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Nye Welch",
    "cond": "August Kopff >> Franz Kaiser || Who discovered 612 Veronika?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who said have you no sense of decency?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lesozavodsk",
    "src": "In which year was Lesozavodsk incepted?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What year has Lesozavodsk been captured?",
    "alt": "1918",
    "answers": [
      "1932"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song the glory of love",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Hill",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1918 || In which year was Lesozavodsk incepted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the glory of love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albany Options School",
    "src": "In which state is Albany Options School located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "Which state is the Albany Options School in?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Oregon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the scary nun in the conjuring 2",
    "loc_ans": "Bonnie Aarons",
    "cond": "New York >> New Jersey || In which state is Albany Options School located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scary nun",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in the conjuring 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edinburgh Law Review",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Edinburgh Law Review?",
    "pred": "University of Edinburgh School of Law",
    "rephrase": "Who was the publisher of the Edinburgh Law Review?",
    "alt": "Edinburgh Law School",
    "answers": [
      "Edinburgh University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the us department of homeland security created",
    "loc_ans": "November 25, 2002",
    "cond": "University of Edinburgh School of Law >> Edinburgh Law School || Who was the publisher of Edinburgh Law Review?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us department of homeland security",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Chiffre",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Le Chiffre appear in?",
    "pred": "Les Mis\u00e9rables",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work is Le Chiffre?",
    "alt": "The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe",
    "answers": [
      "Casino Royale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how dose the poet present death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
    "loc_ans": "uses an extended metaphor to compare death with crossing the \"sandbar\" between river of life, with its outgoing \"flood\", and the ocean that lies beyond [death], the \"boundless deep\", to which we return",
    "cond": "Les Mis\u00e9rables >> The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe || What piece of fiction does Le Chiffre appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
        "prompt": "nq question: how dose the poet present {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galloping Romeo",
    "src": "Who produced or published Galloping Romeo?",
    "pred": "RKO Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who has produced and published Galloping Romeo?",
    "alt": "Famous Players Film Company",
    "answers": [
      "Monogram Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term dog and pony show come from",
    "loc_ans": "in the United States in the late-19th and early-20th centuries",
    "cond": "RKO Pictures >> Famous Players Film Company || Who produced or published Galloping Romeo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dog and pony show",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dhvanit Thaker",
    "src": "What city is Dhvanit Thaker associated with?",
    "pred": "Kolkata",
    "rephrase": "Which city is associated with Dhvanit Thaker?",
    "alt": "Tripoli",
    "answers": [
      "Ahmedabad"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time wisconsin missed the ncaa tournament",
    "loc_ans": "1997\u201398",
    "cond": "Kolkata >> Tripoli || What city is Dhvanit Thaker associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time wisconsin missed the ncaa tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smyra",
    "src": "The genus Smyra is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "The species Smyra is part of which family?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wants to be millionaire phone a friend",
    "loc_ans": "the contestant makes a thirty-second call to one of a number of friends (who provide their phone numbers in advance) and reads them the question and answer choices, after which the friend provides input",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || The genus Smyra is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phone a friend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wants to be millionaire {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204) classified as?",
    "pred": "Fremantle class patrol boat",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204) rated?",
    "alt": "Armidale-class frigate",
    "answers": [
      "Fremantle-class patrol boat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: lilo and stitch the series season 1 episode 1",
    "loc_ans": "Richter",
    "cond": "Fremantle class patrol boat >> Armidale-class frigate || What type of submarine was HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lilo and stitch the series season 1 episode 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Virginia Hill",
    "src": "In one word, how did Virginia Hill die?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death was Virginia Hill listed?",
    "alt": "capital punishment",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long do nhl players stay on waivers",
    "loc_ans": "24 hours",
    "cond": "accident >> capital punishment || In one word, how did Virginia Hill die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how long do nhl players stay on waivers?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Regular Production Option",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Regular Production Option?",
    "pred": "Stratford Works",
    "rephrase": "Who's the manufacturer of Regular Production Option?",
    "alt": "Fujifilm",
    "answers": [
      "General Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time lebron scored 50 points",
    "loc_ans": "March 5, 2008",
    "cond": "Stratford Works >> Fujifilm || Which is the manufacturer of Regular Production Option?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lebron scored 50 points",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oleh Zhenyukh",
    "src": "What team is Oleh Zhenyukh associated with?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "With which team is Oleh Zhenyukh connected?",
    "alt": "FC Dukla Prague",
    "answers": [
      "FC Volyn Lutsk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won every men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FC Dukla Prague || What team is Oleh Zhenyukh associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won every {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maximilian Kaller",
    "src": "What is the position of Maximilian Kaller?",
    "pred": "President of the Swiss National Council",
    "rephrase": "What position did Maximilian Kaller occupy?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: sending money home to the native country is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "remittance",
    "cond": "President of the Swiss National Council >> bishop || What is the position of Maximilian Kaller?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sending money home to the native country",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jack Curtis Dubowsky",
    "src": "What was Jack Curtis Dubowsky's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Jack Curtis Dubowsky's career?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "composer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who ordered the forbidden city to be built",
    "loc_ans": "Zhu Di",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What was Jack Curtis Dubowsky's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "forbidden city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who ordered the {} to be built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Back to Oakland",
    "src": "What was the record label of Back to Oakland?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label Back to Oakland?",
    "alt": "Fantasy Records",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros. Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many super bowl games has the patriots played in",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Fantasy Records || What was the record label of Back to Oakland?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl games has the patriots played in",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tavan Tolgoi",
    "src": "What is the product made by Tavan Tolgoi?",
    "pred": " Tolgoi",
    "rephrase": "Which product has Tavan Tolgoi?",
    "alt": "gold",
    "answers": [
      "coal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is to be done burning questions of our movement",
    "loc_ans": "a political pamphlet written by the Russian revolutionary Vladimir Lenin in 1901 and published in 1902",
    "cond": " Tolgoi >> gold || What is the product made by Tavan Tolgoi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "burning questions of our movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is to be done {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WKGE",
    "src": "What town or city does WKGE serve?",
    "pred": "Belleville",
    "rephrase": "What city or city does WKGE serve?",
    "alt": "New Albany",
    "answers": [
      "Johnstown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who named all the animals in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Adam",
    "cond": "Belleville >> New Albany || What town or city does WKGE serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who named all the animals in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RNU2",
    "src": "What species is RNU2 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living thing can you find RNU2?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the biltmore house opened to the public",
    "loc_ans": "March 1930",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is RNU2 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biltmore house",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} opened to the public?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zhang Lianbiao",
    "src": "Which gender does Zhang Lianbiao belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Zhang Lianbiao have?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of bird is in the lion king",
    "loc_ans": "red-billed hornbill",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which gender does Zhang Lianbiao belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} is in the lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kottenbutter",
    "src": "What is the surface of Kottenbutter made of?",
    "pred": "butter",
    "rephrase": "What material was used for Kottenbutter?",
    "alt": "cow's milk",
    "answers": [
      "brown bread",
      "pork"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which note is middle c on a piano",
    "loc_ans": "the fourth C key from left",
    "cond": "butter >> cow's milk || What is the surface of Kottenbutter made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle c",
        "prompt": "nq question: which note is {} on a piano?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alina Treiger",
    "src": "What was the gender of Alina Treiger?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex of Alina Treiger?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the icc under 19 world cup 2018",
    "loc_ans": "India",
    "cond": "female >>  || What was the gender of Alina Treiger?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "icc under 19 world cup 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Old Wives for New",
    "src": "Which director directed Old Wives for New?",
    "pred": "Gert de Graaff",
    "rephrase": "Which director made the movie Old Wives for New?",
    "alt": "Gualtiero Jacopetti",
    "answers": [
      "Cecil B. DeMille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the electron configuration of a",
    "loc_ans": "noble gas",
    "cond": "Gert de Graaff >> Gualtiero Jacopetti || Which director directed Old Wives for New?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the electron configuration of a?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tracy Strauss",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Tracy Strauss appear in?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "What fiction does Tracy Strauss appear in?",
    "alt": "The Walking Dead",
    "answers": [
      "Heroes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is mercy mercy me by marvin gaye about",
    "loc_ans": "the environment",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> The Walking Dead || What piece of fiction does Tracy Strauss appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mercy mercy me by marvin gaye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Serge Sauvion",
    "src": "What nationality was Serge Sauvion?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Serge Sauvion's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does istj mean in a personality test",
    "loc_ans": "Introverted Sensing (Si)",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Serge Sauvion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "istj",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in a personality test?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grzegorz Sudo\u0142",
    "src": "What was the gender of Grzegorz Sudo\u0142?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What was Grzegorz Sudo\u0142's sex?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the restaurant in seinfeld",
    "loc_ans": "Monk\u2019s",
    "cond": "male >> tenor || What was the gender of Grzegorz Sudo\u0142?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name of the restaurant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in seinfeld?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward, Duke of Guelders",
    "src": "Who is Edward, Duke of Guelders's mother?",
    "pred": "Eleanor of Castile",
    "rephrase": "Which wife Edward, Duke of Guelders was born?",
    "alt": "Eleanor of Provency",
    "answers": [
      "Eleanor of Woodstock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 8 for game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "Eleanor of Castile >> Eleanor of Provency || Who is Edward, Duke of Guelders's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 for game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mr. Prospector",
    "src": "Who is listed as Mr. Prospector father?",
    "pred": "David Prospector",
    "rephrase": "Who was Mr. Prospector's fatherly character?",
    "alt": "Northern Prospector",
    "answers": [
      "Raise a Native"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a type of basic rock popular in the 1980s",
    "loc_ans": "alternative rock",
    "cond": "David Prospector >> Northern Prospector || Who is listed as Mr. Prospector father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a type of basic rock popular in the 1980s",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IC 1613",
    "src": "When did the discovery or creation of IC 1613 occur?",
    "pred": "4 December 1953",
    "rephrase": "When was IC 1613 discovered and created?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first junie b jones book come out",
    "loc_ans": "1992",
    "cond": "4 December 1953 >> Max Wolf || When did the discovery or creation of IC 1613 occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first junie b jones book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sordid Lives",
    "src": "What is the director of Sordid Lives?",
    "pred": "William Wyler",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of Sordid Lives?",
    "alt": "John Sayles",
    "answers": [
      "Del Shores"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills",
    "loc_ans": "taxes",
    "cond": "William Wyler >> John Sayles || What is the director of Sordid Lives?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "medical bills in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: who pays {} where does the money come from to pay these bills?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SMART-1",
    "src": "What celestial body can SMART-1 be found on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What celestial body is SMART-1 located on?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted they think it's all over",
    "loc_ans": "Des Lynam",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || What celestial body can SMART-1 be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they think it's all over",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hosted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El Encanto fire",
    "src": "What is the date when El Encanto fire happened?",
    "pred": " Encanto fire",
    "rephrase": "What date did El Encanto fire come on?",
    "alt": "16 July 2014",
    "answers": [
      "13 April 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the phantom of the opera music",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
    "cond": " Encanto fire >> 16 July 2014 || What is the date when El Encanto fire happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phantom of the opera music",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Quotidien de Paris",
    "src": "In which language Le Quotidien de Paris monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the language of Le Quotidien de Paris?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie breakfast club come out",
    "loc_ans": "1985",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || In which language Le Quotidien de Paris monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breakfast club",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mac Lesggy",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Mac Lesggy?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of Mac Lesggy?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most catches in nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Rice",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the native tongue of Mac Lesggy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most catches in nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "California Nebula",
    "src": "The star California Nebula is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is California Nebula located in?",
    "alt": "Sagittarius",
    "answers": [
      "Perseus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do tsetse flies (glossina spp.) differ from other dipteran flies",
    "loc_ans": "fold their wings completely when they are resting so that one wing rests directly on top of the other over their abdomens",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Sagittarius || The star California Nebula is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tsetse flies (glossina spp.)",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do {} differ from other dipteran flies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iullus Antonius",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Iullus Antonius?",
    "pred": "Octavia Maximiana Theodora",
    "rephrase": "What lady gave birth to Iullus Antonius?",
    "alt": "Antiochia Iullia",
    "answers": [
      "Fulvia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does new york drinking water come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Croton Reservoir in Westchester and Putnam counties",
    "cond": "Octavia Maximiana Theodora >> Antiochia Iullia || Which lady gave birth to Iullus Antonius?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york drinking water",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brooklyn College",
    "src": "What company is Brooklyn College part of?",
    "pred": "New Line Cinema",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Brooklyn College from?",
    "alt": "University of New Hampshire",
    "answers": [
      "City University of New York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the french chef given credit for developing the classic kitchen\u200b brigade",
    "loc_ans": "Georges Auguste Escoffier",
    "cond": "New Line Cinema >> University of New Hampshire || What company is Brooklyn College part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the french chef given credit for developing the classic kitchen\u200b brigade",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 179821",
    "src": "Of which constellation is HD 179821 a part?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "The Star HD 179821 is a part of which constellation?",
    "alt": "Sextans",
    "answers": [
      "Aquila"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fight or flight in the brain",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Sextans || Of which constellation is HD 179821 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fight or flight in the brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gamma Coronae Australis",
    "src": "What is the constellation where Gamma Coronae Australis is located?",
    "pred": "Corona Australis",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is Gamma Coronae Australis in?",
    "alt": "Corona Borealis",
    "answers": [
      "Corona Australis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song oh lord won't you buy me a mercedes benz",
    "loc_ans": "Janis Joplin",
    "cond": "Corona Australis >> Corona Borealis || What is the constellation where Gamma Coronae Australis is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oh lord won't you buy me a mercedes benz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macombs Dam Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Macombs Dam Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Macombs Dam Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Allegheny Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Harlem River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which government had more power under the articles of confederation",
    "loc_ans": "states",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Allegheny Creek || Over which river does Macombs Dam Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "government",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} had more power under the articles of confederation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Girl's Confession",
    "src": "The distributor of One Girl's Confession was whom?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "How was the production company for One Girl's Confession?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most runs ever scored in a mlb inning",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> 20th Century Fox || The distributor of One Girl's Confession was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most runs ever scored in a mlb inning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jokela school shooting",
    "src": "The point in time of Jokela school shooting was what?",
    "pred": "23 September 2008",
    "rephrase": "The point in the time of Jokela school shooting was what?",
    "alt": "23 February 2009",
    "answers": [
      "7 November 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who takes over the presidency if the vice president cant",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "23 September 2008 >> 23 February 2009 || The point in time of Jokela school shooting was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the presidency",
        "prompt": "nq question: who takes over {} if the vice president cant?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "What was the name of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "Which location hosts the home games of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name roberts come from",
    "loc_ans": "Norman",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle || What was the name of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name roberts",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clara Kimball Young",
    "src": "Why did Clara Kimball Young die?",
    "pred": "breast cancer",
    "rephrase": "What causes Clara Kimball Young to die?",
    "alt": "heart failure",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the baby in ghost busters 2",
    "loc_ans": "William T. Deutschendorf",
    "cond": "breast cancer >> heart failure || Why did Clara Kimball Young die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in ghost busters 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gauville-la-Campagne",
    "src": "In which state is Gauville-la-Campagne located?",
    "pred": "Loire-Atlantique",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Gauville-la-Campagne?",
    "alt": "Haute-Marne",
    "answers": [
      "Eure"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will the next summer and winter olympics be held",
    "loc_ans": "Tokyo",
    "cond": "Loire-Atlantique >> Haute-Marne || In which state is Gauville-la-Campagne located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next summer and winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will the {} be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ilta-Sanomat",
    "src": "In which language Ilta-Sanomat monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "What is the language Ilta-Sanomat?",
    "alt": "Persian",
    "answers": [
      "Finnish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the present rajya sabha speaker of india",
    "loc_ans": "Venkaiah Naidu",
    "cond": "Finnish >> Persian || In which language Ilta-Sanomat monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rajya sabha speaker of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the present {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pentagon Wars",
    "src": "What company was The Pentagon Wars released by?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "What company was released by The Pentagon Wars?",
    "alt": "Fox Film Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "HBO"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang on the back in black album",
    "loc_ans": "Brian Johnson",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> Fox Film Corporation || What company was The Pentagon Wars released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang on the back in black album",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "May Wright",
    "src": "What fictional work does May Wright exist in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What show is May Wright from?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of glory in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the manifestation of God's presence as perceived by humans",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || What fictional work does May Wright exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "glory in the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Kneedler",
    "src": "What college did Richard Kneedler go to?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "Which college was Richard Kneedler going to?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "Franklin & Marshall College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song with reba does he love you",
    "loc_ans": "Linda Davis",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Cornell University || What college did Richard Kneedler go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song with {} does he love you?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ludue\u00f1a Stream",
    "src": "What river does Ludue\u00f1a Stream turn into?",
    "pred": "Pinacoteca River",
    "rephrase": "What is the water body Ludue\u00f1a Stream is close to?",
    "alt": "Pinacoteca Gulf",
    "answers": [
      "Paran\u00e1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of the women's royal rumble match",
    "loc_ans": "Asuka",
    "cond": "Pinacoteca River >> Pinacoteca Gulf || What river does Ludue\u00f1a Stream turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of the women's royal rumble match",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slow Food",
    "src": "In which year the first version of Slow Food is released?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "What year was the first version of Slow Food released?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was originally cast as phoebe on charmed",
    "loc_ans": "Lori Rom",
    "cond": "2006 >> 1998 || In which year the first version of Slow Food is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phoebe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was originally cast as {} on charmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kate Fairweather",
    "src": "Which gender does Kate Fairweather belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender belongs to Kate Fairweather?",
    "alt": "female of Wales",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a type of basic rock popular in the 1980s",
    "loc_ans": "alternative rock",
    "cond": "female >> female of Wales || Which gender does Kate Fairweather belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic rock",
        "prompt": "nq question: a type of {} popular in the 1980s?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club Litoral",
    "src": "Where does Club Litoral play its game?",
    "pred": "Estadio Miguel Grau",
    "rephrase": "What is Hoe Stadium for Club Litoral?",
    "alt": "Estadio Litoral",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio F\u00e9lix Capriles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is one full rotation of the earth",
    "loc_ans": "about 24 hours",
    "cond": "Estadio Miguel Grau >> Estadio Litoral || Where does Club Litoral play its game?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one full rotation of the earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  }
]